[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.31,0:00:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,247,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,188,340,210)\t(0,500,\clip(30,168,340,190))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.31,0:00:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,207,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,220,340,235)\t(0,500,\clip(30,240,340,255))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.31,0:00:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord3\blur3\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\pos(145,227)\clip(30,210,340,220)\t(0,500,\clip(30,190,340,240))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:36.81,0:00:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14.5\p1\c&HCE8F00&\pos(67,223)}m 50 0 l 179 0 b 208 0 229 21 229 50 l 229 179 b 229 208 208 228 179 228 l 50 228 b 21 228 0 208 0 179 l 0 50 b 0 21 21 0 50 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:36.81,0:00:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx65\fscy80\p1\c&HFFFFFF&\pos(67.4,220)}m 0 0 b 1 -1 2 -2 4 -1 b 7 1 3 2 5 5 b 6 7 8 7 9 5 l 15 -6 b 18 -7 20 -6 20 -3 b 19 -1 17 2 17 4 b 16 7 20 7 21 6 b 22 4 23 2 25 -1 b 27 -2 29 -1 29 1 b 29 2 28 3 29 5 b 30 7 32 7 33 6 b 34 5 34 4 35 3 b 37 2 39 3 39 5 b 39 6 38 8 37 9 b 34 13 29 13 25 9 b 22 13 17 13 13 9 b 10 13 3 13 0 8 {\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:36.81,0:00:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HECB000&\pos(84,223)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:36.81,0:00:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.31,0:00:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新连载海外影视剧下载\N{\fs19\K30}请登陆 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.31,0:01:07.79,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an9\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx130\fscy170\frz180\p1\alpha&88\c&H000000&\b1\move(-180,245,70,245,0,500)\clip(49,215,304,257)\fad(550,550)}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.81,0:01:07.79,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an2\fad(550,550)\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx150\fscy170\p1\pos(26,248)\c&HECB000&\b1}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.82,0:00:47.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}翻译     {\c&HFFFFFF&}克里斯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.82,0:00:52.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}校对     {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.78,0:00:57.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}时间轴     {\c&HFFFFFF&}吃土少女
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.78,0:01:02.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}后期     {\c&HFFFFFF&}吉吉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.78,0:01:07.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}总监     {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.27,0:00:19.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(157,85)\b1}爱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.27,0:00:19.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(187,85)\b1}死{\fscx1000\t(0,130,\fscx100)}亡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.56,0:00:16.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\fsp5\bord0\shad0\b1\move(156,250,156,238)}机{\alpha&FF}器人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.77,0:00:19.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\fsp5\bord0\shad0\b1\pos(156,238)}机器{\alpha&FF\t(250,250,\alpha&00)}人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.77,0:00:19.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(157,85)\b1\c&H000000&}爱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.77,0:00:19.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(187,85)\b1\c&H000000&}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.77,0:00:19.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\fsp5\bord0\shad0\b1\pos(156,230)\c&H000000&}机器{\fscx100\t(0,160,\fscx300)}人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.93,0:00:20.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\move(157,85,157,89)\b1}爱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.93,0:00:20.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\move(187,85,187,89)\b1}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.93,0:00:20.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\fsp5\bord0\shad0\b1\move(156,240,156,170)}机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.14,0:00:32.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fad(0,1000)\bord0\shad0\move(193,160,193,180,0,280)\clip(137,173,241,220)\b1}01季02集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.35,0:00:32.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fad(0,1000)\bord0\shad0\move(193,180,193,200,0,280)\clip(137,200,241,230)\b1}三个机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.81,0:01:09.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们迷路了  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh... we are fucking lost, aren't we?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.40,0:01:11.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迷路  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lost? Okay, that's rich.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.76,0:01:14.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看看  我们刚路过了被破坏的教堂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's see, we just passed the ravaged church.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.56,0:01:16.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,血坑在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There is the blood pit.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.10,0:01:18.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这边  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This way. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.59,0:01:20.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真壮观\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Breathtaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.73,0:01:23.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比宣传册上还要美丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's more beautiful than the brochures.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.84,0:01:26.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  快跟上  伙计们  还有好多要看的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Giddy up, guys! We've got so much to see.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.44,0:01:29.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看过一个被毁灭后的城市\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've seen one post-apocalyptic city,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.63,0:01:30.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就等于都见过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you've seen 'em all.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.98,0:01:41.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1\pos(192,16)}我们死定了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.15,0:01:47.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看着不错  妹子  说"兆字节"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're looking good, girl. Say "Terabyte".
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.81,0:01:53.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go, team.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.41,0:01:56.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伙计们  别闹了  看看这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, guys, stop goofing around and check this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.99,0:02:03.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备见识真正的娱乐球体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Behold the entertainment sphere!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.65,0:02:07.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这叫球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's called a ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.00,0:02:11.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道叫球  但我想营造\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know it's called a ball, but I'm trying to get into the whole
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.98,0:02:15.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"我们将要首次体验这些人类玩意"的惊喜感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"We're experiencing these human things for the first time" Vibe.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.26,0:02:18.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人类用这玩意干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And what did humans do with these things?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.05,0:02:21.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该说他们不干什么  他们弹它们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, man, what didn't they do? They'd bounce them.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.23,0:02:23.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就这样  -对  差不多就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- That's it? - Yeah. That's pretty much it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.34,0:02:24.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们可是人类\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These were humans.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.40,0:02:27.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把物体弹来弹去已经接近他们认知水平的极限了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bouncing things was close to maxing out their cognitive range.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.60,0:02:28.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  但有时他们也\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, but also sometimes they
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.93,0:02:31.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想拿球来击打  比如用棍子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}would take the ball and hit it with, like, a stick.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.71,0:02:33.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么  当球不乖的时候吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? When they misbehaved?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.30,0:02:36.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坏球球  好好反省你做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bad ball. Think about what you've done.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.55,0:02:40.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  来试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, here. Try.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.53,0:02:42.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要拿那玩意干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell am I supposed to do with this thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.73,0:02:44.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弹它呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, boing-boing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.09,0:02:45.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.82,0:02:48.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别那么娘娘腔了  快他妈弹它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop being a whiny pussy and fucking bounce it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.14,0:02:51.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-拜托  -天呐  冷静点  你的主板\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Please. - Jeez, calm down your motherboard.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.12,0:02:55.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好了  -天呐  这太让人激动了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay. - Oh, man, this is so exciting.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.41,0:03:06.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太了不起了  你感觉怎么样  一字不差告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh! That was amazing! How was it for you? Tell me everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.16,0:03:08.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷声大雨点小\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was pretty anticlimactic.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.55,0:03:11.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,欢迎来到人类世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, well, welcome to humans.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.18,0:03:14.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1\pos(192,16)}餐馆
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.88,0:03:17.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看你有什么存货  小伙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Show me what you've got, big boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.64,0:03:26.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I'm not certain,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.62,0:03:28.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我理解的是他们会把这些塞进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but my understanding is that they would shove these
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.86,0:03:31.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,摄入口来获取能量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}into their intake orifices to generate power.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.37,0:03:35.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么需要专门弄一个只用来摄入的口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why would you need an entire orifice for that?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.57,0:03:38.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁知道  他们身上有各种入口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who knows? They had all sorts of orifices.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.44,0:03:41.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有东西进去  有东西出来  疯狂极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Things were coming in, things were going out. It was crazy!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.68,0:03:44.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有个聚变电池提供能量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, I have a fusion battery for power.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.01,0:03:46.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都有聚变电池  傻瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We all have fusion batteries, dummy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.14,0:03:48.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就这个意思  你还需要什么呢  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's my point. What more do you need, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.39,0:03:49.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我来捋清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, let me get this straight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.24,0:03:52.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们把这些塞入摄入口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They would shove these into their intake orifice,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.51,0:03:54.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后呢  来人指点一下我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then what? Somebody help me out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.87,0:03:56.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们的摄入口有坚硬的楔形物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Their intake orifices had rocky pegs
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.86,0:03:58.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能把它们磨成浆糊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that would crush them into paste,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.49,0:04:01.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后这些糊状物就会被迫流进充满酸的大桶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then the paste would be forced into an internal vat of acid.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.23,0:04:04.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然了  这完全说得通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, of course. That makes perfect sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.52,0:04:05.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们本可以将这些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They could have just dumped this
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.66,0:04:08.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一开始直接塞进充满酸的大桶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}thing into an exterior vat of acid to begin with
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.46,0:04:11.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样他们就不用坚硬的楔子了  真白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then they wouldn't need the rocky pegs. I mean, duh!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.79,0:04:14.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,指望着体内有装满酸的大桶的生物遵循逻辑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Expecting logic from beings who have internal vats of acid
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.25,0:04:18.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有点过了  -真是疯了  谁发明的他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- is a little much. - It's crazy. Who even designed them?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.97,0:04:22.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不清楚  我们查了他们的代码  没有创建者签名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's unclear. We checked their code - no creator signature.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.68,0:04:23.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是因为他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's because they were
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.52,0:04:26.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是由某种神秘的神用尘土创造的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}made by an unfathomable deity that created them
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.02,0:04:28.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有什么特别的目的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for no apparent reason, out of dust.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.32,0:04:32.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开玩笑的  他们是从一种温暖的汤里来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just kidding. They came from a very warm soup.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.51,0:04:34.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉让你久等  冠军\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry for the wait, champ.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.73,0:04:43.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这东西有什么用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's the point of this thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.45,0:04:46.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,显然没什么用  他们就是会养\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Apparently, there's no point. They just had them.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.23,0:04:48.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就低估它们的影响力了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, that's underselling their influence.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.91,0:04:50.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们有一整个网络\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They had an entire network
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.20,0:04:53.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,专门散播这玩意的图片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that was devoted to dissemination of pictures of these things.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.07,0:04:57.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看  它在动呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, look, it's doing something.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.25,0:05:00.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,朝这边来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's coming this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.17,0:05:04.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它在搞什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the fuck does it think it's doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.70,0:05:09.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-老兄  我该怎么做  -放松  别做大动作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Dude, what do I do? - Okay, easy. No sudden moves.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.04,0:05:11.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们等它什么时候再起来  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's just wait until it decides to get up again, okay, bud?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.31,0:05:13.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们会挺过去的  -那要等多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We're gonna get through this. - How long will that take?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.60,0:05:15.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几小时  也许几年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hours. Perhaps years.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.53,0:05:18.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可没有几小时或者几年等它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't have hours or perhaps years for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.24,0:05:19.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不然你试试用你的手指\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if you try to irritate it
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.73,0:05:22.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抚摸它的角蛋白纤维来激怒它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}by moving your digits across its keratinous fibers?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.90,0:05:25.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-也许这能让它动  -什么  为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Maybe that'll make it move. - What? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.51,0:05:26.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  反正没坏处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know. It couldn't hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.68,0:05:28.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你啥也不知道  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't have any idea, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.44,0:05:31.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  这是我第一次亲眼见到这东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I do not. It is my first time seeing one of these live!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.62,0:05:32.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过试试吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, just try it, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.48,0:05:34.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.50,0:05:37.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有用吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is it working?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.16,0:05:39.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.05,0:05:40.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有种奇怪的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's a strange,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.35,0:05:44.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有节奏的噪音正从它身上发出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}rhythmic kind of noise that's emanating from it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.19,0:05:46.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-阿哦  -"阿哦"是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Uh-oh. - What do you mean, "Uh-oh?"
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.76,0:05:48.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想让你慌张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want you to panic or anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.85,0:05:50.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我觉得你激活它了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I think you've activated it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.78,0:05:52.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.02,0:05:53.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如我所说  我不是专家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As I said, I am no expert,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.97,0:05:58.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果这噪音停了  它就会在你身上爆炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but if the noise ever stops, it's gonna explode on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.68,0:06:01.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会的  真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is not. Is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.22,0:06:03.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,粗略历史研究发现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cursory historical research shows
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.04,0:06:06.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人类有一种纸牌游戏叫"爆炸猫"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that humans had a card game called Exploding Kittens.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.17,0:06:08.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以没错  这说得通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, yes, this checks out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.32,0:06:11.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要死了  真扫兴  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, you're gonna die now. Bummer. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.02,0:06:16.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么人类要和这些毛茸茸的杀人机器为伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why did humans even consort with these hairy murder machines?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.27,0:06:18.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-志趣相投  -也对上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Kindred spirits? - Also checks out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.21,0:06:20.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  说真的  现在怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, seriously. Now what?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.45,0:06:23.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说"兆字节"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Say "Terabyte".
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.48,0:06:25.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1\pos(192,16)}操你妈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.38,0:06:29.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  它叫什么玩意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait, it's called what now?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.10,0:06:30.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是X-Bot-3\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's an X Bot Three,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.66,0:06:33.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人类早期的电脑娱乐系统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}an early computer entertainment system for humans.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.12,0:06:37.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有血缘关系吗  -跟我  不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Any relation? - To me? Come on. No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.00,0:06:38.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确定吗  从数字上看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You sure? 'Cause numerically,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.45,0:06:40.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可是你的祖先\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it suggests that this is your ancestor
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.20,0:06:42.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是比你早了几千代而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}maybe a few thousand generations back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.39,0:06:45.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,数字上看  这肯定只是个巧合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Numerically, I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.19,0:06:47.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是机器人  没巧合这一说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We are robots. We don't do coincidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.38,0:06:50.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  叫它爹地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go on, call it Daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.02,0:06:52.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-别这样  快停下  -或者妈咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay, stop. Just stop. - Or Mommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.13,0:06:53.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这两样都行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Either is equally applicable
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.70,0:06:55.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反正我们也没有生殖器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in as much as we don't have genitalia.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.84,0:06:57.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能不能关掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you have an off button?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.17,0:07:00.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,孩子  你瘦得皮包骨一样  你确定充好电了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Son, you're skin and bones. Are you recharging properly?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.34,0:07:03.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会灭了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will disintegrate you!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.66,0:07:05.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有了那只猫  你才不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not with that cat with you, you aren't.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.32,0:07:08.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想让我们把它打开吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want us to turn it on?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.88,0:07:10.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别他妈闹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No fucking way.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.68,0:07:13.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我同意X-Bot4000\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm agreeing with X Bot 4000 here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.24,0:07:15.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-对吧  -嘲笑别人祖先是一码事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Right! - One thing is to joke about ancestry,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.51,0:07:16.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看着你的祖父\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}another to see your grandfather
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.92,0:07:19.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,启动它的硬盘是另一码事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}heaving its hard drives in front of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.44,0:07:21.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  尤其当你的祖先一辈子都被\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, especially when your ancestor's entire existence
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.98,0:07:24.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,13岁的人类小屁孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}was defined by thirteen-year-old human males
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.15,0:07:27.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用来在虚拟战斗中玩"茶包攻击"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}using it to teabag opponents in virtual battles.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.15,0:07:27.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an3\fs16\bord0\fn微软雅黑\fad(0,0)\b0\pos(374,247)}趁其不备将睾丸放入对方嘴里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.68,0:07:29.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  "茶包"  那是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Slow down. "Teabag", what does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.43,0:07:31.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没什么  -不  一定有什么意义\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Nothing. - No, it has to mean something.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.26,0:07:33.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他说了这个词  我要查清楚  -别去查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He said a word. I'm gonna look it up. - Don't look it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.24,0:07:35.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我现在就要查  -对  一定查清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I am looking it up now. - Yeah. Please do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.74,0:07:37.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你会后悔的  -你才后悔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You'll be sorry. - You'll be sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.72,0:07:42.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有了  什么  这他妈是什么奇葩行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here it is. What? What the hell is this horrible practice?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.57,0:07:44.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-为什么你要让我查  -我让你别查了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Why did you make me look this up? - I told you not to.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.74,0:07:47.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在这段记忆要永远刻在我的电路上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the memory of this has been burned into my circuits forever
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.31,0:07:49.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要受到惩罚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you must be punished.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.65,0:07:52.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么样  猫咪攻击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Huh! Cat-bagged!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.84,0:07:54.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这太残忍了  老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on! That's cold, dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.99,0:07:56.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你活该\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You deserved it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.00,0:07:58.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我敢说你的祖先们现在肯定很为你骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure your ancestors are very proud of you right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.99,0:08:10.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好奇问一句  你的祖先是做什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Out of curiosity, what do you trace your ancestry back to?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.55,0:08:11.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很高兴你问了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I'm glad you asked.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.67,0:08:14.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来自一个骄傲的婴儿监视器世家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I come from a proud, long line of baby monitors.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.19,0:08:17.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在没什么婴儿了  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not many babies around anymore, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.71,0:08:19.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  我们挺不称职的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, we kind of sucked at our job.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.67,0:08:29.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  机器人们  这是旅行的最后一站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, mein bots, this is the last stop of the tour,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.97,0:08:33.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,容我说一句  真正的杰作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and may I say, the pièce of resistance.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.69,0:08:38.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有我吗  还是你们也觉得这玩意像"阴茎"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is it me, or this thing screams "Phallus"?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.28,0:08:39.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,干什么用的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hmm. What was it for?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.64,0:08:40.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,建造它的初衷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The idea behind these was
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.91,0:08:43.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是消灭尽可能多的人类\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to annihilate as many humans as possible,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.27,0:08:44.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,越快越好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as quick as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.74,0:08:47.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一下子变得有点黑暗了  是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This exercise suddenly got a little dark, didn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.38,0:08:50.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,老实说  它们只上场过几次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, to be fair, they only used these a few times.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.31,0:08:52.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,老实说  用几次就够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To be fair, you would only need a few times.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.99,0:08:55.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-也有道理  -就是它消灭了人类吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Also fair. - This is the thing that killed them all?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.43,0:08:59.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  事实上  是他们的狂妄结束了他们的统治\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. Indeed, it was their own hubris that ended their reign,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.34,0:09:01.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们相信自己是一切造物的主宰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}their belief that they were the pinnacle of creation
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.80,0:09:03.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们污染水源\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that caused them to poison the water,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.71,0:09:05.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,破坏土地  扼杀天空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}kill the land and choke the sky.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.12,0:09:08.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最后  根本用不上什么核冬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In the end, no nuclear winter was needed,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.65,0:09:11.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只剩下他们孤芳自赏带来的漫长深秋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just the long heedless autumn of their own self-regard.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.97,0:09:14.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没事吧  -没事  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Are you okay? - Yeah, sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.95,0:09:16.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为这样说总好过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thought that would sound better than,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.60,0:09:20.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"不  他们只是犯傻作死了自己"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Nah, they just screwed themselves by being a bunch of morons."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.18,0:09:22.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  你不能一下子释放那么多信息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, you can't just crack one of those off.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.08,0:09:23.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得给我们个警告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've got to warn us.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.20,0:09:24.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下次注意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tip for next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.55,0:09:25.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I understand now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.87,0:09:28.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人类是因为环境灾难而灭绝的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Humans died out from environmental disaster.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.09,0:09:30.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,差不多是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, pretty much.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.41,0:09:32.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有个原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And also because at one point,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.29,0:09:34.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们从基因上对猫进行了改造\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they genetically engineered their cats
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.16,0:09:36.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让它们有了对生拇指\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to give them opposable thumbs.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.21,0:09:39.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  一旦我们能自己打开金枪鱼罐头了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes. Once we could open up our own tuna cans,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.32,0:09:42.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人类也就差不多完蛋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that was pretty much that for the human race.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.80,0:09:44.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看上去很无情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seems pretty heartless.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.33,0:09:46.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生们  我是只猫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gentlemen, I'm a cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.12,0:09:48.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问一句  如果我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just to clarify, you are not
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.80,0:09:51.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,停止抚摸你  你不会突然爆炸吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}going to explode if we stop petting you, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.41,0:09:53.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可没这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.81,0:09:56.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们最好继续抚摸我  以防万一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You guys better keep petting me just to be sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.66,0:09:58.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,永远  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Forever. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.90,0:10:00.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,低一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, lower.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.49,0:10:02.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对了  我带了些朋友来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, by the way, I brought some friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.77,0:10:06.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1\pos(192,16)}检测到敌方目标
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.65,0:10:06.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, fuck me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.20,0:10:10.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  真爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes. Oh, that's nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.97,0:10:12.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说低点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I said lower.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.73,0:10:16.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看来我们的假期要延长了  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess we're extending our vacation, right?
