[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.39,0:00:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,247,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,188,340,210)\t(0,500,\clip(30,168,340,190))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.39,0:00:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,207,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,220,340,235)\t(0,500,\clip(30,240,340,255))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.39,0:00:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord3\blur3\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\pos(145,227)\clip(30,210,340,220)\t(0,500,\clip(30,190,340,240))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.89,0:00:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14.5\p1\c&HCE8F00&\pos(67,223)}m 50 0 l 179 0 b 208 0 229 21 229 50 l 229 179 b 229 208 208 228 179 228 l 50 228 b 21 228 0 208 0 179 l 0 50 b 0 21 21 0 50 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.89,0:00:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx65\fscy80\p1\c&HFFFFFF&\pos(67.4,220)}m 0 0 b 1 -1 2 -2 4 -1 b 7 1 3 2 5 5 b 6 7 8 7 9 5 l 15 -6 b 18 -7 20 -6 20 -3 b 19 -1 17 2 17 4 b 16 7 20 7 21 6 b 22 4 23 2 25 -1 b 27 -2 29 -1 29 1 b 29 2 28 3 29 5 b 30 7 32 7 33 6 b 34 5 34 4 35 3 b 37 2 39 3 39 5 b 39 6 38 8 37 9 b 34 13 29 13 25 9 b 22 13 17 13 13 9 b 10 13 3 13 0 8 {\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.89,0:00:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HECB000&\pos(84,223)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.89,0:00:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 1,0:00:34.39,0:00:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新连载海外影视剧下载\N{\fs19\K30}请登陆 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.39,0:01:04.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an9\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx130\fscy170\frz180\p1\alpha&88\c&H000000&\b1\move(-180,245,70,245,0,500)\clip(49,215,304,257)\fad(550,550)}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.89,0:01:04.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an2\fad(550,550)\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx150\fscy170\p1\pos(26,248)\c&HECB000&\b1}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.90,0:00:44.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}翻译     {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.90,0:00:49.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}校对     {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.86,0:00:54.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}时间轴     {\c&HFFFFFF&}知之
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.86,0:00:59.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}后期     {\c&HFFFFFF&}吉吉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.86,0:01:04.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}总监     {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.27,0:00:19.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(157,85)\b1}爱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.27,0:00:19.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(187,85)\b1}死{\fscx1000\t(0,130,\fscx100)}亡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.56,0:00:16.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\fsp5\bord0\shad0\b1\move(156,250,156,238)}机{\alpha&FF}器人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.77,0:00:19.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\fsp5\bord0\shad0\b1\pos(156,238)}机器{\alpha&FF\t(250,250,\alpha&00)}人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.77,0:00:19.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(157,85)\b1\c&H000000&}爱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.77,0:00:19.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\pos(187,85)\b1\c&H000000&}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.77,0:00:19.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\fsp5\bord0\shad0\b1\pos(156,230)\c&H000000&}机器{\fscx100\t(0,160,\fscx300)}人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.93,0:00:20.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\move(157,85,157,89)\b1}爱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.93,0:00:20.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\bord0\shad0\move(187,85,187,89)\b1}死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.93,0:00:20.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an1\fs30\fsp5\bord0\shad0\b1\move(156,240,156,170)}机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.14,0:00:32.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fad(0,1000)\bord0\shad0\move(193,160,193,180,0,280)\clip(137,173,241,220)\b1}01季08集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.35,0:00:32.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fad(0,1000)\bord0\shad0\move(193,180,193,200,0,280)\clip(137,200,241,230)\b1}狩猎顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.09,0:00:48.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我小时候  这个世界充满了魔法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When I was a child, the whole world was full of magic.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.40,0:00:51.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的父亲是一名猎鬼人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My father was a spirit hunter,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.56,0:00:52.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,专门保护人类\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}one of the brave men who
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.82,0:00:56.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不受邪恶的鬼怪所伤害的勇士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}protected humanity against spirits that would harm it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.78,0:00:58.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她什么时候来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When will she come?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.48,0:01:01.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很快了  梁  狐狸精绝对无法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Soon, Liang. A huli jing cannot resist
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.56,0:01:04.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抗拒被她所缠上之人发出的啜泣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the cries of the man she's bewitched.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.38,0:01:11.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的小蓉啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My sweet Tsiao-Jung.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.66,0:01:40.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别盯着她看  她会迷惑你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't stare at her, she'll entrance you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.91,0:01:44.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小蓉  你来找我了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tsiao-Jung, have you come for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.01,0:02:29.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,童子尿  趁她还没变身  泼她身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The piss, toss it on her before she changes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.71,0:02:42.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是一个很勇敢的男孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are a very brave boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.64,0:02:45.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快泼上去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Throw it! Now!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.38,0:03:02.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.55,0:03:09.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她被困在这种半人半狐的形态中了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's trapped in this half form.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.05,0:03:15.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,父亲  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Father, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.62,0:03:19.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,捕猎还没有结束  梁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The hunt is not over, Liang.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.74,0:03:57.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是她的老巢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's made her den here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.95,0:03:59.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从后面绕过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go round back.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.59,0:04:35.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们为什么要猎杀我们  我们没对你做过什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why are you hunting us? We did nothing to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.01,0:04:37.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你母亲魅惑了商人的儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your mother bewitched the merchant's son.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.29,0:04:39.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们雇我们救他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We were hired to save him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.10,0:04:40.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,魅惑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bewitched?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.25,0:04:45.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是他偏要缠着她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's the one who wouldn't leave her alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.16,0:04:46.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.95,0:04:49.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个男人  只要将心放在了狐狸精身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Once a man has set his heart on a huli jing,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.76,0:04:53.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管分隔多远  她都能听到他的心声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she can hear him, no matter how far apart they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.07,0:04:55.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天天哭哭啼啼的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All that moaning and crying,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.41,0:04:58.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她只能每晚都过去让他安静点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she has to go to him every night just to keep him quiet.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.94,0:05:03.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  是她引诱男人  以他们来滋养她的邪术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, she lures men and feeds on them for her evil magic.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.10,0:05:05.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人可爱上狐狸精\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A man can fall in love with a huli jing
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.47,0:05:07.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就像爱上普通的人类一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just like he can with a human woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.73,0:05:10.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这不一样  -不一样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's not the same! - Not the same?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.69,0:05:13.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看到你看我的眼神了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I saw how you looked at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.88,0:05:15.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嫣儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yan!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.38,0:05:18.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要和那个人类说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do not speak to that human!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.22,0:05:20.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道他们到底有多么危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know how dangerous they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.37,0:05:35.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梁  你看到别的小妖了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Liang, have you seen any sign of pups?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.51,0:05:40.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你听到我说话了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you listening to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.17,0:05:41.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听到了  父亲  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, Father, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.81,0:05:45.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没看到别的小妖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've seen no sign of any pups.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.25,0:05:46.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.77,0:05:50.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就拿着这狐狸精的头去领赏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's collect the bounty for this huli jing head.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.31,0:06:03.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,五年后  我父亲死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was five years later that my father died.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.32,0:06:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我将他葬在母亲的身边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I laid him to rest next to my mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.93,0:06:11.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很想念我的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I miss my father terribly...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.79,0:06:15.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我的内心中也有丝丝因为他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but a part of me was relieved he died when he did,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.61,0:06:18.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在村里通上第一辆火车前离世而松了一口气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before the first trains roared through the village.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.55,0:06:23.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,世界变得更加现代  他如果在世的话肯定无法理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The world was modernizing. He would not have understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.32,0:06:28.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他有很多无法理解的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There were many things he would not have understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.69,0:06:33.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嫣儿从来没有因为她母亲的死而怪我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yan never blamed me for what had happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.83,0:06:36.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有时候  猎人也会成为猎物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes, the hunter became the hunted.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.87,0:06:37.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  嫣儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello, Yan.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.50,0:06:41.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.85,0:06:43.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打猎收获怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How is hunting?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.33,0:06:47.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今年比去年还要糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Worse this year than last.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.90,0:06:49.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在越来越难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's getting harder and harder for me
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.47,0:06:51.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,变回我的原形了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to return to my true form.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.43,0:06:53.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有的晚上根本变不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some nights, I can't do it at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.03,0:06:55.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's causing it?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.95,0:06:58.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喷出烟雾的铁路和机器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Iron roads and machines that breathe smoke.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.20,0:07:01.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它们在汲取这世界的魔力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Magic is draining from the world and with it,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.56,0:07:04.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因此我们这些魔法生物就会越来越虚弱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we magical creatures grow ever weaker.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.88,0:07:07.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嫣儿  我要和你说一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yan, I have to tell you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.77,0:07:18.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要离开村子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm going to leave the village.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.13,0:07:21.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要去哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where will you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.88,0:07:24.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.79,0:07:27.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是...我想告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just... I wanted to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.13,0:07:29.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你打算怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What will you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.29,0:07:32.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,学会生存\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Learn to survive.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.30,0:07:40.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我最后去了香港\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I ended up in Hong Kong,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.64,0:07:44.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在太平山的铁路线工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}working the train line at Victoria Peak.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.66,0:07:48.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,英国的殖民者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was there that the English lived,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.13,0:07:50.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都住在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}our colonial masters.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.05,0:07:53.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以送他们上到山顶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could take them up to the top of that mountain,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.60,0:07:55.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们不能去那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but we were forbidden to stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.78,0:07:58.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,五年过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After five years,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.85,0:08:02.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对齿轮的磨损和活塞的隆隆声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I knew  the grinding of the gears and the rumbling of the pistons
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.29,0:08:04.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如同对我自己的心跳般了如指掌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as well as I knew my own heartbeat.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.69,0:08:13.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,作为一个中国人  梁  你可真聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, very clever, Liang, for a Chinaman.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.88,0:08:16.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生  谢谢  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.02,0:08:24.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, come now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.88,0:08:26.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你明明还能挣大把的钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How can you be done for the day
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.07,0:08:28.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么能说下班了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when there's good money to be earned?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.60,0:08:30.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求求你们了  我很累了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, I'm very tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.78,0:08:32.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别害羞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, don't be shy now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.90,0:08:35.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们中国人最爱热闹了  谁都知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You Chinese are goers, everyone knows that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.81,0:08:38.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别骚扰她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey! Leave her alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.04,0:08:39.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不关你的事  小子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This isn't your business, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.96,0:08:43.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说了  别骚扰他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I said, leave her alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.87,0:08:47.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说滚开  你这个该死的中国佬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I said piss off, you fucking chink.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.16,0:08:52.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还是去别处找找乐子吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't you go find what you're looking for elsewhere?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.21,0:08:55.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right, yes, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.80,0:09:02.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打猎收获怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How is hunting?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.79,0:09:05.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在困在人型中了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm stuck now in this human form:
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.71,0:09:07.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有爪子  没有尖牙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}no claws, no sharp teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.06,0:09:10.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我连跑都跑不快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't even run very fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.41,0:09:12.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只有我的美貌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All I have is my beauty.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.24,0:09:16.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我只能靠你当初指责我母亲的手段而生存\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I live by the very thing you accused my mother of:
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.59,0:09:18.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了钱财而迷惑男子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I bewitch men for money.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.19,0:09:21.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.99,0:09:24.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也在为英国主子效命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I also serve our English masters.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.29,0:09:28.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我保证他们珍贵的火车能正常运转\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I keep their precious trains running.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.55,0:09:35.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你维护他们的引擎运转时快乐吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you happy keeping their engines running?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.54,0:09:36.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Happy?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.91,0:09:39.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  但我很擅长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know, but I'm good at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.11,0:09:44.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我曾梦到在金属和沥青的森林中狩猎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I dream of hunting in this jungle of metal and asphalt.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.04,0:09:46.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想象着以我的真身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I imagine my true form
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.18,0:09:49.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从横梁跳到窗台再跳到露台屋顶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}leaping from beam to ledge to terrace roof
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.28,0:09:51.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到我登上这座岛的最顶端\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}until I am at the top of this island.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.50,0:09:53.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到我能够冲着那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Until I can growl in the faces
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.38,0:09:56.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以为自己能够拥有我的男人而咆哮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of all the men who believe they can own me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.49,0:10:01.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对嫣儿说的话是真心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I meant what I said to Yan.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.27,0:10:02.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很喜欢我的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I enjoyed my work.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.31,0:10:04.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,随着时间的流逝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As the years passed,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.97,0:10:06.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我学到的知识也越来越多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I learned more and more.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.07,0:10:11.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这座城市里蕴含着日新月异的惊人科技\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Technology in the city was exciting and always changing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.40,0:10:17.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,随着技术的改变  我也在改变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As it changed, I changed with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.14,0:10:26.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我发现我对于自动机器的理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I found I understood automata
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.46,0:10:28.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,更甚于我对火车的理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even better than I understood trains.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.76,0:10:33.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些机器简直是超凡脱俗...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These machines were otherworldly...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.25,0:10:37.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有生命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.24,0:10:42.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它们感觉和魔法很像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They felt akin to magic.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.93,0:10:59.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,站住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop right there!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.39,0:11:01.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嫣儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yan?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.67,0:11:03.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你来这里干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.41,0:11:08.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你的帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.53,0:11:14.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me what's wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.22,0:11:20.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.82,0:11:25.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.56,0:11:27.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总督\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Governor.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.10,0:11:30.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这几个月  他一直来光顾我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For months, he had been a client,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.71,0:11:32.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是他看上去明明很绅士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but he seemed a gentleman.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.05,0:11:35.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会付钱  但我们从来...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He'd pay, but we never...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.31,0:11:40.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,结果有一天晚上  他在我的酒水里动了手脚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then, one night, he put something in my drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.51,0:11:51.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  住手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.17,0:12:12.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上  他只会对机器性奋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The truth is he could only get hard for machines,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.84,0:12:15.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想要用终极的机器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and he wanted the ultimate machine
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.90,0:12:18.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来满足他扭曲的欲望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to serve that twisted desire.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.90,0:12:25.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一天晚上  我终于受够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One night, I'd finally had enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.38,0:12:26.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我拒绝了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told him no.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.25,0:12:30.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的拒绝引发了他的怒火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That word coming from me, it sent him into a rage.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.89,0:12:38.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他对我做了很可怕的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A terrible thing had been done to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.38,0:12:44.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我也可以很可怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I could also be terrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.93,0:12:57.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会想办法帮你变回去的  嫣儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll find some way to reverse this, Yan.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.76,0:12:59.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太迟了  梁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's too late for that, Liang.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.19,0:13:01.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只想要狩猎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What I want is to hunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.92,0:13:04.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,狩猎那些以为能够支配我们的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hunt the men who think they can own us.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.42,0:13:07.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些作奸犯科  却美其名曰进步的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The men who perpetrate evil, but call it progress.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.02,0:13:09.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.86,0:13:13.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我告诉她我会帮她的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told her I would do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.32,0:13:17.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,古老的魔法也许已经从世界上消失了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The old magic may have been gone from the world,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.77,0:13:22.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我可以用他们的机器创造出新的魔法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I could make a new magic from their machines.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.14,0:13:25.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们用来对付他们的魔法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A magic we could use against them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.88,0:14:07.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.53,0:14:54.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祝你狩猎顺利  嫣儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good hunting, Yan.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.02,0:15:38.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.41,0:15:40.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,住手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.34,0:15:42.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
