[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.99,0:00:16.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有你父母的电话号码吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there a number we can call for your parents?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.06,0:00:18.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的头发呢  你得了癌症吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's your hair? Do you have cancer?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.29,0:00:19.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你离家出走的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you run away?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.44,0:00:21.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你惹了什么麻烦吗  -那是血吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Are you in some kind of trouble? - Is that blood?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.15,0:00:24.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-住手  你把她吓坏了  -她把我吓坏了才是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Stop it! You're freaking her out! - She's freaking me out!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.40,0:00:25.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我敢打赌她是聋子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I bet she's deaf.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.25,0:00:30.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她不是聋子  -够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Not deaf. - All right, that's enough, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.01,0:00:32.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她只是又冷又怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's just scared and cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.71,0:00:40.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给  这些是干净的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here, these are clean. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.35,0:00:52.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不不不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.44,0:00:54.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.42,0:00:57.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看到没  厕所在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See over there? That's the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:00:59.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保留些隐私  懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Privacy. Get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.00,0:01:16.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不想关上吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't want it closed?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.09,0:01:18.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.38,0:01:20.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原来你会说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, so you can speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.28,0:01:23.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, well...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.23,0:01:27.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那不如我们就把门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}how about we just keep the door...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.68,0:01:31.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样掩上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:01:34.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好点没有  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Is that better? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.20,0:01:42.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这简直疯了  -至少她还会说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- This is mental. - At least she can talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.22,0:01:43.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她会说"是"和"不是"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She said "No" And "Yes."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.29,0:01:45.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你三岁的妹妹说的都比她多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your three-year-old sister says more.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.23,0:01:46.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她刚刚差点脱光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She tried to get naked.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.18,0:01:48.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她肯定有什么很严重的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's something seriously wrong with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.65,0:01:51.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-比如脑子坏了  -她就像...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Like, wrong in the head. - She just went like...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.28,0:01:54.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我赌她是从彭赫斯特逃出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I bet she escaped from Pennhurst.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.04,0:01:56.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-哪儿  -克氏县的精神疗养院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- From where? - The nuthouse in Kerley County.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.64,0:01:58.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你们家很多人在那吗  -去死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You got a lot of family there? - Bite me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.03,0:02:00.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过说真的  好好想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seriously though, think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.46,0:02:03.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就能解释她为什么剃光了头发还疯疯癫癫的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That would explain her shaved hair and why she's so crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.59,0:02:04.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么她会...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why she went like...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.33,0:02:07.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她肯定是逃出来的  可能是个疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's an escapee is the point. She's probably a psycho.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.77,0:02:09.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就像迈克尔·迈尔斯[杀人狂]  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Like Michael Myers. - Exactly!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.70,0:02:11.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们根本就不该带她来这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should've never brought her here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.08,0:02:12.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你想把她丢在风雨中吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So you just wanted to leave her out in that storm?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.82,0:02:14.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我们是出来找威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes! We went out to find Will,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.38,0:02:15.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而不是惹上另一个麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not another problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.62,0:02:17.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我觉得我们应该告诉你妈妈  -附议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I think we should tell your mom. - I second that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.53,0:02:19.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这才是疯了吧  -这怎么就算疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Who's crazy now? - How is that crazy?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.48,0:02:22.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为今晚我们根本不该出来  还记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause, we weren't supposed to be out tonight, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.09,0:02:24.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那又怎么样  -如果我告诉我妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- So? -So if I tell my mom
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.56,0:02:26.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她再告诉你妈妈和你妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and she tells your mom and your mom...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.68,0:02:28.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-天  -我们的家会变成阿尔卡特拉斯岛[监狱岛]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, man. - Our houses become Alcatraz.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.93,0:02:31.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  我们就再也找不到威尔了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Exactly. We'll never find Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.29,0:02:35.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样吧  她今晚住在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, here's the plan. She sleeps here tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.80,0:02:37.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你竟然让一个女生...  -听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You're letting a girl-- - Just listen!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.25,0:02:40.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到了早上  再让她溜到我家附近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In the morning, she sneaks around my house,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.00,0:02:41.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去前门按响门铃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}goes to the front door and rings my doorbell.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.91,0:02:44.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我妈妈会应门  她知道该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My mom will answer and know exactly what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.12,0:02:46.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她会把她送回彭赫斯特或者其他地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She'll send her back to Pennhurst or wherever she comes from.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.26,0:02:47.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们绝对不会扯上关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll be totally in the clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.70,0:02:49.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明天晚上我们继续出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And tomorrow night, we go back out.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.59,0:02:51.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这次一定要找到威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And this time, we find Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.14,0:02:58.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来  这是我的睡袋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here you go. This is my sleeping bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.76,0:03:00.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真的觉得她是疯子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You really think she's psycho?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.86,0:03:02.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我才不会让她住在我家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wouldn't want her in my house.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.75,0:03:08.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mental.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.09,0:03:13.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还没问过你的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, um, I never asked your name.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.38,0:03:21.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that real?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.49,0:03:28.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  我只是...没见过有纹身的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry, I've just... never seen a kid with a tattoo before.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.51,0:03:31.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你叫什么  十一吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's it mean? Eleven?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.82,0:03:36.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是你的名字吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.12,0:03:39.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十一  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Eleven. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.91,0:03:42.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我叫迈克  迈克尔的简称\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, well, my name's Mike. Short for Michael.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.87,0:03:47.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许我们能叫你一一  十一的简称\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe we can call you "El." Short for Eleven.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.62,0:03:52.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, well, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.26,0:03:54.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,晚安  一一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Night, El.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.83,0:03:58.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,晚安  迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Night, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.32,0:05:55.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,妈妈  早饭准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, Mom. Breakfast is ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.08,0:05:59.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-小心点别沾到海报上  -好吧  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What? No, be careful of the poster. - Yeah, okay. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.40,0:06:00.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我吃不下  -我需要你吃点东西  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I can't eat. - I just need you to eat, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.86,0:06:04.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  复印的地方大概三十分钟后就开门了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen. Listen, the Xerox place opens in, like, 30 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.59,0:06:05.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是的  -我不想让你一个人去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. - And I don't want you to go alone...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.46,0:06:07.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我知道  我跟你说了  我可以的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I know. I told you, I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.25,0:06:08.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我让凯伦送你去  因为我要在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...so I'm gonna have Karen take you, 'cause I should be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.98,0:06:12.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  -我们得印个两三百张吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay. - We need to make, what, 200, 300 copies?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.35,0:06:13.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-复印一份多少钱  -好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- How much is a copy? - Yeah, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.17,0:06:14.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好了  妈妈  妈妈  -十美分一张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay, Mom. Mom. - Ten cents?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.03,0:06:16.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-如果我们...十美分  -妈妈  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- If we... Ten cents-- - Mom. Mom. Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.90,0:06:19.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能这样下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't get like this, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.72,0:06:22.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-对不起  对不起  -不  没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - No, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.91,0:06:27.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们等了六个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've been waiting six hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.82,0:06:29.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  我尽快赶来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know. I came as soon as I could.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.59,0:06:31.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,六个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Six hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.17,0:06:32.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能信我一次吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A little bit of trust here, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.53,0:06:36.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们搜了一晚上  一路搜到了卡特斯维尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've been searching all night. Went all the way to Cartersville.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.81,0:06:38.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-然后呢  -一无所获\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- And? - Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.25,0:06:39.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}God.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.61,0:06:43.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芙洛说你接到了一个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Flo says you got a phone call?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.79,0:06:46.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.39,0:06:55.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,风暴把电话都烤熟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Storm barbecued this pretty good.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.13,0:06:57.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-风暴  -还能为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- The storm? - What else?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.42,0:07:00.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得这一点都不奇怪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're saying that that's not weird?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.99,0:07:02.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  很奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, it's weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.43,0:07:04.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们能追踪到这电话是谁打的吗  联系...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can we, like, trace who made the call? Contact the--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.66,0:07:06.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不能这样做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, it doesn't work like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.83,0:07:08.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确定是威尔吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, uh, you're sure it was Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.80,0:07:10.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芙洛说你只是听到了一些呼吸声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because Flo said you just heard some breathing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.67,0:07:13.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  就是他  就是威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. It was him. It was Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.59,0:07:18.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他很害怕  有一些东西...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And he was scared. And then something--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.89,0:07:20.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能只是恶作剧电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was probably just a prank call.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.15,0:07:21.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是有人想吓吓你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was somebody trying to scare you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.24,0:07:23.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谁会这么做  -这事上电视了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Who would do that? - Well, this thing's been on TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.32,0:07:24.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会引出一堆疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It brings out all the crazies,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.44,0:07:26.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,假线索  恶作剧电话之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you know. False leads, prank calls, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.30,0:07:29.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  霍普  这不是恶作剧  就是他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, Hopper, it was not a prank. It was him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.99,0:07:32.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-乔伊  -拜托  能不能也信我一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Joyce. - Come on, how about a little trust here?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.51,0:07:35.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么  你以为...我是编出来的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, you think I'm... I'm making this up?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.43,0:07:37.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没说你是编的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not saying that you're making it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.29,0:07:39.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的意思是现在你很情绪化\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All I'm saying is it's an emotional time for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.96,0:07:42.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你以为我听不出自己儿子的呼吸声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you think I don't know my own son's breathing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.27,0:07:45.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你分辨不出你的女儿的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wouldn't you know your own daughter's?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.95,0:08:01.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-朗尼那里有消息吗  -还没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You hear from, uh, Lonnie yet? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.80,0:08:04.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,够久了  我去找他问问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's been long enough. I'm having him checked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.48,0:08:06.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.50,0:08:08.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在浪费时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're wasting your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.40,0:08:11.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍普\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Hopper.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.29,0:08:12.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍普\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hopper.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.48,0:08:15.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.35,0:08:19.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -去朗尼那\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm sorry? - To Lonnie's.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.45,0:08:21.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果威尔在那  这就意味着他是离家出走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, if Will's there, it means he ran away.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.65,0:08:24.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他看到警察  就知道自己惹了麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if he sees the cops, he'll think he's in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.39,0:08:26.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会...他会躲起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He'll... He'll hide.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.34,0:08:28.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他很擅长躲藏  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You know, he's good at hiding. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.97,0:08:31.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警察很擅长找人  行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, cops are good at finding. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.12,0:08:33.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,陪在你妈妈身边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay here with your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.58,0:08:35.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她需要你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She needs you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.80,0:08:57.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克  慢点吃  好恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Slow down, Mike. That's disgusting.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.43,0:09:00.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,昨晚好好学习了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do a lot of studying last night?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.15,0:09:02.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  我学了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, actually, I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.94,0:09:05.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你考什么  人体解剖学吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What was your test on again? Human anatomy?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.71,0:09:09.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.55,0:09:11.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.13,0:09:24.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你找到了我的超级通讯器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, you found my supercomm.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.91,0:09:26.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,挺酷的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pretty cool, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.17,0:09:27.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我用这个跟我的朋友们说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I talk to my friends with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.72,0:09:29.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,主要是卢卡斯  因为他住得最近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mostly Lucas, 'cause he lives so close.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.95,0:09:31.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,信号挺弱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Signal's pretty weak.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.16,0:09:36.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你带了早餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got you breakfast.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.95,0:09:40.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  这听上去有点怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So listen, this is gonna sound a little weird,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.84,0:09:42.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我要你走出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I just need you to go out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.54,0:09:44.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后走到前门按门铃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then go to the front door and ring the doorbell.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.82,0:09:45.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我妈妈会应门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My mom will answer
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.77,0:09:47.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后你告诉她你迷路了需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you'll tell her that you're lost and that you need help.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.93,0:09:49.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但不管你做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But whatever you do,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.13,0:09:52.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你都不能告诉她你昨天晚上的事或者你认识我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can't tell her about last night or that you know me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.66,0:09:53.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.53,0:09:55.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的  这不是什么大事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really, it's no big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.84,0:09:58.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只要装作再认识一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll just pretend to meet each other again.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.04,0:10:01.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且我妈妈会知道要联系谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And my mom, she'll know who to call.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.47,0:10:05.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.67,0:10:07.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.58,0:10:09.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.37,0:10:13.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行...你不想让我妈找人帮忙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No... you don't want my mom to get help?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.83,0:10:21.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你惹了麻烦  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're in trouble, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.22,0:10:25.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.49,0:10:29.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你给谁惹了麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who are you in trouble with?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.06,0:10:32.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.03,0:10:34.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.73,0:10:36.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坏人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bad people?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.75,0:10:41.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们要伤害你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They want to hurt you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.80,0:10:43.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坏人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The bad people?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.06,0:10:55.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.79,0:10:59.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克尔  你在哪里  我们要迟到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Michael, where are you? We're going to be late.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.08,0:11:01.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-快走吧  -好吧  我会回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Let's go! - All right, I'll be back.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.17,0:11:02.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就待在这好吗  待在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just stay here, okay? Stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.53,0:11:11.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么时候的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When was this?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.60,0:11:13.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,昨晚  不到三公里开外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Last night. Less than two miles away.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.31,0:11:15.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那个男孩呢  -依然失踪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- And the boy? - Still missing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.94,0:11:18.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我的儿子  我知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was my son. I know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.45,0:11:20.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我...我还听到了别的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I... I heard something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.38,0:11:22.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something else?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.21,0:11:25.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像是...某种动物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was like, uh, some kind of animal.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.90,0:11:27.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.03,0:11:30.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请你让霍普快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just please tell Hop to hurry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.14,0:11:34.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔  威尔·拜耶斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will! Will Byers!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.84,0:11:36.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔·拜耶斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will Byers!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.38,0:11:40.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-威尔  -威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Will! - Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.41,0:11:44.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找了什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.47,0:11:46.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.49,0:11:49.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除了没电的电话什么都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, nothing but a dead phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.79,0:11:50.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔伊呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Joyce?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.19,0:11:53.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快要崩溃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}About one step from falling off the edge.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.58,0:11:56.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她一直以来就不是很正常吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's been a few steps for a while now, hasn't she?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.16,0:11:57.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兄弟  她的孩子失踪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kid's missing, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.18,0:11:59.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放尊重点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Show a little class.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.40,0:12:02.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行了  快来  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right. Come on, let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.97,0:12:04.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还有很大一片地要找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got a lot of ground to cover.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.53,0:12:07.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,局长和她之前有一腿吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The chief and her, they've screwed before, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.28,0:12:11.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.01,0:12:13.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这算是肯定吗  还是他俩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That a "Yeah" or did they...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.36,0:12:16.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-威尔  -威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Will! - Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.42,0:12:23.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}霍金斯高中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.37,0:12:27.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"当α粒子穿过金箔  它们会变成..."\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"When alpha particles go through gold foil, they become..."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.51,0:12:29.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-原子空穴  -"一个分子能..."\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Unoccupied space. - "A molecule that can--"
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.79,0:12:31.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.53,0:12:32.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得你学得够多了  南希\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think you've studied enough, Nance.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.75,0:12:35.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-史蒂夫  -我告诉你  你没问题的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Steve-- - I'm telling you, you know, you got this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.08,0:12:37.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别担心  来说更重要的事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't worry. Now, on to more important matters.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.29,0:12:40.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爸要出城开会  我妈要跟他一起去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My dad has left town on a conference and my mom's gone with him,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.53,0:12:42.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-因为她不信他  -也对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- 'cause, you know, she doesn't trust him. - Good call.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.28,0:12:44.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你有兴趣吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So are you in?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.19,0:12:45.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有兴趣干吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In for what?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.33,0:12:47.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有家长  只有大房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No parents? Big house?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.90,0:12:49.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A party?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.16,0:12:50.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回答正确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ding, ding, ding!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.93,0:12:52.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天是周二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's Tuesday.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.40,0:12:54.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天是周二  我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's Tuesday! Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.63,0:12:55.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.51,0:12:57.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是个小派对  就我们几个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It'll be low key. It'll just be us.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.57,0:13:00.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么样  你来不来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you say? Are you in or are you out?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.69,0:13:03.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  你们看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God. Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.63,0:13:06.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  真令人难过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God, that's depressing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.12,0:13:11.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们要不要说点什么  -我觉得他不会说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Should we say something? - I don't think he speaks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.07,0:13:13.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要不要赌一把是他杀了他弟弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How much you want to bet he killed him?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.85,0:13:15.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.73,0:13:23.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}你见过我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.96,0:13:27.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.99,0:13:30.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wanted to say, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.29,0:13:33.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对这一切我感到很遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry about everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.64,0:13:41.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家都挺担心你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone's thinking about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.46,0:13:45.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这糟透了  -是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It sucks. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.30,0:13:50.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他一定没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure he's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.76,0:13:52.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是个聪明的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's a smart kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.41,0:13:57.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得走了  有化学考试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have to go. Chemistry test.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.25,0:13:58.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.54,0:14:00.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-祝你好运  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Good luck. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.54,0:14:06.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全体教职工与同学请注意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Attention, faculty and students.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.04,0:14:10.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今晚八点在足球场将举办协助寻找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At 8 P.M. tonight, there will be an assembly on the football field
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.56,0:14:13.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔·拜耶斯及帮助其家人的集会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in support of Will Byers and his family.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.42,0:14:15.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望大家踊跃参与\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All are encouraged to attend.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.73,0:14:17.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自愿加入搜救队的报名表\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Volunteer sign-ups for search parties
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.68,0:14:19.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以在办公室领取\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are still available in the office.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.68,0:14:27.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, this is weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.39,0:14:28.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他从来不迟到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's never this late.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.32,0:14:30.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我跟你说了  他那个愚蠢的计划没用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm telling you, his stupid plan failed.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.73,0:14:31.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还以为你赞同他的计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you liked his plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.76,0:14:34.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  但那明显很愚蠢  要不他就该到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, but obviously it was stupid, or he'd be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.10,0:14:36.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他妈妈发现一个女孩在他家过夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If his mom found out a girl spent the night--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.24,0:14:37.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他现在就麻烦大了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's in deep shit right about now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.37,0:14:40.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果她是裸睡呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if she slept naked?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.76,0:14:42.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  她不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God, she didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.65,0:14:44.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果维勒夫人告诉我父母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, if Mrs. Wheeler tells my parents...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.85,0:14:47.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不可能  迈克不会出卖我们  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No way. Mike would never rat us out. - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.61,0:14:49.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,重要的是  放学之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All that matters is, after school,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.27,0:14:51.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个怪人就会回到精神病院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the freak will be back in the loony bin,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.12,0:14:54.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就可以专心做真正重要的事  找到威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and we can focus on what really matters, finding Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.57,0:15:11.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要不要喝点什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want anything to drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.61,0:15:14.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有橙汁  脱脂牛奶  还有什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have OJ, skim milk... What else?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.03,0:15:16.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, we have...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.93,0:15:20.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我家客厅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, this is my living room.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.93,0:15:22.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,基本只是用来看电视的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's mostly just for watching TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.50,0:15:24.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很赞吧  22英寸的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice, right? It's a 22-inch.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.60,0:15:27.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比达斯汀家的大十倍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's, like, ten times bigger than Dustin's.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.76,0:15:41.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-漂亮  -是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Pretty. - I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.22,0:15:42.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是我姐姐南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's my sister Nancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.87,0:15:44.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是我妹妹霍莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that's baby Holly.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.25,0:15:45.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是我父母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And those are my parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.99,0:15:47.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你父母呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are your parents like?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.94,0:15:49.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们住在这附近吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do they live close?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.72,0:15:53.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我们的懒人椅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's our La-Z-Boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.92,0:15:56.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爸爸都在这里睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's where my dad sleeps.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.87,0:15:58.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想的话可以试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can try it if you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.97,0:16:00.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.77,0:16:03.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好玩的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.92,0:16:08.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相信我  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just trust me, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.29,0:16:16.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是不是很好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See? Fun, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.34,0:16:19.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你来试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now you try.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.76,0:17:03.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喜欢吗  -喜欢  挺好听的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You like it? - Yeah, it's cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.71,0:17:05.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想要的话这盘混音带可以给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, you can keep the mix if you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.26,0:17:06.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-真的吗  -真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Really? - Yeah, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.89,0:17:08.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有的好歌都在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All the best stuff's on there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.19,0:17:11.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快乐分裂  鲍威  电视乐队  史密斯乐团\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Joy Division, Bowie, Television, The Smiths...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.19,0:17:11.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an3\fs16\bord0\fn微软雅黑\fad(0,0)\b0\pos(374,247)}均为70年代流行的摇滚音乐人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.50,0:17:12.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能完全改变你的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It'll totally change your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.91,0:17:14.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  完全能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, totally.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.77,0:17:16.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你到底在哪里  朗尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where the hell are you, Lonnie?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.83,0:17:19.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想听  我不想听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want to hear it. I don't want to hear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.04,0:17:27.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太荒谬了  我受够了你这些借口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is ridiculous! I'm so sick of your excuses.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.27,0:17:31.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不会来了  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's not coming, is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.20,0:17:34.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你难道喜欢棒球吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you even like baseball?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.84,0:17:38.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不喜欢  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, but... I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.20,0:17:40.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-偶尔跟他一起玩也挺有意思的  -拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's fun to go with him sometimes. - Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.33,0:17:42.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他有跟你一起做过什么你真正喜欢的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Has he ever done anything with you that you actually like?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.10,0:17:44.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打游戏什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, like the arcade or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.67,0:17:48.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我不知道  -没有  他从没做过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I don't know. - No, all right? He hasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.38,0:17:50.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他只是逼着你去喜欢正常的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's trying to force you to like normal things.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.22,0:17:51.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你不应该喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you shouldn't like things
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.30,0:17:53.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别人逼你喜欢的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because people tell you you're supposed to.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.86,0:17:54.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.81,0:17:57.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尤其不能听他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Especially not him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.22,0:18:01.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你真的喜欢碰撞乐队吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you like The Clash? For real?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.54,0:18:03.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For real. Definitely.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.35,0:18:20.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}离开霍金斯\N欢迎下次再来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.03,0:18:43.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔伊  我没想到你今天会来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Joyce, I wasn't expecting you today.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.40,0:18:46.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我让杰弗里来顶班了  -我不是来工作的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I brought Jeffrey in to cover. - I'm not here to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.73,0:18:47.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.12,0:18:49.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,昨晚的暴风雨  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The storm last night, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.37,0:18:52.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得新买个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need a new phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.16,0:18:57.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一共22.56元\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, that looks like $22.56.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.72,0:18:59.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, yeah, you know, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.63,0:19:02.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把钱都给了乔纳森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I gave Jonathan all my money for...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.06,0:19:04.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去复印寻人启事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the copies for the posters.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.06,0:19:07.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要预支薪水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need an advance.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.03,0:19:09.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, well, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.13,0:19:12.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-当然  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Of course. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.21,0:19:18.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能不能预支两个星期的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, uh, I was thinking, two weeks?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.23,0:19:26.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我理解  不过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, I understand, but, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.10,0:19:27.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰弗里替班的钱得给他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have to pay Jeffrey for covering--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.73,0:19:28.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唐纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Donald.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.94,0:19:32.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在这儿工作十年了  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been here ten years, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.04,0:19:35.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你请过病假或翘过班吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have I ever called in sick or missed a shift once?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.24,0:19:39.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我连平安夜和感恩节也照常上班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've worked, uh, Christmas Eve and Thanksgiving.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.92,0:19:42.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道我儿子在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know where my boy is.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.09,0:19:44.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他失踪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.24,0:19:48.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道还能否再见到他  他有没有受伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know if I'm... gonna ever see him again, if he's hurt...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.35,0:19:51.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.11,0:19:56.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要这台电话  还要预支两周薪水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need this phone and two weeks' advance.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.32,0:20:01.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加上一包骆驼牌香烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And a pack of Camels.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.42,0:20:14.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有人  -收到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We're all clear. - Copy that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.95,0:21:13.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,惊人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Extraordinary.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.91,0:21:19.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你准备好了吗  知道什么叫准备吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ready are you? What knows you of ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.40,0:21:20.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他名叫尤达\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His name's Yoda.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.51,0:21:24.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他能用原力隔空移物  像这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He can use the Force to move things with his mind, like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.89,0:21:28.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这只是我的恐龙  罗里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, this is my dinosaur, Rory.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.62,0:21:30.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看  他嘴里有个喇叭所以他能吼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, he has a speaker in his mouth so he can roar.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.30,0:21:41.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些都是我科学展览的奖杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These are all my science fair trophies.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.01,0:21:43.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们每年都得第一名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got first every year.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.93,0:21:46.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除了去年  去年我们第三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Except for last year when we got third.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.96,0:21:47.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}霍金斯中学  小组解题赛  冠军
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.54,0:21:48.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,克拉克老师说完全是暗箱操作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mr. Clarke said it was totally political.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.04,0:21:51.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}火山爆发
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.86,0:22:09.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你认识威尔吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.10,0:22:15.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有看到他吗  昨晚  在路上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you see him? Last night? On the road?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.82,0:22:22.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们该走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We gotta go.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.63,0:22:28.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我买了披萨跟通心粉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I bought pizza and macaroni.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.22,0:22:31.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.56,0:22:36.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,泰德  是你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ted? Is that you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.13,0:22:37.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我  妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just me, Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.06,0:22:39.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-迈克  你怎么在家  -等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mike? What are you doing home? - One second!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.18,0:22:46.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,进去吧  我马上回来  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In here. I'll be right back, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.50,0:22:49.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托你一定要躲进去  否则我妈会发现你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, you have to get in, or my mom, she'll find you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.22,0:22:50.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.82,0:22:53.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会告诉她你的事  我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I won't tell her about you. I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.47,0:22:54.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Promise?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.26,0:22:56.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,意思就是不能违背的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It means something that you can't break.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.11,0:22:57.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-永远不能  -迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Ever. - Michael?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.30,0:23:00.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.05,0:23:19.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pop!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.99,0:23:24.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.82,0:23:27.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.44,0:23:28.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.22,0:23:30.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.66,0:23:33.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.68,0:23:34.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,住手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.71,0:23:38.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.93,0:23:39.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.72,0:23:41.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.75,0:23:43.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.38,0:23:45.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.93,0:23:50.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.91,0:24:01.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是...身体不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just... I don't feel good.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.18,0:24:05.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一起床  头很疼  真的好疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I woke up and my head, it really hurt bad,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.03,0:24:07.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喉咙也沙哑  我本来想告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and my throat was all scratchy, and I wanted to tell you,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.49,0:24:08.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我上次说我生病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but the last time I told you I was sick
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.80,0:24:10.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你还是让我去上学了...  -迈克尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- you made me go to school anyway, and-- - Michael.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.15,0:24:13.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -我没生你的气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah? - I'm not mad at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.11,0:24:17.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有吗  -当然没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No? - No, of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.17,0:24:21.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最近威尔的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All this that's been going on with Will,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.30,0:24:24.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我简直无法想象你的感受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't imagine what it's been like for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.98,0:24:26.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.70,0:24:29.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你有心事能找我谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want you to feel like you can talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.14,0:24:33.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不希望你觉得有什么需要隐瞒我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I never want you to feel like you have to hide anything from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.66,0:24:36.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会支持你的  懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm here for you. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.38,0:24:39.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有别人在这里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there someone else here?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.58,0:24:42.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.35,0:24:45.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Eleven?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.79,0:24:46.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.53,0:24:48.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}El?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.77,0:24:54.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-迈克  -你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mike. - Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.97,0:24:58.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.57,0:25:01.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.39,0:25:41.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-威尔·拜耶斯  -威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Will Byers! - Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.33,0:25:45.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小心  小心点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Careful, careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.24,0:25:47.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我至少还需要你多活个几天呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you alive for the next few days, at least.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.43,0:25:49.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  我掉下去也能活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, hell, I could survive that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.98,0:25:52.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么  乔治·伯恩斯就跳下去过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? George Burness made the jump.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.84,0:25:55.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他当时太醉了  和人打赌十元跳了下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And he was drunk as a skunk. He did it on a $10 bet.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.48,0:25:56.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治是个骗子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}George is a liar.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.52,0:25:57.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从这么高地方跳下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You make that jump from this height,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.65,0:25:59.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,水面也会变成水泥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that water turns into cement.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.58,0:26:00.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就像砸在一吨砖头上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hits you like a ton of bricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.88,0:26:02.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会粉身碎骨的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Break every damn bone in your body.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.17,0:26:06.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.86,0:26:08.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,局长  在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Chief, you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.87,0:26:11.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在  芙洛  请说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, Flo, talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.58,0:26:13.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,局长  我们接到本尼餐厅来电\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Chief, we got a call from over at Benny's.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.89,0:26:15.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你最好马上赶过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think you need to get there right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.04,0:26:31.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}本尼汉堡店
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.38,0:26:40.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.82,0:26:47.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Suicide?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.82,0:26:53.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,失踪儿童  自杀案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Missing kid, suicide...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.15,0:26:55.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你肯定找回大城市警察的感觉了吧  局长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You must feel like a big city cop again, huh, Chief?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.46,0:26:59.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过当时我几乎办的都是陌生人的案子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I mostly dealt with strangers back then.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.51,0:27:03.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,本尼是我朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Benny was my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.29,0:27:42.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.08,0:27:44.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.07,0:27:50.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有事吗  -朗尼在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Can I help you? -Yeah, is Lonnie around?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.48,0:27:52.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他在后院  你想做什么  -看一看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah, he's out back. What do you want? - To look around.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.56,0:27:54.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在做什么  -我很快的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Hey, what do you think you're doing? - I'll be fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.22,0:27:56.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.65,0:27:57.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.99,0:27:59.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔  你在这儿吗  威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will, you here? Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.13,0:28:06.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放开我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get off!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.53,0:28:09.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死的  你变壮了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Damn, you've gotten stronger.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.19,0:28:11.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人能解释一下到底发生什么了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will someone please explain what the hell is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.17,0:28:14.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔纳森  这是辛西娅  辛西娅  这是乔纳森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jonathan, Cynthia. Cynthia, this is Jonathan.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.69,0:28:16.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的大儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My oldest.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.82,0:28:21.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-过来  -放开我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Come here. - Get off me, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.72,0:28:36.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你疯了吗  -听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Are you out of your mind? - Just listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.84,0:28:39.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你疯了  -她知道威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You are out of your mind! - She knows about Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.07,0:28:40.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说她知道威尔什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you mean she knows about Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.88,0:28:43.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在他的照片里指出了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She pointed at him, at his picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.77,0:28:45.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她知道他失踪了  我看得出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She knew he was missing. I could tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.34,0:28:46.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你看得出  -仔细想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You could tell? - Just think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.78,0:28:48.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得我们在幽暗密林找到她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you really think it was a coincidence
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.12,0:28:49.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是个巧合吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that we found her on Mirkwood,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.43,0:28:51.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔就是在那里失踪的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the same place where Will disappeared?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.08,0:28:53.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是很蹊跷  -她说有坏人在追她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- That is weird. - And she said bad people are after her.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.67,0:28:56.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想这些坏人也抓走了威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think maybe these bad people are the same ones that took Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.72,0:28:58.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得她知道他发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think she knows what happened to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.07,0:28:59.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那她为什么不告诉我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then why doesn't she tell us?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.36,0:29:04.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道他在哪里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know where he is?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.29,0:29:05.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道威尔在哪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know where Will is?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.50,0:29:07.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-停下  你吓着她了  -她应该害怕的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Stop it, you're scaring her! - She should be scared!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.03,0:29:10.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你知道他在哪  快告诉我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you know where he is, tell us!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.84,0:29:14.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这简直疯了  我们得把她带去你妈妈那\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is nuts. We have to take her to your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.27,0:29:17.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行  十一说告诉任何大人会让我们身陷危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! Eleven said telling any adult would put us in danger.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.13,0:29:19.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么样的危险  -她叫十一吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What kind of danger? - Her name is Eleven?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.61,0:29:22.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-昵称一一  -迈克  什么样的危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- El for short. - Mike, what kind of danger?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.17,0:29:23.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,危险的危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Danger danger.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.76,0:29:31.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.84,0:29:34.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还是得照原计划行事  我们要告诉你妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're going back to plan A. We're telling your mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.14,0:29:47.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.96,0:29:56.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看这宝贝  你真该看看刚买时的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take a look at this beaut. Should've seen it when I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.23,0:29:57.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,花了我一年  不过就要完成了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Took me a year, but it's almost done.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.14,0:30:02.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的吗  你要不要检查一下我的屁股\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really? You want to check up my ass, too?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.85,0:30:04.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把告诉警察的都告诉你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you the same thing as I told those cops,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.39,0:30:06.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不在这也从没来过这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he's not here and he never has been.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.11,0:30:09.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那为什么不回妈妈电话  -不知道  我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Then why didn't you call Mom back? - I don't know, I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.32,0:30:11.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为想她只是忘了他在哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I assumed she just forgot where he was.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.80,0:30:13.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他迷路了或者怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, he was lost or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.63,0:30:16.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那孩子从来不知道照顾自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That boy never was very good at taking care of himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.62,0:30:18.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是什么玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This isn't some joke, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.31,0:30:19.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,搜救队  记者都来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are search parties, reporters...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.96,0:30:21.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍普不会还是局长吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hopper's not still chief, is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.52,0:30:25.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉你妈她得带你离开那个破地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell your mother she's gotta get you out of that hellhole.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.61,0:30:27.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来城市里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come out here to the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.61,0:30:30.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里的人都更真实  你懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People are more real here, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.63,0:30:32.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样我也可以多见你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then I could see you more.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.46,0:30:38.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你以为我不想见你吗  -我知道你不想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What, you think I don't want to see you? - I know you don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.21,0:30:40.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看  这一定是你妈说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, that's your mother talkin' right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.06,0:30:42.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她知道你在这吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She even know you're here?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.38,0:30:44.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,棒极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, great.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.11,0:30:46.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个孩子失踪了  另一个孩子到处乱跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So one kid goes missing, the other one runs wild?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.11,0:30:49.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真是好家教\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some real fine parenting right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.46,0:30:52.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我只想说  可能混蛋的并是不我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, all I'm saying is, maybe I'm not the asshole, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.62,0:30:59.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以防你不记得他长什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In case you forgot what he looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.93,0:31:01.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}你见过我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.73,0:31:03.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还挺帅的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's kinda cute,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.61,0:31:06.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或许我该拿你换一个年轻版的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe I'll trade you in for the younger model?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.14,0:31:10.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,局长  这不合理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just doesn't make any sense, Chief.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.96,0:31:15.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你...注意到他前几周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You, uh, notice anything...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.68,0:31:18.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么奇怪的地方了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}odd about him the last few weeks?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.15,0:31:21.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们打算下周日去埃托瓦钓鱼的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, we're fixin' to go fishing down the Etowah next Sunday.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.12,0:31:23.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他很期待  我知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, he was lookin' forward to it. I know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.79,0:31:25.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道他有什么仇家吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He got any enemies you might know about?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.75,0:31:27.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不想让他在这的人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, people who might not want him around?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.75,0:31:31.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,前女友们都不太喜欢他  那肯定的  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The exes didn't like him much. That's for sure, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.18,0:31:32.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}nah.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.47,0:31:35.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你最后一次看到他是什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When was the last time you saw him?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.14,0:31:37.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,昨天  跟往常一样午餐时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yesterday. Lunch, same as always.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.19,0:31:39.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就你和你的伙计们  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Just you and the boys? - Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.29,0:31:41.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和亨利还有...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me and Henry and...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.25,0:31:45.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个...小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, there was this, uh, this kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.03,0:31:48.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但这不是小孩干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No kid did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.87,0:31:49.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.46,0:31:52.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.61,0:31:57.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  午餐时有一个小男孩...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. At lunch, uh, there was this boy that, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.94,0:32:00.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想在本尼的厨房偷东西吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, he was trying to steal food out of Benny's kitchen.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.13,0:32:02.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能想象吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you imagine that?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.07,0:32:05.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This kid...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.77,0:32:08.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他长什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what'd he look like?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.93,0:32:13.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他大概这么高  瘦瘦小小\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, he was about yea high. You know, tiny like.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.68,0:32:14.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没仔细看他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't get a good look at him, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.82,0:32:16.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在厨房\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He was back in the kitchen.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.10,0:32:17.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他长这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He look like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.26,0:32:21.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  这是...这是朗尼失踪的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no, that's... That's Lonnie's missin' kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.14,0:32:22.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不是这个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. This was a different kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.43,0:32:24.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这孩子头发很短\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This one had really short hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.92,0:32:26.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是说几乎剃到头皮了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, it was buzzed nearly down to the scalp.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.09,0:32:30.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我们...我们不考虑发型这码事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, well, let's... You know, let's forget about the haircut.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.66,0:32:32.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是说  就算这个孩子是寸头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, if this kid had a buzz cut...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.84,0:32:34.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会是朗尼的孩子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}could it be Lonnie's kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.16,0:32:37.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我...我没仔细看他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I... I didn't get a good look at him.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.33,0:32:41.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过身高一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}About the right height, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.20,0:32:42.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是说  有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, could've been.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.05,0:32:45.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, that's...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.07,0:32:47.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Could've been.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.47,0:32:52.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我不想自己去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I don't want to go by myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.11,0:32:56.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比...芭比  这不难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb... Barb, it's not rocket science.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.56,0:32:57.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你只要告诉你爸妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You just tell your parents
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.41,0:32:59.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你之后会住在我家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you're gonna stay at my place afterwards.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.07,0:33:02.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  告诉他们我们要...学习\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, tell them we're... studying.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.93,0:33:04.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  吃晚饭了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy! Dinner!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.65,0:33:05.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Coming!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.37,0:33:08.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得挂了  一小时后见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I gotta go. I'll see you in an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.08,0:33:20.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,烘肉卷味道不好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something wrong with the meatloaf?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.20,0:33:24.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  只是我午餐吃了两个红肠三明治\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no, I had two bologna sandwiches for lunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.33,0:33:27.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也不知道为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know why.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.45,0:33:29.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.07,0:33:32.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这很美味  妈  -谢谢  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's delicious, Mommy. - Thank you, sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.33,0:33:34.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, there's this...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.90,0:33:37.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今晚在学校操场有个特别活动...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}special assembly thing tonight...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.80,0:33:40.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为威尔举办的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for Will at the school field.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.55,0:33:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比开车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb's driving.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.45,0:33:43.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么现在才给我说呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why am I just hearing about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.65,0:33:45.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还以为你知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you knew.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.91,0:33:47.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说过  找到威尔以前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you, I don't want you out after dark
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.29,0:33:48.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不许你们天黑出门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}until Will is found.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.55,0:33:51.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  但是我如果不去会很奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know, I know, but it'd be super weird if I'm not there.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.97,0:33:54.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为所有人都会参加\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, everyone's going.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.33,0:33:59.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那...十点前回到家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just... be back by 10:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.76,0:34:02.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如你把男孩们也带上吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't you take the boys, too?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.31,0:34:03.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不要  -不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No! - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.58,0:34:07.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们不觉得该参加吗  为了威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't you think you should be there? For Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.88,0:34:13.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  抽筋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry. Spasm.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.58,0:34:20.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的  霍莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay, Holly.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.34,0:34:22.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不过声音很响而已  -你可真行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's just a loud noise. - Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.08,0:34:26.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}本尼汉堡店
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.58,0:34:25.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.75,0:34:31.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最好快出来  伙计  威尔  你在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Better come out, buddy. Will, where are ya?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.29,0:34:44.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得厄尔真的看见威尔了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, you think Earl really saw Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.04,0:34:47.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那他的头发怎么剃光了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, what's he doin' with a shaved head?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.14,0:34:49.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还偷本尼的食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And stealing food from Benny?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.98,0:34:52.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样吧  等我们找到他  再问他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell you what, when we find him, we'll ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.67,0:34:54.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尸体不会回答问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can't ask a corpse questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.62,0:34:56.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,停一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold up!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.23,0:34:57.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找到什么了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got something?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.79,0:35:03.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你找到什么  -我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Hey, what do you got? - Not sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.46,0:35:04.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.11,0:35:07.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找到这个  在那里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I found this. In there.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.54,0:35:14.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小朋友才不可能爬进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No way a kid crawls through there.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.94,0:35:15.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很难说...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.56,0:35:18.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兔子怕了也能咬人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a scared enough one might.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.58,0:35:20.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他哥哥说他很会躲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His brother said he was good at hiding.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.72,0:35:57.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}El?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.51,0:36:06.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有大人  只有我们  跟烘肉卷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No adults. Just us and some meatloaf.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.73,0:36:12.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别担心  他们不会把你的事说出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't worry. They won't tell anyone about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.12,0:36:15.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们保证  懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They promise. Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.36,0:36:18.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要是早知道你有超能力  绝对不敢惹你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We never would've upset you if we knew you had superpowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.42,0:36:22.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,达斯汀的意思是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What Dustin is trying to say is
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.24,0:36:25.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们刚才...吓到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that they were just scared... earlier.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.87,0:36:26.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.51,0:36:28.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只不过想找到我们的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We just wanted to find our friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.07,0:36:29.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Friend"?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.07,0:36:32.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  朋友  威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, friend. Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.25,0:36:36.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"朋友"是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is "Friend"?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.45,0:36:38.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在开玩笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is she serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.60,0:36:43.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-朋友  -就是你会为他赴汤蹈火的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- A friend-- - Is someone that you'd do anything for.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.81,0:36:45.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会把好东西借给他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You lend them your cool stuff,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.09,0:36:46.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比如漫画书和集换卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like comic books and trading cards.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.96,0:36:48.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且永不违背承诺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And they never break a promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.19,0:36:50.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-尤其是吐过口水的  -吐口水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Especially when there's spit. - Spit?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.46,0:36:53.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,口水的承诺就是...你永不违背的承诺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A spit swear means... you never break your word.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.19,0:36:55.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是种契约\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a bond.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.78,0:36:58.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这点很重要  因为好朋友...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's super important, because friends...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.52,0:37:01.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无所不谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they tell each other things.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.65,0:37:03.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,父母不知道的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Things that parents don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.58,0:37:12.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-芭芭拉  靠边停车  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Barbara, pull over. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.42,0:37:13.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,靠边停车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pull over!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.21,0:37:18.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们停这儿干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are we doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.74,0:37:20.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他家离这儿还有三条街\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His house is three blocks away.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.23,0:37:21.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能停在他家车道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can't park in the driveway.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.70,0:37:22.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你认真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.84,0:37:24.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对啊  邻居会看到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, the neighbors might see.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.36,0:37:26.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这太蠢了  我送你去就算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is so stupid. I'm just gonna drop you off.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.52,0:37:28.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冷静点  芭比  拜托嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Calm down, Barb. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.69,0:37:31.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你答应要去的  你要一起去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You promised that you'd go. You're coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.35,0:37:32.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会玩得很开心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna have a great time.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.53,0:37:34.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不过想和你上床\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He just wants to get in your pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.39,0:37:35.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, he doesn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.99,0:37:38.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  说真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nance... seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.51,0:37:41.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他约你去他家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He invited you to his house.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.04,0:37:43.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,家里没大人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His parents aren't home.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.16,0:37:45.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,少来了  你没这么笨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, you are not this stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.78,0:37:47.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,汤米·H和卡洛都会在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tommy H. and Carol are gonna be there.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.99,0:37:51.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,汤米和卡洛大概七年级就开始胡搞了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tommy and Carol have been having sex since, like, seventh grade.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.11,0:37:54.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到时候大概就像个淫乱派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It'll probably just be, like, a big orgy.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.16,0:37:56.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-恶心  -我是说真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Gross. - I'm serious!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.20,0:37:58.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  那...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, well...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.52,0:38:02.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以当我的监护人  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can be, like, my guardian. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.90,0:38:05.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确保我不会喝醉然后做傻事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Make sure I don't get drunk and do anything stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.65,0:38:11.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是新内衣吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that a new bra?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.66,0:38:13.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.93,0:38:28.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比  放轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb, chill.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.01,0:38:29.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很放松啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm chill.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.53,0:38:36.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们好  女士们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello, ladies.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.52,0:39:10.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.49,0:39:12.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冷死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's freezing.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.94,0:39:20.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有没有过被诅咒的感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You ever feel cursed?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.81,0:39:26.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上一次这里有人失踪是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, the last person to go missing here was in, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.50,0:39:30.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,1923年的夏天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the summer of '23.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.70,0:39:33.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上一次有人自杀是1961年秋天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The last suicide was the fall of '61.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.28,0:39:41.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那上一次有人冻死是什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When'd the last person freeze to death?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.20,0:39:47.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,进来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, come back inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.71,0:39:49.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我取暖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Warm me up. Just...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.10,0:39:53.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我在这儿待一会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just give me a minute out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.74,0:40:22.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这怪人在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's the weirdo doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.55,0:40:29.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}El?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.06,0:40:43.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.69,0:40:46.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,超能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Superpowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.81,0:40:55.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在幽暗密林见到过他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you see him? On Mirkwood?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.21,0:40:58.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道他在哪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know where he is?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.40,0:41:15.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.04,0:41:18.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,躲起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hiding.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.76,0:41:19.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔躲起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will is hiding?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.72,0:41:26.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,躲开坏人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}From the bad men?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.27,0:41:30.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是躲开谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then from who?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.62,0:42:35.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在哪呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.06,0:43:06.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一  二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One! Two!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.62,0:43:10.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-三  -住手  汤米  不要啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Three! - Stop it, Tommy, no! Don't!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.13,0:43:12.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真是个混蛋  汤米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're such an asshole, Tommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:27.89,0:43:29.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你那是想打动我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that supposed to impress me?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.60,0:43:33.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没成功吗  -你知道那很老套吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You're not? - You are a cliché, you do realize that?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:33.72,0:43:34.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你才老套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are a cliché.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.87,0:43:37.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用功读书  玩玩乐团\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What with your... your grades and your band practice.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:37.25,0:43:38.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我才不玩乐团呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm so not in band.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:38.71,0:43:40.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行吧  交际花  那不如你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, party girl. Why don't you just,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:40.61,0:43:42.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,向我们展示下喝一罐吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}show us how it's done, then?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.30,0:43:42.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.97,0:43:52.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你得在那扎个小洞  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You gotta make a little hole right in the bott-- - I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.16,0:43:54.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她可聪明呢  你个白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, she's smart, you douche!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:59.25,0:44:01.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,干  干  干\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Chug. Chug. Chug.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:01.72,0:44:04.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,干  干  干\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Chug. Chug. Chug.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.06,0:44:16.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比  想试试吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb, you wanna try?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.98,0:44:18.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? No.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.76,0:44:19.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不想  谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I don't want to. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:19.89,0:44:20.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.93,0:44:22.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-来呀  -南茜  我不想试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Come on. Yeah. - Nance, I don't want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.83,0:44:24.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-很好玩的  试试嘛  -南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's fun! Just give it a-- - Nance...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:25.09,0:44:26.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凡事都要试一试嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just... just give it a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:28.55,0:44:29.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.77,0:44:36.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以是要...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So you just...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:41.14,0:44:42.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-精彩  -你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Gnarly. - Are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:42.77,0:44:44.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没事  -芭比  你出血了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. - Barb, you're bleeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:44.21,0:44:46.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没事  洗手间在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm fine. Where's your bathroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:46.69,0:44:49.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在...一楼穿过厨房  左手边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, it's... It's, uh, down past the kitchen, to the left.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.97,0:44:51.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:04.30,0:45:07.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  你在搞什么  汤米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my, God! What the hell, Tommy?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:52.34,0:45:53.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:55.46,0:45:56.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:58.03,0:45:58.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.32,0:46:05.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:06.82,0:46:09.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:09.52,0:46:10.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我说说话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:11.39,0:46:12.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:12.30,0:46:15.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我你在哪  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just tell me where you are, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:15.01,0:46:17.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听着呢  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can hear you. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:17.70,0:46:18.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.81,0:46:20.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:46:21.18,0:46:23.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, it's me. It's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:24.77,0:46:27.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在哪  你在哪  回答我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are you? Where are you? Just talk to me--
Dialogue: 0,0:46:29.37,0:46:30.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:46:30.98,0:46:31.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:46:32.07,0:46:32.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.35,0:46:35.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no! No...
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.00,0:46:37.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.20,0:46:40.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.34,0:46:48.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:46:51.83,0:46:54.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:47:04.90,0:47:06.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔纳森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jonathan?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:12.86,0:47:14.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What...
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.91,0:47:25.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will...
Dialogue: 0,0:47:54.91,0:47:55.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will...
Dialogue: 0,0:47:57.58,0:47:59.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔  是你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will, is that you?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:22.46,0:48:23.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:27.06,0:48:27.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God...
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.38,0:48:32.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God...
Dialogue: 0,0:48:41.58,0:48:42.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will...
Dialogue: 0,0:49:18.42,0:49:19.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冷死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm freezing.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:20.37,0:49:24.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听说他妈房间有壁炉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I hear his mom's room has a fireplace.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.05,0:49:25.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是说真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you kidding?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:25.03,0:49:27.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,床单就交给你洗了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, well, you know, you are cleaning the sheets.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:27.48,0:49:28.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You all right? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:28.84,0:49:30.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来  我给你找几件干衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah? Come on, let's get you some dry clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:36.81,0:49:37.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nance!
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.00,0:49:39.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:40.94,0:49:42.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:42.90,0:49:43.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nowhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:43.70,0:49:45.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就...上楼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just... upstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:45.67,0:49:46.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,换身衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To change.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:47.45,0:49:49.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我掉进泳池了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I... fell in the pool.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:52.84,0:49:54.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要不你先自己回家吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't you go ahead and go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:54.77,0:49:57.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我...到时候搭车回去就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll just... I'll get a ride or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:57.64,0:49:58.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nance...
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.33,0:50:00.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb...
Dialogue: 0,0:50:01.23,0:50:02.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:03.42,0:50:04.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This isn't you.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:06.33,0:50:07.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:08.16,0:50:11.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你...先自己回家吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just... go ahead and go home, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:31.62,0:50:32.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.33,0:50:41.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给点隐私吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some privacy, maybe?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.70,0:50:44.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, right. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.15,0:50:50.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史蒂夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Steve?
Dialogue: 0,0:51:04.14,0:51:05.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,妈呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Damn.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:07.58,0:51:08.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shut up.
Dialogue: 1,0:05:07.15,0:05:19.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fad(0,1000)\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,200)}{\alpha&FF\t(5825,5825,\alpha&00)}怪{\alpha&00}奇物{\alpha&FF\t(7535,7535,\alpha&00)}语
Dialogue: 1,0:05:07.15,0:05:19.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,243,3406,5908)}{\t(5908,5908,\alpha&FF)}怪{\alpha&FF}奇物语
Dialogue: 1,0:05:07.15,0:05:19.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,231,4031,7535)}{\alpha&FF}怪奇物{\alpha&00\t(7535,7535,\alpha&FF)}语
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.02,0:05:27.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(650,0)\bord0\fs25\t(700,3000,\fs30)\fsp\b1\fn方正粗倩_GBK\c&H00017A&\move(193,214,193,225,700,3000)\u1}第二章\N{\u0}枫树街的怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.03,0:05:31.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,1000)\bord0\fs30\t(,,\fs55)\fsp\b1\fn方正粗倩_GBK\c&H00017A&\move(193,225,193,300)\u1}第二章\N{\u0}枫树街的怪人
Dialogue: 3,0:05:36.44,0:05:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,0)\bord0\shad0\fscx15\fscy20\p1\c&HFFEBD1&\t(4800,5000,\fscx0\fscy0)\pos(79.5,206.307)}m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 {\p0}
Dialogue: 2,0:05:36.44,0:05:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,0)\bord0\shad0\fscx10\fscy14\p1\c&HECB000&\t(4800,5000,\fscx0\fscy0)\pos(92.9,220.68)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 4,0:05:36.44,0:05:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,0)\bord0\shad0\fscx19\fscy20\p1\1a&H3D&\c&HFFFFFF&\blur10\t(4800,5000,\fscx0\fscy0)\pos(78.5,212.307)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:05:36.44,0:05:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\b1\fscx121\fscy104\bord0\shad0\blur20\c&HECB000&\t(0,1000,1,\blur0)\pos(130.3,223.307)}字幕组\N{\fs15\fscx}ZiMuZu.tv
Dialogue: 1,0:05:37.44,0:05:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\b1\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\c&HECB000&\clip(50,204,52,273)\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,204,335,275))\pos(116.7,239.107)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.44,0:05:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\clip(50,204,52,273)\fad(500,500)\3c&HFFFFFF&\fscx600\fs86\alpha&H9F&\c&H000000&\bord1\shad0\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,154,335,275))\pos(193.2,256.8)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.44,0:05:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs16\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\clip(50,154,52,273)\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,154,335,275))\pos(231.9,238.657)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为\N最新最快海外影视字幕下载\N{\fs18}请登陆{\fn方正综艺简体\c&H26F4FF&}www.ZiMuZu.tv
Dialogue: 3,0:05:41.45,0:06:06.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,500,\fscx15\fscy20\t(4750,5250,\fry720\t(9750,10250,\fry0\t(14750,15250,\fry720\t(19750,20250,\fry0\t(24500,25000,\fscx0\fscy0))))))\p1\c&HFFEBD1&\pos(48.8,154.6)\org(51,158)}m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 {\p0}
Dialogue: 2,0:05:41.45,0:06:06.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,500,\fscx10\fscy14\t(4750,5250,\fry720\t(9750,10250,\fry0\t(14750,15250,\fry720\t(19750,20250,\fry0\t(24500,25000,\fscx0\fscy0))))))\p1\c&HECB000&\t(24500,25000,\fry810)\pos(50.8,200.173)\org(51,158)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 5,0:05:41.45,0:06:06.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx18\fscy20\p1\1a&H3D&\c&HFFFFFF&\blur10\pos(39.4,190.973)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.45,0:06:06.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord1\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\alpha&B0\c&H000000&\t(0,200,\fscx2100\fscy600\t(200,400,\fscx2400\fscy300\t(24800,25200,\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\alpha&AA\fscy400\fscx400)))\move(163,211.2,36.5,211.2,24800,25200)\3c&HFFFFFF&}■
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.44,0:05:46.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,290,227))\fs15\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}翻译：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17}星星与野狗 胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.44,0:05:51.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,290,227))\fs15\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}翻译：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17}TheWalkingNerd 小肚腩 小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.44,0:05:56.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fn方正黑体_GBK\bord0\shad0\frx-630\t(0,500,\frx0\t(4500,5000,\clip(40,213,40,248)))\pos(57.12,210.56)\fs15\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}校对：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17}酸奶{\c&H63B8FF&}怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.44,0:06:01.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,0)\bord0\shad0\move(57.12,210.56,400,210.56,4500,5000)\clip(54,195,281,227)\fs15\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}时间轴：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17}西查
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.44,0:06:06.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(300,300)\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\fs15\3c&HEDB425&\4c&H9EF6FF&\shad0\bord0\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\pos(57.12,210.56)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\clip(49,191,295,232)\b1}后期：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))}吉吉  {\fs15\c&HECB000&\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))}总监：{\fs17\c&HFFFFFF&\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))}酸奶{\c&H63B8FF&}怪
