[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.31,0:00:23.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.60,0:00:28.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.46,0:00:32.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.42,0:00:35.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.40,0:00:57.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.43,0:01:02.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, what's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.95,0:01:04.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.49,0:01:35.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're so beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.99,0:01:39.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.95,0:01:45.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.43,0:03:26.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史蒂夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Steve?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.79,0:03:30.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史蒂夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Steve.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.27,0:03:35.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.96,0:03:38.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明天见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}see you tomorrow, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.38,0:04:17.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  你吓死我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus, you scared me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.91,0:04:19.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我吓到你了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I scared you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.26,0:04:20.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  我该打个电话的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know, I should have called.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.38,0:04:21.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你去哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where have you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.11,0:04:23.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们说好10点的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We agreed on 10:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.24,0:04:26.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,集会结束后  有几个人想去吃点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After the assembly, some people wanted to get something to eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.71,0:04:27.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没觉得有什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't think it'd be a big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.98,0:04:30.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就不觉得该打电话跟我说一下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You didn't think to call and let me know?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.06,0:04:31.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在出了那么多事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With everything that's been going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.70,0:04:34.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没意识到已经那么晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't realize how late it was, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.63,0:04:36.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起  妈妈  你还要我怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, Mom. What more do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.26,0:04:37.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, wait...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.96,0:04:39.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这运动衫是谁的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whose sweatshirt is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.77,0:04:41.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史蒂夫的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Steve's.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.15,0:04:43.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史蒂夫的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Steve's.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.73,0:04:46.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史蒂夫是你的男朋友了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So is Steve your boyfriend now?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.28,0:04:47.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.51,0:04:48.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.45,0:04:51.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是太冷了  我管他借来穿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was just cold, so I borrowed his sweatshirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.48,0:04:52.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not a big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.05,0:04:54.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.87,0:04:56.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.14,0:04:59.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以跟我说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.17,0:05:03.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以告诉我的  不管发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can talk to me. Whatever happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.64,0:05:06.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没发生什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.44,0:05:09.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.84,0:05:14.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没发生什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.82,0:05:17.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能走了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can I please go?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.47,0:05:44.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔  威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will? Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.55,0:05:47.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  你听得到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sweetheart, can you hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.94,0:05:48.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.57,0:05:50.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.66,0:05:51.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.45,0:05:55.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}不得擅闯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.48,0:05:55.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.95,0:05:58.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我  跟我说话  跟我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's me. Just talk to me. Talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.97,0:05:59.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just say...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.82,0:06:03.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-妈妈  -乔纳森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mom? - Jonathan!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.27,0:06:05.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-过来  过来  -妈妈  这是干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Come here. Come here. - Mom, what is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.64,0:06:08.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过来  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here. Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.80,0:06:11.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么回事  -是威尔  他...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What's going on? - It's Will. It's Will, he's...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.74,0:06:13.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想跟我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he's trying to talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.85,0:06:18.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他想跟你说话  -对  用灯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He's trying to talk to you? - Yes, through... through the lights.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.22,0:06:19.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-妈妈  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mom... - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.45,0:06:20.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.90,0:06:22.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just... just watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.48,0:06:26.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔  你哥哥来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will... your brother's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.20,0:06:30.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能向他展示你展示给我看的吗  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you show him what you showed me, baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.03,0:06:34.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你  你看到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please... Did you see that?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.74,0:06:36.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是电  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the electricity, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.66,0:06:37.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就是出故障了  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's acting up. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.78,0:06:39.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟电话被烧是一个原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the same thing that fried the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.44,0:06:42.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不是电  乔纳森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! It is not the electricity, Jonathan.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.20,0:06:44.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里有情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something is going on here!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.61,0:06:47.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-昨天  墙...  -怎么  墙怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yesterday, the wall... - What? What about the wall?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.17,0:06:48.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我不知道  -妈妈  先是灯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I don't know. I don't know. - Mom, first the lights,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.64,0:06:49.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在又是墙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then the wall?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.26,0:06:52.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道威尔就在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just know that Will is here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.39,0:06:53.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.25,0:06:56.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-如果我再找些灯来  -不行  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Maybe if I get more lamps... - No, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.34,0:07:00.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不需要灯了  你需要停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't need more lamps. You need to stop this, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.93,0:07:03.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就是迷路了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He is just lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.26,0:07:07.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家都在找他  他们会找到他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People are looking for him, and they're going to find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.11,0:07:08.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.08,0:07:11.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这样没用的  -好吧  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- This isn't helping. - Okay, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.33,0:07:13.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  对不起  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.27,0:07:15.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能帮我个忙吗  妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you do me a favor, Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.82,0:07:18.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能不能尽量睡会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you just try and get some sleep?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.56,0:07:20.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-嗯  -可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. - Huh? Can you do that for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.53,0:07:22.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我保证  我会的  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I promise. I will. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.15,0:07:24.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-嗯  -让我先在这儿坐会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. - I just need to sit here for a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.98,0:07:26.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我去做早餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, I'll go make breakfast.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.77,0:07:28.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.77,0:07:45.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只要告诉爸妈放学后有视听俱乐部活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We just tell our parents we have AV Club after school.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.94,0:07:48.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样我们有几小时时间实施幽暗密林行动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That'll give us at least a few hours for Operation Mirkwood.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.79,0:07:52.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真觉得怪胎知道威尔在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You seriously think that the weirdo knows where Will is?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.13,0:07:54.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-相信我  好吗  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Just trust me on this, okay? - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.15,0:07:55.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你带装备了吗  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Did you get the supplies? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.13,0:07:58.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,望远镜  越南的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Binoculars... from 'Nam.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.91,0:08:00.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,军刀  也是越南的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Army knife... also from 'Nam.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.84,0:08:03.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,锤子  迷彩手帕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hammer, camouflage bandana...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.50,0:08:05.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有手腕火箭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the wrist rocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.31,0:08:07.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要拿弹弓对付魔王吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna take out the Demogorgon with a slingshot?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.65,0:08:10.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首先  这叫手腕火箭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}First of all, it's a wrist rocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.01,0:08:12.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其次  魔王不是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And second of all, the Demogorgon's not real.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.76,0:08:13.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是编的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's made up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.67,0:08:15.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果真有什么怪物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if there is something out there,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.59,0:08:17.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要射中他的眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna shoot it in the eye...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.98,0:08:20.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-射瞎他  -达斯汀  你拿了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- and blind it. - Dustin, what did you get?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.76,0:08:25.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, alrighty.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.29,0:08:27.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, we've got...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.46,0:08:30.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威化饼  糖果  聪明豆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nutty Bars, Bazooka, Pez, Smarties,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.71,0:08:33.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,品客  饼干  苹果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pringles, Nilla Wafers, apple,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.03,0:08:35.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-香蕉  还有什锦果仁  -不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- banana, and trail mix. - Seriously?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.23,0:08:38.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要能量好在旅途中维持精力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need energy for our travels. For stamina.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.06,0:08:40.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再说  我们还需要什么武器啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And besides, why do we even need weapons anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.32,0:08:42.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们有她  -她就是关上了扇门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We have her. - She shut one door!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.96,0:08:44.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用意念啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With her mind!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.44,0:08:46.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开玩笑吗  这多疯狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you kidding me? That's insane!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.09,0:08:49.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想象下她还能做什么其他的酷炫事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Imagine all the other cool stuff she could do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.05,0:08:50.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比如\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.05,0:08:56.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她肯定能让这个飞起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I bet... that she could make this fly!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.77,0:09:01.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,集中注意  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, concentrate. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.46,0:09:04.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  再来一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, one more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.67,0:09:06.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.87,0:09:09.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用你的超能力  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Use your powers, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.39,0:09:12.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.72,0:09:14.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她不是狗  -孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- She's not a dog! - Boys!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.38,0:09:15.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上学了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Time for school!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.45,0:09:19.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,待在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just stay down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.49,0:09:21.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别出声  别走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't make any noise, and don't leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.85,0:09:24.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你饿了  就吃达斯汀的零食  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you get hungry, eat Dustin's snacks, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.49,0:09:26.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-迈克尔  -来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Michael! - Coming!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.69,0:09:28.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道电力线吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know those power lines?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.07,0:09:29.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-电力线  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Power lines? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.71,0:09:31.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是我家后面的那种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The ones behind my house?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.41,0:09:32.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.15,0:09:34.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放学后在那里跟我们碰面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Meet us there, after school.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.44,0:09:35.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放学后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After school?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.43,0:09:36.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  3点15分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, 3:15.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.06,0:09:48.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等数字变成315  就来找我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When the numbers read three- one- five, meet us there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.98,0:09:51.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,315\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Three-one-five."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.03,0:09:52.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,315\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Three-one-five.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.66,0:10:24.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-一切都好吧  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Is everything okay? - Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.52,0:10:25.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好得很\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, totally.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.77,0:10:27.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.66,0:10:32.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,觉得好像大家都在盯着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I feel like everyone's... staring at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.51,0:10:34.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没告诉任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I didn't... I didn't tell anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.10,0:10:35.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.30,0:10:37.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know. Of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.52,0:10:40.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那汤米和卡洛呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But what about, like, Tommy, and Carol and them?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.77,0:10:42.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这是疑神疑鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're being paranoid.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.95,0:10:45.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-对不起  -不  很可爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm sorry. - No. No, it's cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.32,0:10:50.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很开心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had a good time.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.45,0:10:53.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.63,0:10:55.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. Me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.89,0:11:28.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾莉  芭比呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Ally. Where's Barb?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.88,0:11:30.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不该问你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, shouldn't you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.81,0:11:33.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你完全没见着她吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You haven't seen her anywhere... at all?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.82,0:11:41.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到了  翡翠城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There she is. Emerald City.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.31,0:11:43.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听说他们在里面造太空武器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I heard they make space weapons in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.43,0:11:44.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太空武器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Space weapons?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.56,0:11:46.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  里根的星战嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. You know, like, Reagan's Star Wars.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.90,0:11:49.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们大概是要把苏联人炸成渣渣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess we're gonna blow the Ruskies to smithereens.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.00,0:11:52.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, can I help you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.73,0:11:54.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯  我们要进去看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, yeah. We're here for a tour.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.95,0:11:56.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们这儿不能随便看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, we don't give tours.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.77,0:11:59.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  就进去看一圈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay... A quick look around.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.08,0:12:01.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要权限的  你可以联络\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have to get clearance for that. You can contact, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.94,0:12:03.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能源部的里克·谢弗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick Schaeffer at the Department of Energy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.27,0:12:05.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可能看到电视播了  有个本地的孩子失踪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you seen it on TV. We got a local kid that's missing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.69,0:12:07.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有原因认为他可能是溜进去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have reason to believe he might have snuck in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.36,0:12:10.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说了  你得去找谢弗先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like I said, you have to speak to Mr. Schaeffer.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.26,0:12:14.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你叫什么  -帕特里克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What's your name? - Patrick.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.21,0:12:15.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕特里克  我们镇长惊慌不已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Patrick, I got a panicked mayor,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.75,0:12:17.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记者对我步步紧逼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I got reporters breathing down my neck
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.63,0:12:19.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他妈妈简直要崩溃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I got a very upset mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.90,0:12:22.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道孩子不在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I know the kid's not in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.52,0:12:25.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我总得查一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I gotta check off this box.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.75,0:12:28.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕特里克  能帮个忙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Patrick, would you do me a favor?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.59,0:12:33.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去找你老板  看看能不能给我们安排一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Would you speak to your boss and see what you can swing for us?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.26,0:12:35.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会非常感激的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'd really appreciate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.53,0:12:38.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最多就10分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm talking ten minutes, tops.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.95,0:13:51.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,...占据了黎巴嫩的一大部分地区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...was occupying a large part of Lebanon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.76,0:13:54.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天  叙利亚成了...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Today, Syria has become a home for...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.64,0:13:59.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have the power!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.04,0:14:01.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,...一件恒久的礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...gift that will last forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.13,0:14:03.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来自和谐珍宝收藏...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}From the Harmony Treasures' collection...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.41,0:14:11.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}可口可乐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.31,0:15:18.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}就要可乐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.43,0:15:29.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}圣诞节
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.79,0:16:38.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-乔伊  -给我记上  唐纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Joyce... - Just ring me up, Donald.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.04,0:16:42.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得这个失踪的孩子从这里爬了进来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you think this missing boy may have crawled through there?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.11,0:16:44.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这么想的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, that was the idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.21,0:16:46.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得这不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I just don't see how that'd be possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.80,0:16:48.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有一百多个摄像头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've got over 100 cameras.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.67,0:16:51.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每一寸土地都能拍到  再加上我的人手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Every square inch covered, plus all my guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.22,0:16:53.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没人能闯进来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No one breaks in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.88,0:16:55.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,孩子更不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Certainly not some kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.44,0:16:57.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些摄像头的录像都保存着吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Those cameras, you keep the tapes?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.65,0:17:05.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果不介意我问  你们这里干什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you don't mind me asking, what do you guys do in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.77,0:17:07.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你问错人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're asking the wrong guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.66,0:17:09.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想赶超苏联人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Staying one step ahead of the Russians?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.26,0:17:11.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,差不多吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I expect. Something like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.84,0:17:14.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这里谁管事  -布伦纳博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Who's in charge here? - That'd be Dr. Brenner.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.28,0:17:16.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他建太空激光枪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And he builds the space lasers?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.16,0:17:18.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-太空激光枪  -别理他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Space lasers? - Ignore him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.02,0:17:23.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是6日和7日的晚上吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the night of the 6th and 7th we're seeing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.08,0:17:24.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's correct.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.46,0:17:37.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就这些吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.71,0:17:40.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说了  如果有我们会看到他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like I said, we would have seen him.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.90,0:17:46.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,7日晚上  我们组织了搜索队找威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The night of the 7th, we had a search party out for Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.13,0:17:47.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记得那晚是怎么样的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You remember anything about that night?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.95,0:17:50.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也没发生什么  我们最后取消了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mmm, not much to remember. Called it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.35,0:17:52.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-因为暴雨  -对啊  那晚下得很大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- 'Cause of the storm. - Yeah, a lot of rain that night.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.04,0:17:54.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,录像看起来像下着雨吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see any rain on that tape?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.38,0:17:57.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么想的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.56,0:17:59.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.11,0:18:03.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他们在撒谎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But they're lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.16,0:18:05.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}霍金斯警察局
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.09,0:20:47.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以说我觉得科学就是扯淡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's why science doesn't make any damn sense to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.42,0:20:50.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我发誓  看啊  绝对是冻伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I swear. Look at this. It's totally frostbite.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.39,0:20:53.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢了  伙计  泳池都加热了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, thanks, man. It's a heated pool.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.98,0:20:55.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果不是冻伤  那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, if it's not frostbite, then what is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.55,0:20:57.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我才不管是什么呢  真恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ugh, I don't care what it is, it's disgusting!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.39,0:20:59.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把脚拿下桌子  我们吃饭呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get it off the table. We're eating here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.41,0:21:02.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,汤米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Tommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.27,0:21:05.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你走时  看到芭比了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When you left, did you see Barb?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.59,0:21:07.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -芭芭拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What? - Barbara.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.72,0:21:09.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她今天没来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's not here today.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.56,0:21:12.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我真的不知道你说的是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I seriously have no idea who you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.86,0:21:14.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得了  别犯浑  你...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, don't be an ass, man. Did you...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.81,0:21:16.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你昨晚看没看到她离开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you see her leave last night or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.50,0:21:20.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我们走时她已经不在了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, she was gone when we left.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.55,0:21:23.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或许是受不了听人叫唤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Probably couldn't stand listening to all that moaning.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.22,0:21:26.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史蒂夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, Steve!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.87,0:21:30.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-史蒂夫  史蒂夫  -史蒂夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, Steve! Oh, Steve! - Oh, Steve...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.38,0:21:34.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-史蒂夫  -行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, Steve! - Okay, chill.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.35,0:21:37.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  她肯定没事的  她大概就是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen... I'm sure she's fine. She's probably just...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.28,0:21:40.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她大概就是翘课了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she's probably just, like, skipping or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.75,0:21:41.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.37,0:21:43.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, probably.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.18,0:22:04.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这个呢  -太大了  弹弓装不下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- How about this one? - Too big for the sling.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.64,0:22:08.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得十一的超能力是像X战警那样是天生的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, do you think Eleven was born with her powers, like the X- Men,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.55,0:22:12.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是后天获得的  像绿灯侠那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or do you think she acquired them, like... like Green Lantern?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.27,0:22:15.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不是超级英雄  她就是个怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's not a superhero. She's a weirdo.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.26,0:22:17.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那又如何  X战警也是怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why does that matter? The X- Men are weirdos.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.67,0:22:20.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你那么爱她  干吗不娶她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you love her so much, why don't you marry her?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.25,0:22:21.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.55,0:22:23.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-迈克  不是吧  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mike, seriously? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.27,0:22:24.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看她那眼神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You look at her all, like...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.41,0:22:27.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"一一  一一  一一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Hi, El! El! El! El!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.98,0:22:29.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我好爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I love you so much!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.63,0:22:31.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你能嫁给我吗"  -闭嘴啦  卢卡斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Would you marry me?" - Shut up, Lucas.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.27,0:22:33.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  闭嘴  卢卡斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, shut up, Lucas.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.56,0:22:35.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们这群废物在这儿干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you losers doing back here?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.55,0:22:37.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概是找他们失踪的朋友吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Probably looking for their missing friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.14,0:22:40.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不好笑  这事很严肃的  他有危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's not funny. It's serious. He's in danger.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.46,0:22:43.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真不想戳破  没牙仔  他没危险了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hate to break it to you, Toothless, but he's not in danger.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.75,0:22:46.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他已经死了  我爸就这么说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's dead. That's what my dad says.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.33,0:22:49.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说他大概是被其他基佬杀了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He said he was probably killed by some other queer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.80,0:22:51.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走吧  别理他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Just ignore them.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.05,0:22:58.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看着路  青蛙脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Watch where you're going, Frogface.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.17,0:23:01.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没事吧  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You all right? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.24,0:23:10.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about this one?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.08,0:23:14.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-嗯  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.32,0:23:15.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就它了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, this is it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.17,0:23:17.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.94,0:23:20.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这块能杀怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, this is the monster killer!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.84,0:24:34.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯伦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Karen.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.08,0:24:39.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我给你带了砂锅菜来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I brought you a casserole.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.89,0:24:42.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.42,0:24:46.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要进来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, you wanna... come in?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.33,0:25:05.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽莎  你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Marissa. How you doin'?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.77,0:25:08.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还敢来这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have a lot of nerve showing up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.37,0:25:10.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.39,0:25:12.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你至少可以打个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You could have at least called, said,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.12,0:25:14.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"玛丽莎  我们没戏的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Marissa! Hey, it's not gonna work out.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.43,0:25:17.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉浪费了你的时间  我是个混蛋"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry I wasted your time. I'm a dick."
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.20,0:25:18.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.42,0:25:24.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.65,0:25:26.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或许我们下周可以再出去一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe we could go out again next week?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.19,0:25:34.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,报纸  你们这儿有报纸吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Newspapers? You guys got newspapers around here?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.32,0:25:38.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有《纽约时报》《邮报》  所有大报纸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have the New York Times, the Post, all the big ones.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.17,0:25:39.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,按年份和话题整理的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Organized by year and topic.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.90,0:25:42.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阅读室里有对应的微缩平片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can find the corresponding microfiche in the reading room.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.73,0:25:43.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  我们想找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, we're looking for
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.47,0:25:45.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍金斯国家实验室的全部报道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}anything on the Hawkins National Laboratory.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.45,0:25:47.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是该去找那个失踪的孩子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, shouldn't you be looking for that missing kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.42,0:25:49.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就是在找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. We are.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.77,0:25:52.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你先翻《时报》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, so, why don't you start with the Times,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.59,0:25:54.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们找《邮报》吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and we'll check out the Post.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.10,0:26:04.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,图书管理员也不放过啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The librarian?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.20,0:26:19.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}霍金斯实验室阻止调查
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.59,0:26:25.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}据传有实验虐待事件
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.06,0:26:33.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}精神控制实验被曝光
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.80,0:26:39.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}马丁·布伦纳博士被告上法庭
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.55,0:26:42.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}泰芮·艾芙斯提出指控  "他们抢走了我女儿"
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.56,0:26:52.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔一向喜欢圣诞节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will always loved Christmas, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.22,0:26:54.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就想  如果我把灯都挂上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So I thought if I... I put the lights up...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.25,0:26:56.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  他...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know, he...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.33,0:26:59.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样我会觉得他还在家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'd feel like he was home somehow.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.05,0:27:00.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这很傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's silly, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.57,0:27:03.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不不  这不傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. No, it's not silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.87,0:27:06.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔纳森还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How is Jonathan holding up?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.82,0:27:08.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他很擅长照顾自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, he's good at taking care of himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.69,0:27:10.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他一向如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He always has been, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.77,0:27:11.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.87,0:27:15.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他觉得我是要疯了  但...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, he thinks I'm losing my mind, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.85,0:27:19.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出什么事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is something the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.31,0:27:21.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, no. No, I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.84,0:27:24.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有点电力故障\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're having electrical problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.35,0:27:25.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔伊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Joyce.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.92,0:27:27.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want you to know something.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.49,0:27:30.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你需要什么  任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you need anything, anything at all...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.92,0:27:32.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和泰德都会帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ted and I are here for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.80,0:27:35.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.14,0:27:35.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.19,0:27:39.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How... how's Mike dealing with this?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.16,0:27:40.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is he, uh, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.82,0:27:43.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克  我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike? Uh... I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.13,0:27:45.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他昨天没去上学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He skipped school yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.35,0:27:48.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他以前从没这样过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's never done anything like that before.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.58,0:28:30.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把砂锅菜给你腾出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me throw in that casserole, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.86,0:28:34.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍莉哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, where's Holly?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.21,0:28:50.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不该进来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She shouldn't be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.65,0:28:53.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  她现在特喜欢到处探索\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I'm sorry. She's quite the explorer these days.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.90,0:28:57.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-等等  你看到什么了吗  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Wait, did you see something? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.24,0:28:58.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看到什么了  告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What did... what did you see? Tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.93,0:29:01.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你看到什么了  -乔伊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What did you see? What... - Joyce... Joyce!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.03,0:29:04.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  凯伦  多谢你的砂锅菜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen... Karen, thank you for the casserole,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.87,0:29:06.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我需要你离开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I need you to leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.99,0:29:07.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.76,0:29:11.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接啊  接啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, come on, come on...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.45,0:29:14.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.72,0:29:17.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍兰德太太  我是南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hi, uh, Ms. Holland, it's Nancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.78,0:29:19.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, Nancy, how are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.11,0:29:20.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  我很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good. I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.38,0:29:23.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想问下  芭比在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, I was just wondering, uh, is Barb there?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.06,0:29:25.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不在  她还没回来呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, she hasn't come home yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.71,0:29:29.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但她昨晚守夜之后回过家吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But she did come home, right? After the vigil?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.64,0:29:32.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  她说昨晚要住你家的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, she said she was staying with you last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.21,0:29:36.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  没错  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right, yes. She did, sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.29,0:29:39.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是问  她今早回家了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I meant, did she come home this morning?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.73,0:29:40.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她好像落下了几本教材\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think she left some textbooks
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.80,0:29:42.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她说要回去取的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and she was gonna go pick them up.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.19,0:29:45.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我没见过她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, um, no, I haven't seen her.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.13,0:29:49.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个  我想起来了  她在图书馆呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do... Do you know what? I just remembered... she's at the library.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.70,0:29:53.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  你找到她后叫她马上打给我好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy, will you please have her call me as soon as you find her?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.91,0:29:56.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯  当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. Yeah, I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.01,0:29:58.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉打扰了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry to bother you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.40,0:30:04.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}霍金斯高中
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.81,0:30:12.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.58,0:30:14.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.70,0:30:16.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,妮可跟我们讲了你的作品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nicole here was, uh, telling us about your work.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.61,0:30:18.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-听说很不错  -是啊  好酷啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We've heard great things. - Yeah, sounds cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.60,0:30:19.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们想看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we'd just love to take a look.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.93,0:30:23.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,作为艺术鉴赏家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, as... connoisseurs of art.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.66,0:30:24.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道你们在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know what you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.58,0:30:25.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.33,0:30:28.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把我的包还给我  别...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, give me my bag. No, just...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.47,0:30:29.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他都发抖了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Man, he is totally trembling.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.97,0:30:31.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定有什么想隐瞒的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He must really have something to hide.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.11,0:30:32.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.41,0:30:35.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.65,0:30:38.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-天呐  -我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, man. - Let me see.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.14,0:30:40.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.03,0:30:43.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一点都不让人感到发毛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, this isn't creepy at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.90,0:30:45.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是在找我弟弟  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I was looking for my brother. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.67,0:30:47.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  这叫跟踪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, this is called stalking.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.02,0:30:51.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -女主角来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What's going on? - Here's the starring lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.00,0:30:52.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.54,0:30:54.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这变态昨晚偷看我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This creep was spying on us last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.01,0:30:58.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这张大概是打算回头慢慢品味的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He was probably gonna save this one for later.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.17,0:31:06.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,瞧  可以看出来  他知道这么做不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, you can tell that he knows it was wrong, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.35,0:31:09.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但变态就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Man, that's the thing about perverts...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.10,0:31:11.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们天生是如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's hardwired into 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.04,0:31:14.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们控制不了自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, they just can't help themselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.27,0:31:18.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.45,0:31:20.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只能拿走他的玩具了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we'll just have to take away his toy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.46,0:31:22.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-史蒂夫  -不  别  别拿我照相机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Steve... - No, please, not the camera.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.90,0:31:24.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不不  等等  汤米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, wait, wait... Tommy, Tommy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.31,0:31:27.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.44,0:31:30.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here you go, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.67,0:31:37.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走吧  比赛要开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, let's go. The game's about to start.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.16,0:31:44.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.61,0:31:59.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Nance!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.69,0:32:01.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.47,0:32:29.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,315\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Three-one-five.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.38,0:32:31.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,315\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Three-one-five.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.14,0:32:33.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,315\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Three-one-five.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.78,0:33:43.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.33,0:33:45.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa! Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.05,0:33:47.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.72,0:33:48.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.02,0:33:50.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.33,0:33:55.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.64,0:34:47.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不可思议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Incredible.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.54,0:35:42.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}El!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.96,0:35:46.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.93,0:35:51.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上来  我们只有几小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hop on. We only have a few hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.51,0:36:04.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我跟蒙蒂老师说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, I told Mr. Mundy...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.12,0:36:07.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"10加Y等于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"The solution of ten plus Y equals...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.53,0:36:08.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,舔我啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}blow me."
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.21,0:36:11.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,胡扯  你真那么做了  这会儿就留堂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bull, if you did that, you'd be in detention right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.45,0:36:12.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,周六\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Saturday.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.77,0:36:14.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,蒙蒂老师肯定还是处呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I bet Mr. Mundy's still a virgin.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.76,0:36:16.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他肯定是处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, he's so a virgin!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.16,0:36:19.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或许你该舔他  卡洛  说不定能分高点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you should blow him, Carol. Help your grades a bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.97,0:36:22.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  你去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa, Nance, where you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.32,0:36:24.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我忘记了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I totally forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.73,0:36:26.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我答应妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told my mom I would, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.61,0:36:28.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会跟她做件事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would do something with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.04,0:36:30.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思  比赛就要开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, what do you mean? The game's about to start.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.10,0:36:31.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.67,0:36:35.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她是怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell's wrong with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.63,0:36:37.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或许她看你对那个疯子发疯时吓到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe she freaked out when you went all psycho on the psycho.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.98,0:36:39.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,少来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, give me a break.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.40,0:36:42.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你指望跟这种完美小姐约会能怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What'd you expect, dating Miss Perfect?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.45,0:36:49.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们为什么伤害你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why did they hurt you?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.02,0:36:51.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.50,0:36:56.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, that.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.74,0:36:59.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就是课间时摔倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just fell at recess.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.98,0:37:01.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-迈克  -怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mike... - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.40,0:37:03.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,朋友要说真话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Friends tell the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.38,0:37:09.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我被一个白痴  特洛伊  绊倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was tripped by this mouth breather, Troy, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.71,0:37:10.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mouth breather?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.87,0:37:12.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯  就是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, you know...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.99,0:37:14.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,蠢蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a dumb person.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.29,0:37:15.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,二货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A knucklehead.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.33,0:37:16.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,二货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Knucklehead?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.91,0:37:19.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道我为什么没直说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know why I just didn't tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.64,0:37:21.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,学校里人人都知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone at school knows.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.30,0:37:24.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就是不希望你觉得我没用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just didn't want you to think I was such a wastoid, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.43,0:37:26.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-迈克  -怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mike... - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.15,0:37:27.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我理解的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.36,0:37:31.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.38,0:37:33.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.55,0:37:56.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.77,0:37:59.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.58,0:38:19.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.56,0:38:31.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.46,0:38:50.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.03,0:40:08.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔  你在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will... are you here?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.54,0:40:14.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  好好好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, good, good, good, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.15,0:40:16.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.11,0:40:20.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闪一次是"是"  闪两次是"否"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, blink once for yes, twice for no.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.38,0:40:22.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以吗  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you do that for me, sweetie?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.82,0:40:23.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you do...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.28,0:40:29.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, good boy. Good boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.29,0:40:31.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  我得知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Baby, I need to know...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.48,0:40:35.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还活着吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.33,0:40:44.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你安全吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you safe?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.77,0:40:59.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要知道怎么找到你  亲爱的  你在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to know where to find you, honey. Where... where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.34,0:41:02.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能告诉我你在哪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you... can you tell me where you are?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.92,0:41:03.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.21,0:41:09.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你  宝贝  我得找到你  告诉我该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, baby. I need to find you. Tell me what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.22,0:41:12.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please just...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.16,0:41:16.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.31,0:41:46.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你提早回来了  比赛怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're home early! How was the game?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.17,0:41:52.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy? What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.04,0:41:54.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是芭比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's Barb.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.74,0:41:55.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.93,0:41:58.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她出事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}something happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.20,0:42:01.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出大事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something terrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.88,0:42:05.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  局长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know, Chief.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.31,0:42:06.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不知道什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What don't you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.52,0:42:09.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这女人  泰芮·艾芙斯  好像真的是疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This lady, Terry Ives, sounds like a real nut to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.67,0:42:13.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的孩子被带走做迷幻剂精神控制实验了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Her kid was taken for LSD mind control experiments?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.11,0:42:15.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她名誉扫地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's been discredited.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.13,0:42:16.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,指控被撤销了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Claim was thrown out...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.13,0:42:17.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  别管她了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, forget about her.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.00,0:42:21.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}精神控制实验被曝光
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.11,0:42:19.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take a look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.81,0:42:22.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-马丁·布伦纳博士  -谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Dr. Martin Brenner. - Who?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.25,0:42:23.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,布伦纳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Brenner.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.84,0:42:25.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他负责霍金斯实验室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He runs Hawkins Lab.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:25.87,0:42:26.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.05,0:42:30.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不觉得有意思吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't find that interesting?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.89,0:42:31.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not really.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.13,0:42:34.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他当年参与了什么嬉皮破玩意  那又如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He was involved in some hippie crap back in the day, so what?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.83,0:42:39.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  这不是嬉皮破玩意  是中情局批准的研究\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, this isn't hippie crap. This is CIA- sanctioned research.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.32,0:42:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不代表他跟我们那孩子有什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't mean he had anything to do with our kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.45,0:42:44.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得了  看啊  他们都穿着病服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Look at that. Hospital gowns. All of 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.52,0:42:46.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那老师在管道边发现的布料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, that piece of fabric that the teacher found by the pipe.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.72,0:42:48.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得看上去很像病服的布料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That sure looked like a hospital gown to me, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.81,0:42:51.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我说错了吗  -我不知道  局长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Am I wrong? - I don't know, Chief.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.45,0:42:52.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.23,0:42:54.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,配合一下啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Work with me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.07,0:42:57.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是说这里有什么大阴谋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not saying that there's some grand conspiracy.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.74,0:42:58.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.38,0:43:05.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是说  或许真出了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm saying maybe something happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.22,0:43:10.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或许威尔在错误的时候出现在了错误的地点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe Will was in the wrong place at the wrong time
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.27,0:43:12.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他看到了不该看到的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and he saw something that he shouldn't have.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.33,0:43:15.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这太牵强  -是个起点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's a reach. - It's a start.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.23,0:43:18.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍威尔  局长在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Powell, is the chief with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.41,0:43:20.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是霍普  什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hopper here. What do you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.25,0:43:36.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}霍金斯警察局
Dialogue: 0,0:44:04.38,0:44:05.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.73,0:44:08.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  威尔住这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, this is where Will lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.66,0:44:09.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,躲藏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hiding.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.82,0:44:12.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不不  他住这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, this is where he lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.43,0:44:14.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他失踪了  不在这儿  懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's missing from here. Understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.73,0:44:20.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们来这儿干什么  -她说他藏在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What are we doing here? - She said he's hiding here.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.38,0:44:21.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.91,0:44:24.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我发誓  如果我们那么远都白走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I swear, if we walked all the way out here for nothing...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.53,0:44:26.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就是白走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's exactly what we did.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:26.37,0:44:29.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我早说她根本什么都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you she didn't know what the hell she was talking about!
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.15,0:44:31.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么带我们来这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why did you bring us here?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.32,0:44:34.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克  别跟她浪费时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike, don't waste your time with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.60,0:44:35.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你想怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want to do then?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:35.44,0:44:37.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,报警  昨天就该这么做了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Call the cops, like we should have done yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.21,0:44:39.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们不能报警  -伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We are not calling the cops! - Hey, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.05,0:44:41.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们还有什么别的选择  -伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What other choice do we have? - Guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.43,0:44:50.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.47,0:45:10.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:10.75,0:45:12.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  宝贝  跟我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, baby, talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.70,0:45:14.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我说话  你在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Talk to me. Where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.91,0:45:18.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,R  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"R." Good, good, good, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:18.26,0:45:19.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  继续\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's good. Come on, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.43,0:45:21.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,I\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"I...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.22,0:45:23.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,G\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}G...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:23.65,0:45:25.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,H  T\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}H... T...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:26.31,0:45:27.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,H\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}H...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.58,0:45:28.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,E\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}E...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.83,0:45:30.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,R  E\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}R... E..."
Dialogue: 0,0:45:31.03,0:45:32.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"就在这儿"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Right here."
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.33,0:45:34.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"就在这儿"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Right here"?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:35.00,0:45:37.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know what that means.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.65,0:45:39.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你告诉我该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to tell me what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:39.55,0:45:40.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我该做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What should I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.78,0:45:44.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我怎么找到你  我该做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do I get to you? How do I find you? What should I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:48.93,0:45:51.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\fs18\b1}跑
Dialogue: 0,0:46:51.38,0:46:52.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:00.39,0:47:02.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  拜托别是那孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God. Please tell me it's not the kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:30.76,0:47:33.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是威尔  不可能的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not Will. It can't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.10,0:47:44.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是威尔  真的是威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's Will. It's really Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:51.67,0:47:52.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike...
Dialogue: 0,0:47:52.91,0:47:54.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"迈克"  迈克什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Mike"? "Mike," What?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:54.90,0:47:57.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你本该帮我们找到活着的他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were supposed to help us find him alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:57.06,0:47:58.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说他还活着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said he was alive!
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.62,0:48:00.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么撒谎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why did you lie to us?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.78,0:48:02.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.46,0:48:04.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有什么毛病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:04.99,0:48:06.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-迈克  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mike... - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:10.35,0:48:12.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克  别这样  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike, come on. Don't do this, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:12.80,0:48:13.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike...
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.81,0:48:16.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克  你去哪  迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike, where are you going? Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:48:21.44,0:48:22.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:48:34.20,0:48:34.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:35.39,0:48:37.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,妈妈  怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mom, what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:41.11,0:48:41.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:47.45,0:48:48.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Michael?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:50.87,0:48:51.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 1,0:02:33.40,0:02:45.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fad(0,1000)\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,200)}{\alpha&FF\t(5825,5825,\alpha&00)}怪{\alpha&00}奇物{\alpha&FF\t(7535,7535,\alpha&00)}语
Dialogue: 1,0:02:33.40,0:02:45.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,243,3406,5908)}{\t(5908,5908,\alpha&FF)}怪{\alpha&FF}奇物语
Dialogue: 1,0:02:33.40,0:02:45.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,231,4031,7535)}{\alpha&FF}怪奇物{\alpha&00\t(7535,7535,\alpha&FF)}语
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.27,0:02:53.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(650,0)\bord0\fs25\t(700,3000,\fs30)\fsp\b1\fn方正粗倩_GBK\c&H00017A&\move(193,214,193,225,700,3000)\u1}第三章\N{\u0}圣诞快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.28,0:02:57.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,1000)\bord0\fs30\t(,,\fs55)\fsp\b1\fn方正粗倩_GBK\c&H00017A&\move(193,225,193,300)\u1}第三章\N{\u0}圣诞快乐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:02.69,0:03:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,0)\bord0\shad0\fscx15\fscy20\p1\c&HFFEBD1&\t(4800,5000,\fscx0\fscy0)\pos(79.5,206.307)}m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 {\p0}
Dialogue: 2,0:03:02.69,0:03:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,0)\bord0\shad0\fscx10\fscy14\p1\c&HECB000&\t(4800,5000,\fscx0\fscy0)\pos(92.9,220.68)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 4,0:03:02.69,0:03:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,0)\bord0\shad0\fscx19\fscy20\p1\1a&H3D&\c&HFFFFFF&\blur10\t(4800,5000,\fscx0\fscy0)\pos(78.5,212.307)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:03:02.69,0:03:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\b1\fscx121\fscy104\bord0\shad0\blur20\c&HECB000&\t(0,1000,1,\blur0)\pos(130.3,223.307)}字幕组\N{\fs15\fscx}ZiMuZu.tv
Dialogue: 1,0:03:03.69,0:03:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\b1\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\c&HECB000&\clip(50,204,52,273)\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,204,335,275))\pos(116.7,239.107)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.69,0:03:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\clip(50,204,52,273)\fad(500,500)\3c&HFFFFFF&\fscx600\fs86\alpha&H9F&\c&H000000&\bord1\shad0\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,154,335,275))\pos(193.2,256.8)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.69,0:03:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\fs16\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\clip(50,154,52,273)\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,154,335,275))\pos(231.9,238.657)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为\N最新最快海外影视字幕下载\N{\fs18}请登陆{\fn方正综艺简体\c&H26F4FF&}www.ZiMuZu.tv
Dialogue: 3,0:03:07.70,0:03:32.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,500,\fscx15\fscy20\t(4750,5250,\fry720\t(9750,10250,\fry0\t(14750,15250,\fry720\t(19750,20250,\fry0\t(24500,25000,\fscx0\fscy0))))))\p1\c&HFFEBD1&\pos(48.8,154.6)\org(51,158)}m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 {\p0}
Dialogue: 2,0:03:07.70,0:03:32.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,500,\fscx10\fscy14\t(4750,5250,\fry720\t(9750,10250,\fry0\t(14750,15250,\fry720\t(19750,20250,\fry0\t(24500,25000,\fscx0\fscy0))))))\p1\c&HECB000&\t(24500,25000,\fry810)\pos(50.8,200.173)\org(51,158)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 5,0:03:07.70,0:03:32.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx18\fscy20\p1\1a&H3D&\c&HFFFFFF&\blur10\pos(39.4,190.973)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.70,0:03:32.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord1\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\alpha&B0\c&H000000&\t(0,200,\fscx2100\fscy600\t(200,400,\fscx2400\fscy300\t(24800,25200,\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\alpha&AA\fscy400\fscx400)))\move(163,211.2,36.5,211.2,24800,25200)\3c&HFFFFFF&}■
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.69,0:03:12.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,290,227))\fs15\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}翻译：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17}怪物{\c&H3CC43C&}草
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.69,0:03:17.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,290,227))\fs15\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}翻译：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17}怪物{\c&H3CC43C&}草
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.69,0:03:22.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fn方正黑体_GBK\bord0\shad0\frx-630\t(0,500,\frx0\t(4500,5000,\clip(40,213,40,248)))\pos(57.12,210.56)\fs15\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}校对：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17}酸奶{\c&H63B8FF&}怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.69,0:03:27.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,0)\bord0\shad0\move(57.12,210.56,400,210.56,4500,5000)\clip(54,195,281,227)\fs15\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\b1}时间轴：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17}苏菲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.69,0:03:32.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(300,300)\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\fs15\3c&HEDB425&\4c&H9EF6FF&\shad0\bord0\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\pos(57.12,210.56)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&HECB000&\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\clip(49,191,295,232)\b1}后期：{\c&HFFFFFF&\fs17\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))}吉吉  {\fs15\c&HECB000&\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))}总监：{\fs17\c&HFFFFFF&\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))}酸奶{\c&H63B8FF&}怪
