[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,18,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 1,0:06:23.14,0:06:35.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fad(0,1000)\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,200)}{\alpha&FF\t(5825,5825,\alpha&00)}怪{\alpha&00}奇物{\alpha&FF\t(7535,7535,\alpha&00)}语
Dialogue: 1,0:06:23.14,0:06:35.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,243,3406,5908)}{\t(5908,5908,\alpha&FF)}怪{\alpha&FF}奇物语
Dialogue: 1,0:06:23.14,0:06:35.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\c&H000012&\bord3\fs80\t(,,\fs40)\3c&H1523C2&\fn方正粗倩_GBK\move(193,285,193,231,4031,7535)}{\alpha&FF}怪奇物{\alpha&00\t(7535,7535,\alpha&FF)}语
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.88,0:06:42.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(650,0)\bord0\fs25\t(700,3000,\fs30)\fsp\b1\fn方正粗倩_GBK\c&H291AF4&\move(193,214,193,225,700,3000)\u1}第二章\N{\u0}不给糖就捣蛋  怪胎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.89,0:06:46.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,1000)\bord0\fs30\t(,,\fs55)\fsp\b1\fn方正粗倩_GBK\c&H291AF4&\move(193,225,193,300)\u1}第二章\N{\u0}不给糖就捣蛋  怪胎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.07,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,247,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,188,340,210)\t(0,500,\clip(30,168,340,190))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.07,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,207,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,220,340,235)\t(0,500,\clip(30,240,340,255))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.07,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord3\blur3\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\pos(145,227)\clip(30,210,340,220)\t(0,500,\clip(30,190,340,240))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:08.57,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14.5\p1\c&HCE8F00&\pos(67,223)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 3,0:00:08.57,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HF6DBA1&\pos(67,223)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35{\p0}
Dialogue: 5,0:00:08.57,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx15\fscy18\p1\c&HFFFFFF&\blur9\pos(58,213)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:08.57,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HECB000&\pos(84,223)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:08.57,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.07,0:00:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新连载海外影视剧下载\N{\fs19\K30}请登陆 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.07,0:00:44.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an9\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx130\fscy170\frz180\p1\alpha&88\c&H000000&\b1\move(-180,245,70,245,0,500)\clip(49,215,304,257)\fad(550,550)}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.57,0:00:44.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an2\fad(550,550)\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx150\fscy170\p1\pos(26,248)\c&HECB000&\b1}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.58,0:00:19.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}翻译    {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.58,0:00:24.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}翻译     {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.58,0:00:29.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}校对     {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.58,0:00:34.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}时间轴     {\c&HFFFFFF&}Ans 大葱 啾啾啾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.58,0:00:39.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}后期     {\c&HFFFFFF&}吉吉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.58,0:00:44.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}总监     {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.18,0:00:07.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再见  迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Goodbye, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.09,0:00:47.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.72,0:00:59.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.70,0:01:06.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克  迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike? Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:08.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.18,0:01:10.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.81,0:01:54.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,二队  汇报情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bravo team, check in.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.92,0:04:04.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,俄罗斯人呢  万一他们来找她呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about the Russians? What if they come looking for her?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.09,0:04:05.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们不知道她在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They don't know where she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.30,0:04:07.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不可能在我们不知道的情况下联络你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And she can't contact you without us knowing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.26,0:04:09.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对你来说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The most important thing
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.27,0:04:11.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最重要的事是继续好好生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is for you to try to go on with your lives
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.99,0:04:15.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-并保守这...  -机密  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- and to keep all of this... - Top secret. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.56,0:04:19.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白  这房子里的都是爱国者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Understood. We're all patriots in this house.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.63,0:04:21.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-从头说起  -我什么都告诉你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Let's go back to the beginning. - I told you everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.93,0:04:23.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这很艰难  迈克尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I understand this is difficult, Michael.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.66,0:04:25.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道她在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know where she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.70,0:04:27.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就算我知道  我也绝不会告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And even if I did, I'd never tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.48,0:04:30.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我绝对不会告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would never tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.82,0:04:32.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这很难接受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know it's difficult to accept,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.71,0:04:35.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她跟你说的并不是事实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the stories she told you were not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.36,0:04:37.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她是一个非常危险的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's a very dangerous individual.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.88,0:04:40.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果她联系你  你必须告诉我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If she contacts you, you must tell us.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.56,0:04:45.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不然你和你的家人就会面临巨大的危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Otherwise, you're putting yourself and your entire family at risk.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.87,0:04:50.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你明白吗  迈克尔  你明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you understand, Michael? Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.12,0:04:52.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Michael?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.47,0:04:54.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Michael?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.22,0:05:01.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,散开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fan out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.59,0:05:04.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,派人去左侧查看  我去右侧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Somebody check the left side, I'll check the right side.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.31,0:07:05.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, Jesus!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.23,0:07:07.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ghost.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.77,0:07:09.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I see that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.74,0:07:11.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-万圣节  -的确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Halloween. - Sure is.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.99,0:07:15.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但现在得先吃早饭  好吗  吃东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But right now, it's breakfast, okay? Come on, let's eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.12,0:07:17.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们看不到我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They wouldn't see me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.55,0:07:21.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谁看不到你  -坏人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Who wouldn't see you? - The bad men.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.18,0:07:23.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.99,0:07:26.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不给糖就捣蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Trick or treat.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.11,0:07:30.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想去玩不给糖就捣蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to go trick-or-treating?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.56,0:07:35.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道规矩的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know the rules.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.95,0:07:37.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是的  但是...  -那你知道答案是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yes, but... - Yeah, so you know the answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.58,0:07:40.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但是他们看不到我  -不  我不管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No, but they wouldn't see me. - No. Hey. I don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.28,0:07:42.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但他们看不到我  -我不管  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- But they wouldn't see me. - I don't care, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.75,0:07:45.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要你出去  不管是不是扮成鬼  都很冒险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You go out there, ghost or not, it's a risk.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.86,0:07:48.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能冒险  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't take risks. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.04,0:07:51.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那样很愚蠢  而且...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're stupid, and...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.94,0:07:53.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不愚蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're not stupid!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.56,0:07:56.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.75,0:08:00.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赶紧拿下来  坐下吃饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, you take that off, sit down and eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.76,0:08:02.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的早饭要凉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your food's getting cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.56,0:08:17.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, look...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.93,0:08:23.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如我明晚早点下班  给你买点糖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about I get off early tonight, and I buy us a bunch of candy,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.12,0:08:24.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们能坐在一起边吃边胖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and we can sit around and get fat,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.92,0:08:26.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后一起看恐怖电影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and we watch a scary movie together?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.02,0:08:29.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样让步怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How's that for a compromise?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.86,0:08:31.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Compromise"?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.57,0:08:37.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让座的让  步伐的步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}C-O-M-promise. Compromise.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.19,0:08:41.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就当做你今天要学的词吧  怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about that's your word for the day? Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.68,0:08:46.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,意思是大家都退一步  大家都一半开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's something that's kinda in-between. It's like halfway happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.49,0:08:49.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,515之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}By 5-1-5?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.77,0:08:53.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,五点十五分之前  好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}5:15. Yeah, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.34,0:08:55.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Promise?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.23,0:08:59.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.43,0:09:01.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.63,0:09:05.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一半开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Halfway happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.62,0:09:24.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.23,0:09:27.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  该起床了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, honey, up and at 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.42,0:09:29.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.96,0:09:32.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-乔纳森  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Jonathan? - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.17,0:09:34.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.68,0:09:36.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -威尔在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What? - Where's Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.83,0:09:38.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他不在自己房间里吗  -不在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He's not in his room? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.32,0:09:41.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.79,0:09:43.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.80,0:09:45.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尿尿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Peeing?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.19,0:09:48.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.13,0:09:51.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.74,0:09:54.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,背上...这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's get this... on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.02,0:09:57.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要一些胶带  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need some tape. Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.66,0:10:12.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.40,0:10:16.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.90,0:10:20.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你又出现幻觉了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you have another episode?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.36,0:10:23.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  这只是...我写的故事中的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, it's just, um... A sketch for a story I'm writing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.98,0:10:27.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.39,0:10:31.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,三  二  一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Three, two, one...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.36,0:10:35.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an3\fs16\bord0\fn微软雅黑\fad(0,0)\b0\pos(374,235)}1984年喜剧电影《捉鬼敢死队》中的主角扮相
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.39,0:10:33.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  拿着质子炮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Great. Hold up the proton blaster.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.62,0:10:37.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  现在把灯打开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, now turn to the light.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.10,0:10:42.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我看看那些珍珠牙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh! I want to see those pearls. Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.90,0:10:44.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an3\fs16\bord0\fn微软雅黑\fad(0,0)\b0\pos(374,235)}1984年喜剧电影《捉鬼敢死队》中的经典台词
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.90,0:10:44.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会打给谁[《捉鬼敢死队》经典台词]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who you gonna call?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.96,0:10:50.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太可爱了  宝贝  太可爱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Adorable, baby. Just adorable!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.84,0:10:54.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-天啊  你真是个呆子  -闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- God. You are such a nerd. - Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.81,0:10:57.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难怪你只和男孩子玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No wonder you only hang out with boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.19,0:10:59.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-艾瑞卡  -事实而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Erica! - Just the facts.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.69,0:11:01.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,呆子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nerd.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.88,0:11:04.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  我真喜欢这套服装  继续\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My God, I love this costume. Keep it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.78,0:11:06.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  最后一张了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, that's the last one.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.01,0:11:08.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  再来一张  拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, just one more. Come on, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.51,0:11:11.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我能去学校了吗  -等等  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Can I go to school? - Wait, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.78,0:11:14.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好了  说"你会打给谁"  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay, say, "Who you gonna call?" - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.32,0:11:22.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-*你会打给谁*  -*捉鬼敢死队*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- *Who you gonna call?* - *Ghostbusters!*
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.65,0:11:23.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯宾格勒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Spengler!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.95,0:11:25.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-伊根  -范克曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Egon! Yeah! - Venkman!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.43,0:11:29.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -你为什么是范克曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What? - Why are you Venkman?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.25,0:11:31.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-因为我是范克曼  -不  我才是范克曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Because I'm Venkman. - No, I'm Venkman.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.03,0:11:32.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么不能有两个范克曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why can't there be two Venkmans?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.77,0:11:34.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为现实中只有一个范克曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because there's only one Venkman in real life.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.35,0:11:35.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们好几个月前就说好了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We planned this months ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.95,0:11:37.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是范克曼  达斯汀是斯坦茨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm Venkman, Dustin's Stantz,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.73,0:11:39.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是伊根  你是温斯顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you're Egon, and you're Winston.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.35,0:11:42.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我明确不同意当温斯顿  -你同意了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I specifically didn't agree to Winston. - Yes, you did!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.09,0:11:45.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我觉得没有  -谁都不想当温斯顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I don't think he did. - No one wants to be Winston, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.17,0:11:46.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,温斯顿怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's wrong with Winston?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.23,0:11:49.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,温斯顿怎么了  他超晚才加入的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's wrong with Winston? He joined the team super late,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.15,0:11:51.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他一点也不搞笑  他都不是个科学家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he's not funny, and he's not even a scientist!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.43,0:11:54.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但他很酷  -如果他很酷  那你当温斯顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah, but he's still cool. - If he's cool, then you be Winston.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.39,0:11:55.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我不行  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I can't! - Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.83,0:11:59.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-因为...  -因因...因为你不是黑人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Because... - B-b-because you're not black?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.10,0:12:00.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没这么说  -你这么想了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I didn't say that! - You thought it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.33,0:12:04.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没这么说  -迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I didn't say that! - Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.97,0:12:08.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伙计们  伙计们  伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Guys... Guys! Guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.17,0:12:13.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么没人扮装\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why is no one else wearing costumes?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.09,0:12:17.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.39,0:12:19.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.90,0:12:22.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家什么时候决定不穿的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When do people make these decisions?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.04,0:12:23.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去年大家都扮装了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone dressed up last year.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.76,0:12:26.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我告诉你们  这是个阴谋  -淡定点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's a conspiracy, I'm telling you. - Just be cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.04,0:12:28.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会打给谁  呆子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who you gonna call? The nerds!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.07,0:12:43.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-要上吗  -现在不行  我们看上去像白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We gonna do this? - Not right now. We look like morons.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.50,0:12:45.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许她喜欢《捉鬼敢死队》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe she likes Ghostbusters?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.12,0:12:47.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她当然喜欢《捉鬼敢死队》  但是这不是重点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course she likes Ghostbusters, but that's not the point.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.53,0:12:50.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,重点是我们现在扮装了  她没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The point is we're dressed up and she isn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.19,0:12:52.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有带日常穿的衣服  你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't bring regular clothes. You?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.29,0:12:52.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.94,0:12:55.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们别无选择  我们要上了  不然没机会了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then we have no choice. We gotta do this. It's now or never.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.66,0:12:57.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没错  -我们上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Right. - Let's engage.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.54,0:13:03.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以下课再问她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could ask her after class.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.65,0:13:05.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没错  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yup. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.30,0:13:11.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看  完全一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See? It's an exact match.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.69,0:13:20.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但他为什么要骗我  -他是个孩子  乔伊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- But... why would he lie to me? - He's a kid, Joyce.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.44,0:13:23.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也听到他描述发作时的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, you heard him describe these episodes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.49,0:13:26.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不像是在讨论噩梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not like he's describing a nightmare.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.04,0:13:28.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说得好像全是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He talks about them like they're real.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.49,0:13:31.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为那不是噩梦  只是闪回\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, because they're not nightmares, they're flashbacks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.33,0:13:33.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认识几个经历过这种事的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know a couple guys who have had these things,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.55,0:13:37.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感觉就像身临其境  感觉好像是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it feels like you're there, like it's happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.36,0:13:41.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那这是什么  -欧文斯说过可能会严重起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Then what the hell is this? - Owens said it would get worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.98,0:13:43.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那个地方  -那你打算怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- That place... - What do you wanna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.14,0:13:44.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要带他回芝加哥吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanna take him back to Chicago?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.05,0:13:47.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个波士顿的家伙应该...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, there's that guy in Boston that's supposed to be...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.71,0:13:49.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们都是一群骗子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're all a bunch of quacks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.38,0:13:52.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们只会和你说一样的话  榨你的钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They'll all tell you the same thing, just cost you more money.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.32,0:13:57.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得他...对创伤的说法没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think he's right... about trauma.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.31,0:13:58.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说得没错  的确已经快一年了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And he's right we're coming up on a year, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.94,0:14:04.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得大家都很难熬  你我...特别是威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think everybody's on edge. Me, you... Will most of all.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.20,0:14:08.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得我们只要撑过接下来几周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think we just gotta get through the next few weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.14,0:14:14.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一切都不会变回原来的样子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing's gonna go back to the way that it was.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.36,0:14:16.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不一定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not really.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.97,0:14:18.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是会好起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it'll get better.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.90,0:14:20.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,假以时日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.04,0:14:30.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Here. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.72,0:14:36.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  霍普\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus! Hopper...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.22,0:14:37.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我想起过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Brings me back to old times.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.22,0:14:39.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.30,0:14:43.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-在五六年级...  -传你的香烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Sharing my cigarettes between... - Fifth and sixth period.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.64,0:14:45.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  在楼梯下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, under the steps.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.89,0:14:48.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一次库伯老师抓到我们了  记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mr. Cooper caught us that time, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.21,0:14:50.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他突然冒出来大喊"小混蛋们"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He was like, "Hey, assholes."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.45,0:14:53.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们跑  我们马上就跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We ran. We just ran.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.37,0:15:08.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  我真想这一切早点结束\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}God, I want this to be over.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.26,0:15:10.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.05,0:16:00.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,情况怎么样  牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How's it looking out there, cowboy?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.32,0:16:02.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你懂的  博士  一如既往\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, you know, Doc. The usual.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.97,0:16:06.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,漂亮  肮脏  再带点辐射\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice and nasty with a chance of radioactivity.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.52,0:16:21.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  都烤透了  有人饿了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yeah, it's barbecued all right. Anyone hungry?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.81,0:16:27.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.73,0:16:30.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们恢复了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...we're back on!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.62,0:16:37.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一场风暴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There was this storm.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.43,0:16:40.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  你看到风暴时有什么感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. So how did you feel when you saw the storm?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.66,0:16:43.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得僵住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I felt frozen.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.02,0:16:46.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冻僵吗  很冷吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Actually frozen? Cold?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.10,0:16:51.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  就是你害怕的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, like how you feel when you're scared,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.80,0:16:55.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会无法呼吸  无法说话  什么都做不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you can't breathe or talk or do anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.79,0:16:58.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能感觉到有股邪恶...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I felt... I felt this evil...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.57,0:17:24.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  你不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy, this isn't you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.50,0:17:31.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭比  你先自己回家吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barb, just go ahead and go home, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.68,0:17:33.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.43,0:17:35.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.18,0:17:38.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.50,0:17:40.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了  你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's going on? Are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.89,0:17:49.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我不能再继续这样下去了  -怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I can't keep doing this. - Doing what?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.44,0:17:51.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,假装一切都没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pretending like everything's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.56,0:17:52.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.62,0:17:54.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芭芭拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barbara.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.92,0:17:56.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家好像都忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like everyone forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.61,0:18:00.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像除了她的父母  根本没人在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like nobody cares. Except her parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.03,0:18:01.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-现在他们要卖了房子  -南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- And now they're selling their house. - Nance...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.50,0:18:04.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们下半辈子都会去寻找她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And they're going to spend the rest of their lives looking for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.55,0:18:06.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我知道  -他们要被毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I know. - It's destroying them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.10,0:18:09.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  但是  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know. I know. Okay? I get it. But listen,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.48,0:18:10.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们什么都做不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}there's nothing we can do about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.50,0:18:13.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以告诉他们真相\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, we could tell them the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.45,0:18:16.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道我们不能这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you know that we can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.48,0:18:17.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不用全部告诉他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't have to tell them everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.83,0:18:19.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是什么游戏  南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This isn't some game, Nance.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.47,0:18:21.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他们发现我们告诉别人...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If they found out that we told any...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.34,0:18:29.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们会把我们抓起来  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They could put us in jail. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.22,0:18:31.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也可能更糟  他们会毁了我们的家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or worse, they could destroy our families.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.14,0:18:33.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们能为所欲为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They could do anything they want.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.49,0:18:36.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想想你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay? Just think about what you're saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.37,0:18:46.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, it's...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.69,0:18:50.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这很难熬  但我们...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's hard, but let's...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.31,0:18:55.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们去蒂娜那个愚蠢的派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}let's just go to Tina's stupid party...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.43,0:18:58.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,穿上我们花了一大把\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}wear our stupid costumes
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.77,0:19:00.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,愚蠢的时间做的愚蠢的服装\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that we've been working on for a stupid amount of time,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.77,0:19:06.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,假装我们就是两个愚蠢的少年  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and just pretend like we're stupid teenagers, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.02,0:19:09.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以吗  就今晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can we just do that, just for tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.10,0:19:13.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.48,0:19:17.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.14,0:19:35.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克斯  我是达斯汀  这是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hi, Max. I'm Dustin, and this is...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.69,0:19:37.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-卢卡斯  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Lucas. - Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.35,0:19:38.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟踪狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The stalkers.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.62,0:19:42.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  其实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, no. Actually...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.37,0:19:44.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没有尾行你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We weren't stalking you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.01,0:19:47.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我们只是担心  因为你是新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, we were just concerned because, you know, you're new and all.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.54,0:19:49.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  为了你的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, for your safety.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.55,0:19:52.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有很多恶霸呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are a lot of bullies here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.53,0:19:55.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-很多很多  太疯狂了  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- So many bullies, it's crazy. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.43,0:19:57.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你们才穿着质子灯捉鬼服吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that why you're wearing proton packs?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.53,0:19:59.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些是没用的 但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, these don't function. But...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.95,0:20:04.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我有这个很好用的小陷阱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I do have this handy-dandy little trap here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.85,0:20:08.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看  还会开关  你看  你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And look, it even opens and closes. Look, look, look...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.75,0:20:10.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Voila!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.07,0:20:12.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很厉害吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's cool, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.65,0:20:14.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不厉害吗  好吧  但是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No? Okay. But, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.17,0:20:17.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们昨天晚上聊到你是新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, we were talking last night, and you're new here,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.78,0:20:19.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可能没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so you probably don't have
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.46,0:20:21.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带你去玩不给糖就捣蛋的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}any friends to take you trick-or-treating,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.34,0:20:24.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怕被人欺负  我们就在想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you're scared of bullies, so we were thinking
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.60,0:20:26.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你跟着我们也行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that it would be okay if you come with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.69,0:20:29.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-也行  -对  我们的团体很民主\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- "It'd be okay"? - Yeah. Our party's a democracy,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.30,0:20:30.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多数投票赞同你来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the majority voted you could come.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.55,0:20:31.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没想到跟你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Didn't realize it was such
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.40,0:20:33.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一起去不给糖就捣蛋是这么大的荣幸啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}an honor to go trick-or-treating with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.07,0:20:33.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  我是说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I mean...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.79,0:20:35.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们知道哪里有大号糖果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We know where to get the full-sized candy bars.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.69,0:20:36.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们觉得你会想加入我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We figured you'd want in.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.01,0:20:38.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你还真是够自以为是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's presumptuous of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.10,0:20:44.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  那...你来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. Totally. Uh, so, um... you'll come?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.45,0:20:50.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们晚上七点在枫叶街胡同见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're meeting at the Maple Street cul-de-sac at 7:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.77,0:20:52.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,七点准时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}7:00 on the dot!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.33,0:20:55.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自以为是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Presumptuous."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.61,0:20:57.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是在夸我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's a good thing, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.48,0:21:02.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is it bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.33,0:21:06.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,卢卡斯  那不好吗  卢卡斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lucas, is it bad? Lucas?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.22,0:21:08.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,混蛋  卢卡斯  那不好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Son of a bitch, Lucas. Is it bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.39,0:21:14.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感觉怎么样  就像丝绸划过你的肌肤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How does it feel? Like pouring pure silk onto my skin.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:17.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无情  冷酷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Inhuman. Relentless.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.43,0:21:21.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿诺德·施瓦辛格是...《终结...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold Schwarzenegger is... The Term...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.09,0:21:23.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我吓坏了  我不知道该怎么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I'm stunned. I don't know what to think.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.73,0:21:26.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你不爱我了吗  -我当然爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Don't you love me? - Of course I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.12,0:21:29.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只不过这太突然了  这一点都不像你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just that it's so sudden. I mean, it's not like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.46,0:21:32.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾瑞卡  我这样都是因为你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Erica, I am this way because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.45,0:21:34.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我  -我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Me? - "Me?"
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.79,0:21:37.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你让我变得不安又狂躁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have made me wild and impetuous,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.24,0:21:38.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就像和你一样  -狂躁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- just like you. - "Impetuous."
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.80,0:21:40.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人们肯定会惊呆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People are going to be aghast.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.48,0:21:43.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-人们肯定会惊呆了  -他们会喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- "People are going to be aghast." - They're gonna love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.90,0:21:48.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,整个小镇都会震惊  整个世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, it's gonna stun the whole town. The whole world!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.44,0:21:52.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾瑞卡  告诉我你会嫁给我  今晚在这里...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Erica, tell me that you will marry me, in this house, tonight...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.31,0:22:52.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会伤害你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not gonna hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.22,0:22:55.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你叫什么名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.72,0:22:59.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你冰天雪地在这里干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What're you doing out here in the cold?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.74,0:23:25.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1}警察局
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.71,0:23:44.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是说梅瑞尔对你的农场下毒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, you're telling me that Merrill poisoned your farm,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.44,0:23:47.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为他认为你给他的农场下毒  而你没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because he thinks you poisoned his, which, of course, you didn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.45,0:23:50.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我有他说我下毒那晚的不在场证明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, sir. And I got me an alibi the night he accuses me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.76,0:23:53.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的珍妮和她的孩子们在城里  整晚我都陪着他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My Jenny and her boys were in town. I was with them all night.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.12,0:23:54.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看到梅瑞尔下毒了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you actually see Merrill?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.50,0:23:57.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不需要  那家伙是个疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No need. That man done lost his mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.14,0:23:59.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到处诽谤我  疯疯癫癫地威胁我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Went around slandering me, threatening all sorts of madness.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.74,0:24:01.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南瓜阴谋  局长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A pumpkin conspiracy, Chief.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.33,0:24:03.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍金斯的《唐人街》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hawkins' very own Chinatown.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.11,0:24:05.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  梅瑞尔威胁要做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen, Merrill threatening to do something
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.14,0:24:06.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和他真的做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and him actually doing something
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.32,0:24:07.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是两件截然不同的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are two very different things.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.79,0:24:09.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有更好的解释吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got a better explanation?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.29,0:24:09.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,寒冷的天气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cold weather.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.94,0:24:11.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在是十月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's October.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.07,0:24:12.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  很冷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, it's a cold one.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.04,0:24:14.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看到这双手了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see these hands?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.01,0:24:16.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-嗯  -你知道为什么会变成这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. - You know why they look like that? -
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.48,0:24:18.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你老了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because you're old?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.51,0:24:19.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're damn straight.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.85,0:24:23.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我管理农场很久了  局长  很久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I've been doing this a long time, Chief. A long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.92,0:24:26.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我从来没见过这种情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I ain't never seen anything the likes of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.83,0:24:27.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}None of us have.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.13,0:24:29.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}None of us?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.14,0:24:30.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅瑞尔昨晚不仅只对我家下手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Merrill didn't just hit me last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.90,0:24:32.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他几乎对每户人家都下手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He hit damn near everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.44,0:24:33.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.28,0:24:35.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·奥戴尔  彼得·弗里林\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jack O'Dell, Pete Freeling,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.59,0:24:38.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里克·尼利  克里斯坦森一家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick Neary, the Christensens.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.28,0:24:41.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们家的庄稼都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All of their crops, dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.98,0:24:45.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再说一遍名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me those names again.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.23,0:25:02.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你再迟到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're late again.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.18,0:25:03.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我得先做完作业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I had to get catch-up homework.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.73,0:25:05.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  我不关心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus. I don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.59,0:25:07.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你再迟到  就自己滑回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're late again, and you're skating home.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.50,0:25:08.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.22,0:25:23.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  这地方真是个屎坑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}God, this place is such a shithole.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.74,0:25:25.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有那么糟糕  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's not that bad. - No?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.70,0:25:33.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闻到了吗  麦克斯  这就是屎味\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You smell that, Max? That's actually shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.88,0:25:36.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-母牛屎  -我没看到母牛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Cow shit. - I don't see any cows.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.14,0:25:38.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你肯定是没见过高中女生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Clearly, you haven't met the high-school girls.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.57,0:25:41.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么  你现在喜欢这里了吗  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- So what, you like it here now? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.92,0:25:43.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那你为什么要维护这里  -我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Then why are you defending it? - I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.95,0:25:45.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听起来像是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure sounds like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.16,0:25:49.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反正我们被困在这里  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just we're stuck here, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.39,0:25:51.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说得对  我们被困在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're right. We're stuck here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.26,0:25:54.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是谁的错呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And whose fault is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.94,0:25:56.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.81,0:25:59.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你说什么  -没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What'd you say? - Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.54,0:26:02.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你说是我的错吗  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Did you say it's my fault? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.28,0:26:05.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道是谁的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know whose fault it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.73,0:26:07.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Say it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.03,0:26:11.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Max...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.98,0:26:13.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}say it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.19,0:26:17.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Say it!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.58,0:26:30.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的  去年大家都扮装了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really, everyone dressed up last year.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.29,0:26:31.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比利  减速\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Billy, slow down.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.96,0:26:34.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你的新乡巴佬朋友吗  -不  我不认识他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, these your new hick friends? - No! I don't know them.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.57,0:26:36.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你肯定不介意我撞他们吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess you won't care if I hit 'em, then?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.48,0:26:38.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一次全部撞倒有额外奖励吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I get bonus points, I get 'em all in one go?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.42,0:26:40.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  比利  别玩了  这不好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, Billy, stop. It's not funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.61,0:26:45.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.21,0:26:49.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比利  别闹了  这不好玩  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Billy, come on, stop it. It's not funny. Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.23,0:26:51.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-快快快  -迈克  我们得赶紧避开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Go! go! go! go! go! - Mike, you need to haul ass!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.63,0:26:52.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比利  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Billy, stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.38,0:26:55.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死  该死  该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa! Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.74,0:26:58.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,差一点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah! That was a close one, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.88,0:27:00.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上帝啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Holy shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.98,0:27:02.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Was that...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.66,0:27:05.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,疯狂麦克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mad Max.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.98,0:27:17.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1}南瓜自选\N2个4元
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.08,0:27:35.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在还想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, you tryin' to tell me,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.25,0:27:38.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,认真地告诉我  这是因为天气冷吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with a straight face, cold did this?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.73,0:27:40.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,延伸到哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How far does it go?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.38,0:28:01.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,局长  收到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Chief, you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.36,0:28:04.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,局长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Chief.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.18,0:28:05.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那边情况如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How's it looking over there?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.33,0:28:09.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像有个巨人尿在杰克的豆田里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like a giant pissed all over Jack's bean field.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.69,0:28:11.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闻上去也是  你那边有味道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Smells, too. It smell over there?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.29,0:28:13.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯  有一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, yeah, little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.73,0:28:16.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闻上去跟疗养院似的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Smells like a nursing home, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.71,0:28:19.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们跟着这些腐烂的区域  看看延伸到哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen. I want you guys to track the rot, see how far it goes.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.48,0:28:21.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,标记一下所有死掉的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just, uh, mark anything that's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.73,0:28:24.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那得花点时间  -那就花这个时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- That's gonna take some time. - So take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.88,0:28:27.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不知道到底是怎么回事  可能是毒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And, look, we don't know what caused this. Could be poison.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.19,0:28:29.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以不要不戴手套碰任何东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So don't touch anything without gloves.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.61,0:28:34.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  局长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Copy that, Chief.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.11,0:28:37.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有标志旗吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got any marking flags?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.58,0:28:55.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你按T是放大  W是缩小\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So you hit "T" To zoom in, and "W" Zooms back out.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.15,0:28:57.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看  小菜一碟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See? Easy-peasy.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.31,0:29:00.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记得要关闭电源省电\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just make sure to turn off the power to save energy there.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.03,0:29:02.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  跟着你的哥哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen. Stay close to your brother, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.84,0:29:04.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  听着  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And listen, listen, listen...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.39,0:29:06.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你感觉不舒服之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you get a bad feeling or anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.30,0:29:08.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就要他赶紧把你送回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you tell him to take you straight home.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.14,0:29:09.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要保证  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You promise? - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.24,0:29:09.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.11,0:29:11.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-准备好了吗  伙计  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Are you ready, bud? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.13,0:29:14.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,注意安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.60,0:29:17.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望不会太糟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hope it doesn't suck!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.46,0:29:24.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不懂她看上他什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just don't get what she sees in him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.10,0:29:25.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.56,0:29:27.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.21,0:29:30.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少他不会对我区别对待\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At least he doesn't treat me different.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.08,0:29:34.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我都不能自己去玩不给糖就捣蛋  真逊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, I can't even go trick-or-treating by myself. It's lame.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.76,0:29:36.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么  你觉得我很逊吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? You think I'm lame?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.72,0:29:39.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  但是南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, but it's not like
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.31,0:29:41.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才不会去看着迈克  你懂吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nancy's coming to watch over Mike, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.97,0:29:50.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will! Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.73,0:29:55.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别越过小河  别越过小河\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, don't cross the streams. Don't cross the streams!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.55,0:30:02.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.66,0:30:04.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.72,0:30:07.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我让你自己去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If I let you go on your own,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.95,0:30:09.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你保证只会去附近要糖吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you promise to stay in the neighborhood?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.65,0:30:11.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保证  保证  当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah! Yeah, yeah, totally.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.23,0:30:12.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后九点前回迈克的家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And be back at Mike's by 9:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.72,0:30:14.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-九点半  -九点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- 9:30? - 9:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.13,0:30:15.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  -说好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. - Deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.74,0:30:17.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-说好了  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah, deal. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.65,0:30:19.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Will.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.27,0:30:21.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别让你的呆瓜朋友们用这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't let any of your spazzy friends use this, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.43,0:30:22.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.90,0:30:25.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望不会太糟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hope it doesn't suck.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.68,0:30:27.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.71,0:30:31.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-伊根  -今晚准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Egon! - Yeah! You ready for tonight, man?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.89,0:30:36.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1}蒂娜的万圣节派对
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.80,0:30:37.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Awesome!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.23,0:30:49.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,38  39  40  41  42\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...thirty-eight, thirty-nine, forty, forty-one, forty-two!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.17,0:30:53.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,42\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Forty-two!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.54,0:30:57.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,新的啤酒桶之王诞生了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got ourselves a new Keg King!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.36,0:30:58.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-比利  比利  比利  -这才像样  霍金斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Billy! Billy! Billy! - That's how you do it, Hawkins!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.95,0:31:00.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这才像样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's how you do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.78,0:31:05.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比利  比利  比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Billy! Billy! Billy!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.28,0:31:25.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,新的啤酒桶之王诞生了  哈灵顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got ourselves a new Keg King, Harrington.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.59,0:31:28.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没错  -吃瘪吧  哈灵顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah, that's right! - Yeah. Eat it, Harrington.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.27,0:31:45.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里面是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's in this?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.99,0:31:49.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,纯燃料  纯燃料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pure fuel! Pure fuel!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.53,0:31:57.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take it easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.40,0:31:59.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢点  南茜  南茜  南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take it easy. Nance, Nance, Nance...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.93,0:32:01.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们今晚就是愚蠢的少年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're just being stupid teenagers for the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.51,0:32:02.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是说好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wasn't that the deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.77,0:32:37.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不不不  -来吧  来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No. No, no. - Come on. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.00,0:32:40.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-来来来  来吧  -不不不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yes. Yes. Yes. Come on. - No. No. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.58,0:32:42.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这才对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, there it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.69,0:32:47.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在我德古拉面前扮科学怪人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You playing Frankenstein to my Dracula?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.14,0:32:50.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你僵硬得和石板似的  放松  -对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Come on, you're stiff as a board. Relax. - I'm sorry. It's...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.88,0:32:56.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他没事的  乔纳森和他一起呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's fine. Okay? Jonathan's with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.82,0:32:57.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.45,0:33:00.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是每次他不在我身边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just every time he's away from me,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.83,0:33:02.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就好像无法安心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's like I can't function.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.75,0:33:07.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我知道这听起来很蠢  -不  这不蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I know it sounds silly. - No, it's not silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.10,0:33:09.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.87,0:33:17.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一起离开霍金斯...怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if we were to move out of Hawkins... together?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.50,0:33:18.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What? - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.59,0:33:21.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是吧  内莉[歌名]  不  我只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa, Nellie, right? No, I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.94,0:33:23.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直在想你说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been thinking about what you said.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.31,0:33:26.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在这里的这些记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}About how we've got all these memories here,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.23,0:33:27.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以及你真希望能有钱就能搬走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you wish you had enough money to move.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.46,0:33:30.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的父母要卖掉他们在缅因州的房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, my parents are selling their house in Maine.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.98,0:33:33.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,边上有一家翻睿侠  我能去那里工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's a RadioShack nearby. I'm sure they'd take me on.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.03,0:33:34.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们能...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could just...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.83,0:33:41.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-现在轮到我傻了  -鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- My turn to be silly now. - Bob...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.72,0:33:44.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  没事  我喝了酒就会说胡话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, it's fine. Wine makes me crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.83,0:33:47.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太难解释了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, it's just so hard to explain.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.91,0:33:51.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just this...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.60,0:33:54.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是个普通的家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is not a normal family.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.03,0:33:56.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以变得普通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It could be.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.29,0:34:00.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以变得普通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It could be.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.51,0:34:13.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,终于来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Finally.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.79,0:34:17.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,受害者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Victims.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.52,0:34:24.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不给糖就捣蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Trick or treat!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.45,0:34:28.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们真可爱  小除虫员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, aren't you cute? The little exterminators.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.37,0:34:34.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再收到三个火枪手牛轧糖我就自杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If I get another 3 Musketeers, I'm gonna kill myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.68,0:34:36.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,三个火枪手怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's wrong with 3 Musketeers?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.09,0:34:37.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,三个火枪手怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"What's wrong with 3 Musketeers?"
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.65,0:34:39.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没人喜欢三个火枪手  -只是牛轧糖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No one likes 3 Musketeers. - Yeah, it's just nougat.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.91,0:34:41.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是牛轧糖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa. "Just nougat"?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.41,0:34:43.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是牛轧糖  对我来说可是头三名的糖果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just nougat? It is top three for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.88,0:34:45.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-头三名  -头三名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Top three? - Top three!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.63,0:34:47.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  饶了我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God. Give me a break.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.12,0:34:49.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说真的  我能一口气吃下整整一大碗牛轧糖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seriously, I can just eat a whole bowl of nougat. Straight up.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.95,0:34:57.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  你们真该看看你们的表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Holy shit! You should have seen the look on your faces.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.29,0:34:59.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有你  谁会这么尖叫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you? Who screams like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.05,0:35:00.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你听上去像个小姑娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You sound like a little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.62,0:35:04.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们到底来不来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, you guys coming or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.66,0:35:06.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听说应该去洛克诺拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I heard we should hit up Loch Nora.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.59,0:35:07.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,富人们都住在那里  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's where the rich people live, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.43,0:35:11.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.42,0:36:03.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.06,0:36:05.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  被你抓到了  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, you got me, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.88,0:36:08.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,万圣节快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Happy Halloween.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.17,0:36:18.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死  该死  该死  该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.83,0:36:43.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1}霍金斯警察局
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.45,0:36:46.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,孩子  能给我一些糖吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, kid. Give me some of that candy, would you?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.13,0:36:48.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.09,0:36:53.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那现在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right. How about now?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.09,0:36:57.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是谁  我是玛利亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who are you? I'm Maria.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.87,0:37:00.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你愿意陪我玩吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will you play with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.49,0:37:05.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想要我的花吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Would you like one of my flowers?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.47,0:37:20.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,L\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}L...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.38,0:37:24.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1}国际莫斯码
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.20,0:37:22.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,A\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.27,0:37:24.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,T\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}T...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.66,0:37:27.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,E\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}E.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.09,0:37:30.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Late.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.90,0:38:29.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1}洛克诺拉
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.59,0:38:35.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,又是一大块的糖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Another full-size.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.95,0:38:39.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说真的  有钱人真是冤大头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like, seriously, rich people are such suckers.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.01,0:38:41.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  你不是有钱人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait. You're not rich, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.53,0:38:43.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我住在老樱桃街\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I live up Old Cherry Road.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.73,0:38:47.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  那条街用来滑板很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, it's fine. I mean, the street's good for skating.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.27,0:38:49.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  弯弯曲曲的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, totally tubular.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.89,0:38:54.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了  我念得不对吗  还是说扭扭曲曲的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? Did I say that right? Or is it, like, tubular.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.66,0:38:58.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该是歪歪扭扭的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's, like, totally tubular.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.82,0:39:01.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-歪歪扭扭的  -真陡的坡  哥们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Totally tubular! - What a gnarly wave, dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.84,0:39:05.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-毛绒绒的  哥们  -别闹了  我耳朵疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Totally brodacious, bro! - Stop. My ears are hurting.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.31,0:39:14.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你同意了吗  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Did you agree to this? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.85,0:39:16.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让她加入我们团队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To her joining our party.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.01,0:39:18.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是万圣节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just for Halloween.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.17,0:39:19.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你应该先和我说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should have checked with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.90,0:39:21.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们很开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, they were excited.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.20,0:39:22.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为你不会介意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess I thought you'd be okay with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.95,0:39:24.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她毁掉了一年中最棒的夜晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's ruining the best night of the year.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.49,0:39:38.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小心点  僵尸小子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Watch it, Zombie Boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.84,0:39:41.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不给糖就捣蛋  怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Trick or treat, freak.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.00,0:39:59.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.58,0:40:01.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.61,0:40:07.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.70,0:40:54.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.61,0:40:56.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威尔  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will, what's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.94,0:40:58.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我到处找不到你  你没受伤吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I couldn't find you. Are you hurt?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.95,0:41:00.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Holy shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.41,0:41:03.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他没事吧  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Is he okay? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.26,0:41:04.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我送你回去  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna get you home, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.90,0:41:06.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我马上送你回去  扶着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna get you home. Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.78,0:41:08.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好了  别紧张  -我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- All right, take it easy. - I got him.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.09,0:41:10.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.11,0:41:12.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续要糖吧  反正我也觉得无聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep trick-or-treating. I'm bored anyways.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.95,0:41:16.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's wrong with him?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.58,0:41:51.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,服装不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice costume.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.92,0:41:53.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,服装不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice costume.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.95,0:41:57.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  我扮成一个讨厌参加派对的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, uh, yeah. I'm going as a guy who hates parties.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.92,0:42:00.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我叫萨曼莎  -乔纳森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm Samantha. - Uh, Jonathan.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.05,0:42:13.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲吻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kiss?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.50,0:42:15.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是说这个乐队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The band.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.54,0:42:19.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不不不  -放开我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No, no, no. - Get off.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.66,0:42:22.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  你喝得够多了  -去你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No, you've had enough, okay? - Screw you!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.38,0:42:25.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  我是认真的  别喝了  我是认真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nance, I'm serious. Hey. Hey. Hey. Stop. No, I'm serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:25.96,0:42:27.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-放下来  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Put it down. - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.24,0:42:29.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-南茜  放下来  -史蒂夫  放开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Nance, put it down. - Steve! Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.46,0:42:30.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放开我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop. Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.65,0:42:37.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,搞什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.20,0:42:39.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nance.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.86,0:42:51.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,南茜  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nance, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.52,0:42:54.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-擦不掉的  南茜  -擦得掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- That's not coming off, Nance. - It's coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.69,0:42:57.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来  我送你回家吧  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Let me just take you home, okay? Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:58.09,0:43:00.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我送你回家吧  来  -你想要这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Let me take you home. Come on. - You wanted this.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.96,0:43:03.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我不想这样  我要你别喝了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I didn't want this. I told you to stop drinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.22,0:43:05.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-都是胡扯  胡扯  -不  不是胡扯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's bullshit. Bullshit. - No, it's not bullshit. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.61,0:43:07.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  这不是胡扯  -不  你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No, it's not bullshit, Nancy. - No, you.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:08.61,0:43:11.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你胡扯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:11.59,0:43:12.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:12.68,0:43:16.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你假装一切都没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're pretending like everything is okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.21,0:43:22.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像我们...我们没有杀死芭比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, like we didn't... like we didn't kill Barb.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:23.54,0:43:29.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像都很好  好像我们相爱  然后去派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like, it's great. Like, we're in love and we're partying.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.96,0:43:34.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好啊  我们去派对  派对  我们来派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, let's party, huh? Party. We're partying.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.99,0:43:37.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,简直是胡扯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:39.71,0:43:41.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像我们相爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Like we're in love"?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:43.16,0:43:45.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,胡扯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.17,0:43:49.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不爱我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't love me?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:50.69,0:43:52.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是胡扯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.53,0:44:24.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像...好像我被困住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like... like I'm stuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.71,0:44:26.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像困在逆世界了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like, like, stuck in the Upside Down?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.88,0:44:29.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.68,0:44:32.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道在视觉大师里  会变得...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know on a View-Master, when it gets, like...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.98,0:44:34.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-夹在两边中间  -是的  差不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Caught between two slides? - Yeah. Like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.91,0:44:38.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像一边是我们的世界  另一边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like one side's our world, and the other...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.68,0:44:41.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一边是逆世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The other slide is the Upside Down.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.45,0:44:46.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:47.67,0:44:52.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后到处都有声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And there was this noise coming from everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.22,0:44:57.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后我看到一些东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then I saw something.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.87,0:45:01.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-魔王吗  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- The Demogorgon? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:02.06,0:45:08.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像是天空中的巨大阴影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was like this huge shadow in the sky.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.57,0:45:13.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只不过是活的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Only, it was alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:14.89,0:45:16.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且要来抓我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And it was coming for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.11,0:45:21.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些都是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is this all real?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.23,0:45:25.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是说像医生说的那样  都是你想象的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or is it like the doctors say, all in your head?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.45,0:45:28.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  只不过...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know. Just...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:29.87,0:45:32.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托不要告诉其他人  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just please don't tell the others, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.24,0:45:34.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们不会明白的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They won't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.19,0:45:39.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十一会明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Eleven would.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.16,0:45:41.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She would?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.38,0:45:43.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:44.35,0:45:45.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她总是能明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She always did.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.43,0:45:52.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有时我觉得我还是能看到她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes I feel like I still see her.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.29,0:45:57.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她好像还在身边  但她不在了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like she's still around, but she never is.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:59.47,0:46:02.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道  有时候我觉得我都疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know. Sometimes I feel like I'm going crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:03.27,0:46:04.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:08.28,0:46:10.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们都疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, well, if we're both going crazy,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.30,0:46:12.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们就是一起疯  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then we'll go crazy together, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:13.53,0:46:16.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  一起疯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. Crazy together.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:18.56,0:47:19.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔纳森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jonathan?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:11.85,0:48:15.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,孩子  开门  听着  我知道我迟到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, kid. Open up, all right? Look, I know I'm late.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.81,0:48:18.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我买了糖  我买了好东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got candy here, all right? I got all the good stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:23.74,0:48:26.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托你  能开门吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, will you open the door?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.06,0:48:28.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我快被冻死在外面了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna freeze to death out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.44,0:48:48.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,孩子  能开门吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, kid. Open up, would you?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:50.49,0:48:56.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我...有事拖住了  忘了时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got, uh... stuck somewhere, and I lost track of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.20,0:49:00.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.01,0:49:04.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一一  你能开一下门吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}El, would you please open the door?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.64,0:49:07.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}El?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.06,0:49:13.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.11,0:49:19.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我就自己在这里  把糖都吃光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just gonna be out here by myself, eating all this candy.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:19.98,0:49:21.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要变胖了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna get fat.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:22.48,0:49:24.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一个人在这里很不健康\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's very unhealthy to leave me out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:26.19,0:49:28.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能会心脏病发之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Could have a heart attack or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.33,0:49:32.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是  随便你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But, you know, you do what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:37.46,0:49:39.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,四分之一磅的美国牛肉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One quarter pound of all-American beef,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.97,0:49:43.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现切西红柿和四条脆培根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}fresh-cut tomato, and four strips of crispy bacon.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.15,0:49:46.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人说培根了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did somebody say bacon?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:46.95,0:49:48.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,新鲜柠檬...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Refreshing lemon...
Dialogue: 0,0:49:48.49,0:49:50.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,泡一泡更美味\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...and they're perfect for dunking. Mmm!
Dialogue: 0,0:50:26.38,0:50:28.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第353天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's day 353.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:32.56,0:50:34.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今天过得很不开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had a bad day today.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:35.52,0:50:36.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know. I...
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.09,0:50:40.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你能在我身边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess I wish you were here.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:41.75,0:50:43.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是说  我们都希望你在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, we all do.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:46.30,0:50:49.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你在  求你给我一些信号\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're out there, just please give me a sign.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:57.59,0:50:58.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.36,0:51:01.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Eleven?
Dialogue: 0,0:51:56.14,0:51:57.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弯弯曲曲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tubular.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:58.99,0:52:00.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弯弯曲曲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tubular.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:01.35,0:52:02.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弯弯曲曲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tubular.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:08.29,0:52:10.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喵喵  是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mews, is that...
Dialogue: 0,0:52:20.38,0:52:23.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,完了  完了  完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:44.09,0:52:45.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Holy sh...
