[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 未设定
Original Script: 未设定
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[Aegisub Project Garbage]
Scroll Position: 438
Active Line: 442
Video Position: 4279

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.39,0:00:03.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,《生活大爆炸》前情提要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.31,0:00:07.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得到了普林斯顿大学的夏季研究奖学金\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was offered a summer research fellowship at Princeton.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.18,0:00:09.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很不错的大学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A fine institution.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.29,0:00:11.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔伯特·爱因斯坦教过书的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The place where Albert Einstein taught,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.87,0:00:13.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱纳德也是在那里拿到博士学位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and where Leonard got his PhD,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.99,0:00:15.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以那学校可能没落了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so it may have gone downhill.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.51,0:00:19.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,各位  还记得诺维茨基博士吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gentlemen, you may remember Dr. Nowitzki.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.03,0:00:21.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她又回来加州理工读博士后啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's back at Caltech for her postdoc.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.29,0:00:28.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问一下  你是想和我发展恋爱关系吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Question. are you seeking a romantic relationship with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.46,0:00:30.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我是呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if I were?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.21,0:00:32.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这会引起一系列的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, that would raise a number of problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.91,0:00:36.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是同事  我现在有女友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're colleagues, I'm currently in a relation...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.69,0:00:42.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米  艾米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Amy? Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.72,0:00:44.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Amy?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.78,0:00:56.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,300)\bord0\shad3\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HFFFFFF&\fscy112\fsp1\b1\pos(188.632,266.143)}时至今日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.41,0:00:59.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你愿意嫁给我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will you marry me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.17,0:01:03.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请稍等我一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One moment, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.93,0:01:07.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是吧  你要在这节骨眼接电话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really, you're going to answer that right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.39,0:01:08.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是莱纳德打来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's Leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.08,0:01:09.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想失礼嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want to be rude.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.53,0:01:11.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.34,0:01:12.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你上哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, hey, where you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.49,0:01:13.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打你电话找你好久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've been calling you for hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.87,0:01:16.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  我的手机之前开了飞行模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I'm sorry, my phone was on "Airplane" mode.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.77,0:01:17.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.11,0:01:20.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我在飞机上"飞行"啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I was on an airplane.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.73,0:01:23.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开免提\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, put him on speaker.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.25,0:01:24.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你去哪里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. ?Hey, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.92,0:01:27.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来普林斯顿大学找艾米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I came to Princeton to see Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.49,0:01:29.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说来也挺有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a funny story, actually.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.21,0:01:31.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我当时在跟诺维茨基博士共进午餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was having lunch with Dr. Nowitzki,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.96,0:01:33.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后她亲吻了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and she kissed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.50,0:01:34.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -啥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Excuse me? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.17,0:01:35.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.58,0:01:38.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在那一刻我意识到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And in that moment, I realized
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.68,0:01:41.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米才是我余生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that Amy was the only woman I ever wanted to kiss
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.76,0:01:43.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唯一想亲吻的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the rest of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.52,0:01:47.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我来新泽西跟她求婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So I came to New Jersey to ask her to marry me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.29,0:01:49.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真是太甜了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, that's so sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.17,0:01:51.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢尔顿...  -不过呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Sheldon... - Yeah, although
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.09,0:01:54.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的确是先去征求了某位男士的祝福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}there was one man whose blessing I needed first.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.90,0:01:58.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想过了  我确实想要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've thought about it, and I really want to spend
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.37,0:02:00.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与艾米共度余生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the rest of my life with Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.41,0:02:03.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会祝福我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do I have your blessing?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.35,0:02:05.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, Sheldon...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.20,0:02:10.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得你应该将她的手指变成土星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...I think you should make her finger like Saturn
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.39,0:02:13.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再往她手指上套个土星"环"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and put a ring on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.38,0:02:17.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你去问了霍金博士而不是艾米父亲吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You asked Stephen Hawking and not her father?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.66,0:02:19.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍金博士是个天才\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stephen Hawking's a genius.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.35,0:02:23.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他不支持  我才不要浪费时间去问她爹呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If he said no, I wasn't gonna waste my time on her father.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.98,0:02:25.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你有问过我父亲吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you did ask my father?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.82,0:02:27.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有  他同意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did. He said yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.75,0:02:31.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但不是用机械人式语音说的  所以没那么酷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Although, not in a robot voice, so it wasn't nearly as cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.09,0:02:33.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的天啊  真不敢相信你们订婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. Oh, my God, I can't believe you guys are engaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.56,0:02:34.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没订上婚呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're not engaged, yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.96,0:02:36.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这都半天了她还不回答我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's taking forever to answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.56,0:02:38.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是因为你在讲电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because you're on the phone!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.77,0:02:42.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们稍后回电\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll call you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.93,0:02:48.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她同意了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She said yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.75,0:02:50.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恭喜你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yay! ?Congratulations!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.80,0:03:19.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,母亲  我有好消息与你分享\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mother, I have some good news to share.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.64,0:03:21.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们订婚啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're engaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.87,0:03:25.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我真为你们开心  但我一点都不惊讶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am so happy for you two, but I'm not surprised.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.96,0:03:27.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我为此事祈祷多时了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been praying for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.39,0:03:29.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这件事上帝没半点功劳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, God had nothing to do with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.20,0:03:32.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,完全是因为我跟别的女人接了吻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It happened because I was kissing another woman,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.20,0:03:35.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,令我意识到我想跟艾米共度余生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it made me realize I wanted to be with Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.56,0:03:37.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,居然有超过一名女性对你有兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}More than one woman was interested in you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.68,0:03:40.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可能祈祷太猛了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I might have prayed a little too hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.12,0:03:41.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  我想先...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait, oh, and I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.80,0:03:43.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想现在就跟你说清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want to let you know right now
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.12,0:03:45.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不会在教堂里成婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that we are not getting married in a church.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.23,0:03:46.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's all right, Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.28,0:03:49.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,耶稣在哪里  那便是教堂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anywhere Jesus is is a church.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.24,0:03:50.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他不会在我们婚礼上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, he won't be at our wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.68,0:03:52.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会在我心里  所以只要我人在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's in my heart, so if I'm there,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.82,0:03:54.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he'll be there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.84,0:03:56.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  那他就是你带的伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, well, then, he's your plus-one.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.05,0:03:58.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你带人的名额就用完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't get to bring anyone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.08,0:03:59.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's fine. Love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.68,0:04:01.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也爱你  再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Love you, too. Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.64,0:04:04.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,主啊  谢谢您\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lord, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.66,0:04:06.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,虽然您无所不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even though you can do anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.66,0:04:10.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但这事真显出了您的无上威能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that was mighty impressive.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.43,0:04:12.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们订婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're engaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.69,0:04:14.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God, that's amazing!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.65,0:04:16.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢着  快告诉我整个经过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait, uh, tell me everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.42,0:04:18.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样的  诺维茨基博士亲了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, Dr. Nowitzki was kissing me...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.85,0:04:21.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以别再用这事当故事开头了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, you can stop leading with that part of the story.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.78,0:04:23.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恭喜你们啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, congratulations.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.99,0:04:25.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太为你们俩高兴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm so happy for you two.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.59,0:04:27.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,稍等  我得告诉伯纳黛特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold on, I have to tell Bernadette.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.38,0:04:28.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,妮妮  你猜怎么着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Bernie, guess what?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.78,0:04:31.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢尔顿跟艾米订婚啦  你敢信吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sheldon and Amy got engaged. Can you believe it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.68,0:04:36.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  我真不敢相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God. I cannot believe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.70,0:04:40.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她好像高兴到...  在喜极而泣啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's so happy... I think she's crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.39,0:04:44.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得谢尔顿会想要办一场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you think Sheldon's gonna want
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.97,0:04:47.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,奇葩的《星舰迷航》风婚礼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}some weird Star Trek wedding?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.42,0:04:50.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.61,0:04:52.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱纳德当时想说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, Leonard could barely finish the words
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.24,0:04:53.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"《神秘博士》婚礼蛋糕"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Doctor Who wedding cake"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.67,0:04:56.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没说完就被我狠狠拒绝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before I shut that down hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.11,0:05:00.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有在听我说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you listening to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.54,0:05:03.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有啊  你对莱纳德毫无人性  我听到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, you're mean to Leonard. I heard you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.27,0:05:06.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.80,0:05:08.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要告诉你一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I'm gonna tell you something,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.31,0:05:09.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你不许惊慌失措\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you can't freak out,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.68,0:05:11.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我已经很手足无措了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because I'm already freaking out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.66,0:05:13.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God, what is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.06,0:05:15.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我又怀孕了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm pregnant again.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.30,0:05:16.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wha...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.50,0:05:25.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有点儿意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Interesting.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.94,0:05:29.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,霍华德知道了会疯的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Howard's gonna lose his mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.88,0:05:31.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢着  你还没告诉他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait, you haven't told him yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.32,0:05:32.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.29,0:05:35.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你第一个告诉我吗  妮妮小亲亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You told me first? Oh, Bernie!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.65,0:05:39.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事不应该啊  我们很小心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This wasn't supposed to happen-- we were careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.13,0:05:40.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对啊  我本来还以为哺乳期内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I didn't even think you could get pregnant
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.22,0:05:41.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,女人是不会怀孕的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}while you were breastfeeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.34,0:05:43.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,结果呢  老娘就怀了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, guess what? You can.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.69,0:05:46.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  听着  这是桩好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, look, look, this is a good thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.41,0:05:47.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样哈雷就会有个弟弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Halley's gonna have a little brother
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.79,0:05:49.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者妹妹陪她玩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or sister to play with.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.11,0:05:51.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想那应该是会挺有爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess that would be pretty cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.77,0:05:53.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道吗  我也是我爸妈的意外之喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And, you, know, I was a surprise to my parents,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.73,0:05:55.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爸说我是发生在他们身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and my dad said it was the best thing
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.06,0:05:56.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最美好的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that ever happened to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.99,0:06:00.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  也许这个宝宝是上天的恩赐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. Maybe this baby actually is a blessing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.23,0:06:02.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  亲爱的  当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God, honey, of course it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.42,0:06:05.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我怎么会又怀上了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How am I pregnant again?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.33,0:06:07.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对啊  你们怎么搞的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, what were you thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.32,0:06:14.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,机票确认好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, I'm all checked in to my flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.12,0:06:15.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要走了我好难过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I'm sad you're leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.99,0:06:18.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么你订当天来回呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why'd you only book a flight for one day?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.37,0:06:20.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来是为了求婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I came here to propose.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.61,0:06:22.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要是你拒绝我  我可不想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you'd said no, I wouldn't want to stick around
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.56,0:06:24.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,留下来看着你的蠢样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}looking at your stupid face.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.60,0:06:28.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样的  只有你拒绝我的情况下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, mind you, your face is only stupid
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.54,0:06:31.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你才会是一脸蠢样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the "No" version of the story.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.56,0:06:35.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我答应了  现在能享用你这货一辈子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I said yes, so I get a lifetime of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.29,0:06:37.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  聪明样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, you do, smart face.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.49,0:06:40.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如你多待几天吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't you stay a few extra days?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.73,0:06:42.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没带别的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I don't have any other clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.72,0:06:43.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以去买\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll get you some.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.79,0:06:45.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要了吧  我这个人很挑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I don't know, I'm pretty particular.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.90,0:06:48.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离这儿不到1600米的地方有家漫画店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, there's a comic book store less than a mile from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.50,0:06:50.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,棒  买买买\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perfect, let's go shopping.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.01,0:06:54.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对了  我今晚要跟同事共进晚餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, um, and I'm having dinner with some colleagues tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.39,0:06:56.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们会很高兴见到你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure they'd love to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.11,0:06:59.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来嘛  好不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, what do you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.77,0:07:02.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你开始用烦我的招数了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Aw, you're nagging me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.42,0:07:04.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感觉我们已经结婚了似的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like we're already married.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.89,0:07:06.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那到底好不好嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that a yes or a no?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.21,0:07:09.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  留点力等蜜月了再叨逼叨吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Geez, save some for the honeymoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.25,0:07:14.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,瞧  那是诺维茨基\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at Nowitzki over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.03,0:07:17.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不敢相信她想从艾米身边\N\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't believe she tried to steal Sheldon from Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.19,0:07:18.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,瞧好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.24,0:07:20.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要过去告诉她  他们订婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna go there and tell her that they're engaged now
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.34,0:07:22.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的小把戏落空了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and that her little plan didn't work.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.17,0:07:23.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是因为你想维护谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because you're sticking up for Sheldon,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.48,0:07:25.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是因为你还在气她拒绝了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or because you're still mad she rejected you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.43,0:07:28.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,距离太远  听不到你在讲什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Too far away, can't hear you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.20,0:07:30.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  拉蒙娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello, Ramona.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.64,0:07:31.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.95,0:07:34.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么独自一人坐在这呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why are you sitting by yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.44,0:07:35.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, that's right,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.71,0:07:39.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢尔顿在新泽西  他和艾米订婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sheldon's in New Jersey being engaged to Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.38,0:07:41.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.50,0:07:43.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在谢尔顿闪边去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now that Sheldon's out of the picture,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.17,0:07:46.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以再给你个机会跟我约会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could give you one more chance to go out with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.49,0:07:49.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢邀  不用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nope, I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.79,0:07:52.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.98,0:07:56.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小爷可不会再问第二次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will not ask again.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.71,0:07:59.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我真心希望你不会再问了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I sincerely hope not.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.57,0:08:01.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.67,0:08:05.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那在气氛变尴尬之前我先撤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm going to leave before this gets awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.41,0:08:10.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要我做晚饭吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Want me to make dinner?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.89,0:08:13.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好啊  不过你能先坐下来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, sure, but first, why don't you have a seat?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.05,0:08:15.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有东西给你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's something I need to show you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.43,0:08:19.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是晚饭教程的话就完美了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ooh, if it's how to make dinner, that'd be great.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.56,0:08:29.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是...  验孕棒吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is this a... pregnancy test?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.21,0:08:31.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.57,0:08:38.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这表示...  有了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That means... positive?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.56,0:08:40.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.90,0:08:42.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.93,0:08:47.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.13,0:08:49.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}N-- No.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.67,0:08:53.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.30,0:08:56.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.85,0:09:03.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这怎么可能发生呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How could this even happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.21,0:09:05.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们这么小心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, w-- we were careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.37,0:09:06.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就是发生了  -不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Well, it did. - ?No!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.96,0:09:09.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我不能接受  -接受现实吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}-Yes! Yes! - ?No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.29,0:09:10.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  好吧  行吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay! Okay! Okay!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.53,0:09:12.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, w-what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.49,0:09:13.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么叫"我们该怎么办"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you mean what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.65,0:09:14.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们又要生一个宝宝了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna have another baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.63,0:09:15.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  不  -别叫了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No! No! ?- Stop that!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.85,0:09:18.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就是怀了  -我也想不叫啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}?- Yes! - No, I'm trying!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.78,0:09:23.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这感觉很可怕  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I know it's scary, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.53,0:09:27.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都是负责任的成年人  我们能行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we're both responsible adults, we can do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.07,0:09:28.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真这么想吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You really think so?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.66,0:09:31.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.58,0:09:37.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  斯图尔特  -你好  拉杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Hey, Stuart. - Oh, hey, Raj.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.67,0:09:38.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么能帮到你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What can I help you with?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.56,0:09:40.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要买一份订婚礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to buy an engagement gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.65,0:09:43.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你来错地方了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you came to the wrong place.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.14,0:09:45.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是送给谢尔顿和艾米的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's for Sheldon and Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.58,0:09:47.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不是吧  他们订婚了  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No way! They're engaged? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.18,0:09:49.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真是个令人激动的好消息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, that's exciting news.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.59,0:09:51.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁能想到谢尔顿和艾米会是下一对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who would've thought Sheldon and Amy would be the next two
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.75,0:09:52.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喜结连理的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to tie the knot?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.95,0:09:54.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可不是嘛  我才是那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me about it. I'm the one
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.51,0:09:58.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在莱纳德和佩妮婚礼上接到捧花的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who caught the bouquet at Leonard and Penny's wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.51,0:09:58.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}通常是女生抢捧花\N抢到捧花的人会延续幸福/最快下一个结婚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.59,0:09:59.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.89,0:10:00.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh... you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.91,0:10:03.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们可能会喜欢这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they might like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.97,0:10:07.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,超人和神奇女侠  挺浪漫的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Superman and Wonder Woman, it's kind of romantic.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.00,0:10:09.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.16,0:10:11.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我干嘛给他们买礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why am I buying them a gift?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.68,0:10:12.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们已经拥有爱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They have love.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.72,0:10:14.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,幸福脱单的都去死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Screw them and their happiness.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.50,0:10:17.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有没有适合苦逼单身狗的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you have for someone who's bitter and alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.62,0:10:20.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,基本上全部都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Literally everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.70,0:10:25.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢尔顿  这两位是我研究小组的领导\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sheldon, these are the heads of my research team.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.82,0:10:27.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  -赞恩博士  哈里斯博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, hello. - Dr. Zane, Dr. Harris,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.44,0:10:29.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我未婚夫  谢尔顿·库珀博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this is my fiance, Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.74,0:10:30.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我第一次这样叫他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the first time I've said that
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.82,0:10:32.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我都荡漾得起鸡皮疙瘩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it kind of gave me the goose bumps.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.29,0:10:34.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,库珀博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dr. Cooper,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.90,0:10:37.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很高兴能见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we are so excited to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.15,0:10:38.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太客气了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, that's very kind of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.74,0:10:42.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想要的话  饭后我可以在你们的菜单上签名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you'd like, I could autograph your menus after dinner, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.65,0:10:45.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但最好别让我发现你们拿去网上拍卖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I better not see those on eBay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.71,0:10:47.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不不  我们只是很开心能见到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no, we're just excited to meet the man
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.77,0:10:50.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赢得这位才华横溢女士的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who landed this brilliant woman here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.18,0:10:51.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那一点都不难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That wasn't hard,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.80,0:10:54.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是她倒贴我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she threw herself at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.00,0:10:58.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但要让宇宙向我展露"私密"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, getting the universe to show me its naughty bits,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.01,0:11:00.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那才需要费一番功夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that-that took some doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.36,0:11:03.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢尔顿是物理学家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sheldon's a physicist.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.76,0:11:05.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,挺不错啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, that's nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.54,0:11:10.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米  我最近读了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Amy, I recently read your paper on lesions
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.22,0:11:12.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关于嗅觉受体损伤的论文\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the olfactory receptors in the brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.70,0:11:14.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,非常富有创见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was inspired.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.21,0:11:16.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看来水平不算太臭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, well, I guess it didn't stink.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.86,0:11:19.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但即使臭了  那只老鼠也闻不到 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if it did, that rat wouldn't have known it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.59,0:11:21.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}?I'm sorry,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.24,0:11:22.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你肯定不想坐在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure you don't want to sit here
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.50,0:11:24.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我们聊工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and listen to a bunch of work talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.26,0:11:25.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我很喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no, I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.45,0:11:26.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们来聊工作吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, but let's talk about work.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.50,0:11:28.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米的工作  我的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Amy's work, my work.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.17,0:11:30.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如就先聊我的工作吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, why don't we start with my work?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.04,0:11:33.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还真有个问题想问库珀博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Actually, I do have a question for Dr. Cooper.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.42,0:11:36.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米首次告诉你她对突触追踪的切入点时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When Amy first told you about her approach to synaptic tracing,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.86,0:11:39.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有意料到会给这个领域带来巨大变革吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}did you think it was gonna revolutionize the field?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.20,0:11:41.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.72,0:11:43.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要问的就是这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's your question?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.43,0:11:46.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么  你是综艺节目《今夜娱乐》的人吗 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you, Entertainment Tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.79,0:11:47.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.30,0:11:49.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来给你提供一个更好的问题  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me give you a better question. Here,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.20,0:11:50.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"库珀博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}um, "Dr. Cooper,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.27,0:11:52.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听说你正在为美国军方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I heard you were working on a top-secret project
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.79,0:11:54.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,研究一个最高机密项目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the U.S. Military.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.08,0:11:55.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如跟我们说说这个吧"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't you tell us about that?"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.23,0:11:57.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这才是个好问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, that's a great question.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.26,0:12:00.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  那项目怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, what was that like?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.83,0:12:03.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能告诉你  那可是最高机密\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I can't tell you that, it's top-secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.03,0:12:12.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,刚才好心累\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Boy, that was exhausting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.79,0:12:15.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无意冒犯  但你的同事很无礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, no offense, but your colleagues were pretty rude.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.28,0:12:19.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  是他们无礼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really, they were rude?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.00,0:12:19.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.95,0:12:22.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们只会一直说你的事  说你有多了不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They just kept talking about you and how great you are,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.91,0:12:25.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,完全无视我多次提起我自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}no matter how many times I brought me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.33,0:12:27.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们是我的同事  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, these are my colleagues
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.70,0:12:29.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想谈论我的工作成果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and they want to talk about my work.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.07,0:12:31.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这有什么好让你不爽的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why does that bother you so much?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.17,0:12:32.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我也在场啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I was there.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.25,0:12:35.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就像请《变形金刚》的擎天柱来吃饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like having Optimus Prime over to dinner
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.13,0:12:37.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,却不叫他变身卡车一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and not asking him to turn into a truck.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.03,0:12:40.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道吗  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what, Sheldon?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.21,0:12:43.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你并非永远都是房间里最聪明的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not always the smartest person in every room.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.03,0:12:45.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你很可能都不是这房间里最聪明的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You may not even be the smartest person in this room.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.82,0:12:47.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I am sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.14,0:12:50.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难道尼尔·德格拉塞·泰森躲在沙发后面吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, is Neil deGrasse Tyson hiding behind the couch?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.14,0:12:50.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}著名天体物理学家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.30,0:12:51.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果真是  他也没多聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause if he is, he's not that smart,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.79,0:12:53.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为后面挺多灰的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's pretty dusty back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.98,0:12:58.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要去哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.30,0:12:59.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要气冲冲地回我的房间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm storming off to my room.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.97,0:13:02.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我能气冲冲地走去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, then where am I supposed to storm off to?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.12,0:13:04.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你那么聪明  怎么不自己想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you're so smart, why don't you figure it out?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.79,0:13:10.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有其他卧室吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there another bedroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.00,0:13:14.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者小房间之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps a-a den?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.81,0:13:20.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们对你子宫里那个新事件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, how are you guys doing with all the new
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.47,0:13:23.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,适应得怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}events in your womb?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.68,0:13:27.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.73,0:13:30.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很明显这事我们也没预料到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Obviously, it was a surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.30,0:13:32.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发生了一些哭泣和争吵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There was some crying and some yelling.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.60,0:13:35.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有些打和好炮的提议被拒绝了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some suggestion of make-up sex that did not go over well,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.01,0:13:37.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哪怕我们并不会怀上加怀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even though it's not like we can get more pregnant.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.27,0:13:42.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们意识到这是一份礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But then we realized that it's a gift, in the sense
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.98,0:13:44.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,虽然我们没有主动要求\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that we didn't ask for it,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.71,0:13:46.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也没有主动选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and we may not have chosen it...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.21,0:13:48.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且我们已经有一个了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we already have one.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.98,0:13:52.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每当我买到喜欢的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, whenever I find a top I like,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.55,0:13:55.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就会回去再买一件同款不同色的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I always go back and get a second one in a different color.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.96,0:14:03.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望你们的宝宝不会是不同色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which I hope is not the case with your baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.91,0:14:08.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你们吓坏了  但你们是很好的父母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know you guys are freaked out, but you're great parents,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.43,0:14:10.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们如果需要帮忙  我们随时都在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and if you ever need help, we are here for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.46,0:14:12.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  不管什么忙  开口就是了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, anything at all, just ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.13,0:14:15.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道你们能做什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ooh, you know what you could do?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.63,0:14:17.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们可以也生个宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You could have a baby, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.89,0:14:23.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思  你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, what?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.56,0:14:27.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真是个好主意  我们可以一起经历这个过程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, that's a great idea, we could go through it together.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.01,0:14:28.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那一定会很好玩  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wouldn't that be fun?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.31,0:14:30.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们刚刚才在说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You guys were just saying
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.46,0:14:32.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们有多害怕多凄惨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}how freaked out and miserable you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.94,0:14:35.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我经常说疯话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I say a lot of crazy things.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.00,0:14:37.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,毕竟我怀孕了  体内激素发生变化\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm pregnant and hormonal.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.96,0:14:40.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  生个宝宝  干起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do it! Have a baby, do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.56,0:14:44.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那画面超级萌  我们的孩子在一起玩耍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, it'd be so cute, our kids playing together?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.38,0:14:45.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么样  你们俩快去把床单滚起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you say, why don't you two hit the old mattress
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.94,0:14:47.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赶紧搞出个娃娃来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and whip up a family?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.33,0:14:49.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们才不会为了让你们开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, we're not gonna have a baby
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.56,0:14:51.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就赶紧生孩子呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just to make you guys feel better.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.16,0:14:54.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想让我俩生孩子  除非是我们准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, if we're gonna have a baby it's gonna be when we are ready,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.16,0:14:55.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者我确定佩妮要抛弃我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or when I'm certain Penny is gonna leave me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.99,0:14:57.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.29,0:15:03.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们都是我的朋友  我应该为他们高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're my friends, and I should be happy for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.81,0:15:04.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也努力过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A-And I'm trying,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.75,0:15:09.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我只感到满腹纠结和莫名的空虚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but all I feel is this gnawing, empty sensation in my gut.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.73,0:15:11.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也曾有过这种感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had that once.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.38,0:15:13.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,后来发现是我肚里长了绦虫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Turned out it was a tapeworm.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.99,0:15:17.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cool. Uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.39,0:15:22.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是...  这种事很难跟其他朋友聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just...it's hard talking to my other friends about this,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.83,0:15:24.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我想你可以理解我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I knew you would understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.52,0:15:25.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.63,0:15:27.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你和我都是单身狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because you and I are both alone,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.38,0:15:29.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想想还真是抚慰人心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}which is actually kind of comforting,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.18,0:15:31.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少我们单着的路上有个伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because at least we can be alone together.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.40,0:15:33.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这真是太尴尬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mm. This is-this is awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.82,0:15:37.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今晚本来打算提早关店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I, um, I was actually gonna close up a little early tonight
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.09,0:15:38.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我要去约会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'cause I have a date.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.56,0:15:40.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.50,0:15:41.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.20,0:15:46.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请原谅我无法为你感到开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Forgive me if I'm having trouble being happy for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.02,0:15:51.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小傻瓜  痛在你身  乐在我心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't be silly, I'm loving your pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.62,0:15:56.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这会是我俩结婚以后的状态吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is this how our marriage is going to be?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.92,0:15:58.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有时候人们会更愿意和她说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes people will be more interested
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.39,0:16:00.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而不是和我说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in talking to her than to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.51,0:16:02.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在人在厕所吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you sitting in a bathroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.40,0:16:05.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.48,0:16:07.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要一个能让我摔门冲入的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I needed a place to storm off to
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.18,0:16:09.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是唯一可以的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it was all that was available.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.14,0:16:10.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.87,0:16:15.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果有冲马桶的声音  谈话立刻结束\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if I hear a flush, this conversation is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.87,0:16:19.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些人的面前有一位世界级的智者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Those people were in the presence of a world-class mind,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.11,0:16:22.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而他们却只想聊那些无聊废话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and all they wanted to talk about was their own nonsense.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.49,0:16:25.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能听出其中的讽刺意味吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you see the irony in that statement?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.15,0:16:29.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听出来没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about now?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.55,0:16:34.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about now?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.23,0:16:38.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我等你慢慢想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.92,0:16:43.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.27,0:16:45.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,糟了  今天是我们的纪念日吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, crap, is it our anniversary?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.21,0:16:48.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.36,0:16:53.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.21,0:16:55.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  那我们是在庆祝什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, so what are we celebrating?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.97,0:16:58.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道  博纳黛特和霍华德又怀孕了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you know, Bernadette and Howard are pregnant again,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.76,0:17:00.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米和谢尔顿也要结婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and Amy and Sheldon are getting married.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.29,0:17:02.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想让你感到受冷落\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't want you to feel left out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.87,0:17:04.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么  受冷落吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah. Left out?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.00,0:17:05.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,博纳黛特肚子里要长一个小宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, Bernadette has to grow a baby inside of her,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.88,0:17:07.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米马上要嫁给另一个小宝宝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and Amy has to marry one.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.19,0:17:08.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的人生非常圆满\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My life is great.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.12,0:17:12.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你不想吃这蛋糕了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So do you not want the cake?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.16,0:17:14.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把它端走试试  看你怎么死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Try and take it away, see what happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.74,0:17:19.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,糟了  今天真是我们结婚纪念日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, crap, it is our anniversary.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.58,0:17:22.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,结婚纪念日快乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Happy anniversary!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.81,0:17:27.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.26,0:17:31.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有些事我要告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's something I need to say to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.07,0:17:33.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm listening.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.55,0:17:37.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直在想复仇者联盟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been thinking about the Avengers.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.60,0:17:40.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I believe that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.18,0:17:44.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我觉得这没什么好跟我说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I don't think that's something you needed to say to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.45,0:17:49.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我意识到钢铁侠超屌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I realized that Iron Man is great.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.29,0:17:52.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但同时  美国队长也很不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And also, that Captain America is great.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.40,0:17:56.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有时钢铁侠还会出现在美国队长的电影里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And sometimes, Iron Man is in a Captain America movie,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.04,0:17:59.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他也不会因为这不是钢铁侠电影而生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and he's not mad it's not an Iron Man movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.00,0:18:01.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他只是帅气飞来  让观众热血沸腾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, he can fly in, give the audience a thrill,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.93,0:18:03.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后再霸气飞走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then fly away.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.83,0:18:06.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今晚应该这么表现才对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that should've been me tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.95,0:18:10.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我应该当你电影中的讨喜龙套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I should've been the delightful cameo in your movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.48,0:18:13.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you, Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.28,0:18:15.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相反的  我表现得像暴怒的绿巨人一样...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Instead, I was like the Hulk, and I...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.74,0:18:17.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,够了  请不要再提复仇者联盟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, please stop talking about the Avengers.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.74,0:18:20.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总而言之\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.93,0:18:23.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我为你骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm proud of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.48,0:18:25.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以后会尽量学习分享目光焦点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I'm going to try to do a better job
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.69,0:18:29.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我们是同一个队的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of sharing the spotlight because we're a team.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.77,0:18:35.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你懂吗  我们就像是棒球道奇队的球员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know? Much like t-the Dodgers.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.03,0:18:41.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他们有超能力  会打击犯罪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If they had superpowers, and fought crime.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.73,0:18:43.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且雷神索尔也在队里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And Thor was in them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.87,0:18:47.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢尔顿  我知道这很不容易\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sheldon, I know this isn't easy,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.52,0:18:51.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你会有一辈子来慢慢练习\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you'll have a whole lifetime to practice.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.15,0:18:54.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许真的需要这么久  我对此非常不在行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-It could take that long, I'm really bad at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.58,0:18:59.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许... \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, maybe, um,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.49,0:19:03.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我该从现在开始  赶紧回帕萨迪纳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I should start right now, and go back to Pasadena
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.94,0:19:06.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你好好独自享受这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and let you have this experience to yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.56,0:19:08.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就是想回到那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You just want to go back
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.53,0:19:10.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家都稀罕你的地方吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'cause that's where everybody makes a fuss over you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.69,0:19:13.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的同事说得对  你真是冰雪聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, your colleagues are right, you are brilliant.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.59,0:19:22.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(300,300)\bord0\shad3\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HFFFFFF&\fscy112\fsp1\b1\fs22\pos(192,217.6)}3个月后
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.45,0:19:21.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们好呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.54,0:19:23.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾米  欢迎回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Amy, welcome back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.13,0:19:24.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我看看订婚戒指\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, l-let me see the ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.92,0:19:26.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,美死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ooh, nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.75,0:19:28.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喂喂  别乱看呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}H-Hey, her eyes are up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.66,0:19:33.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就是亲了谢尔顿的女人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-Is that the woman who kissed Sheldon?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.68,0:19:39.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有可能  -很难说  跟我们说说普林斯顿的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Uh... Could be. - Hard to say. Tell us about Princeton.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.45,0:19:40.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请稍等我一会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Excuse me for a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.53,0:19:43.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我们之后再聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not-- well, we'll catch up later.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.12,0:19:44.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这将是自从我的阿姨在家族聚会上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is going to be the biggest smackdown
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.81,0:19:46.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和我表姐穿了同样的沙丽之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}since my Aunt Noopur showed up at the family reunion
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.97,0:19:50.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最大的一次撕逼大战了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}wearing the same sari as my cousin Sruti.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.15,0:19:54.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诺维茨基博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dr. Nowitzki?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.84,0:19:59.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,福勒博士  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dr. Fowler. Um, hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.81,0:20:03.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  我衷心谢谢你全家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you. Thank you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,247,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,188,340,210)\t(0,500,\clip(30,168,340,190))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,207,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,220,340,235)\t(0,500,\clip(30,240,340,255))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\p1\bord3\blur3\shad0\fscx150\fscy0\t(0,400,\fscy160)\alpha&566\c&H000000&\pos(145,227)\clip(30,210,340,220)\t(0,500,\clip(30,190,340,240))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:00.40,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14.5\p1\c&HCE8F00&\pos(67,223)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 3,0:00:00.40,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HF6DBA1&\pos(67,223)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35{\p0}
Dialogue: 5,0:00:00.40,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx15\fscy18\p1\c&HFFFFFF&\blur9\pos(58,213)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:00.40,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HECB000&\pos(84,223)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172{\p0}
Dialogue: 1,0:00:00.40,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 1,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新连载海外影视剧下载\N{\fs19\K30}请登陆 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.44,0:03:10.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\bord0\shad0\fscx150\fscy170\frz180\p1\alpha&88\c&H000000&\b1\move(-180,245,70,245,0,500)\fad(500,500)\clip(49,215,345.6,257)}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.44,0:03:10.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx150\fscy170\p1\pos(26,248)\c&HECB000&\b1}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.44,0:02:58.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻译     {\c&H0BFDFE&}钢铁赛打爆美队  {\c&HFFFFFF&}灰灰是菇凉  油腻希  猫中之王
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.44,0:03:02.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}校对     {\c&H0BFDFE&}单亲爸爸赛太公  {\c&HC69FF4&}退休跑路YY猫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.44,0:03:06.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx150\fscy170\p1\pos(157,248)\c&HECB000&\b1}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.44,0:03:06.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}后期      灰灰是菇凉      时间轴    三水
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.44,0:03:10.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}总监     {\c&H0BFDFE&}新浪微博@赛太公
Dialogue: 6,0:03:10.79,0:03:12.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\move(156.6,76,156.6,75.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H232727&\fs10\t(0,271,0.4,\fs47)\fscy80\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}生
Dialogue: 6,0:03:10.79,0:03:12.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\move(156.6,108,156.6,107.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H232727&\fs10\t(0,271,0.4,\fs47)\fscy80\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}活
Dialogue: 6,0:03:10.79,0:03:12.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\move(185.4,88,185.4,87.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H070729&\fs12\t(0,271,0.4,\fs50)\fscy110\fscx90\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}大
Dialogue: 6,0:03:10.79,0:03:12.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\move(212.4,79.2,212.4,78.4)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H010044&\fs8\t(0,271,0.4,\fs40)\fscy\t(271,1481,1,\fs41)}爆
Dialogue: 6,0:03:10.79,0:03:12.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\move(237,86.4,237,85.6)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H050061&\fs8\t(0,271,0.4,\fs40)\fscy\t(271,1481,1,\fs41)}炸
Dialogue: 6,0:03:10.79,0:03:12.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\move(189,242.4,189,244)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H2D2F2F&\fs3\t(0,271,0.4,\fs18)\fscy110\fscx90\t(271,1481,1,\fs18.5)}第十一季  第一集
